What's wrong?  You're scaring me.
Sis, you've been had by that Yamada guy.
That bastard...  Was talking about you on the internet!
How you two met...  Your fears...
He showed it all on the internet and made a fool out of you!
You're kidding...
I can't...
This is unbelievable.
He betrayed you.
Here, look.
The time with the stalker...
Our parents' divorce...  Stuff that should've been kept private...
He talks about it all in detail!
Please, stop!
Oh no, it's not just that
There's all this other sick ramblings about you on this board!
Saori
Yamada's here.
That bastard...
Keisuke?
Good morning.
Um, what...
You made a show out of sis all over the internet
Keisuke, stop.
Let him explain himself.
I heard about the message board
...and about how you wrote about me on it...
...is that true?
Oh...  Um...  Well, that...
So it was true.
Well...  Actually...
I came here to talk about that...
Was it fun?
Talking about me...
having a good laugh from talking about me...
...was it fun?
That's not what I was trying to do.
That board...
I...
...didn't know how to date women, and so...
I don't want to hear it.
I was a fool for believing in you.
Please...
...don't show yourself in front of me again.
You've got it wrong!
Sis's world is way too different from yours.
Wait, please...  Stop!
(In Japanese culture, a man will say 'mother' to his wife...)
I only wanted to talk to you...
(...since family members address each other using...)
It's not like I'm going to turn on the TV!
(...the point of view of the youngest in the family)
You okay?
No, I'm not okay, thanks.
Yeah, I guess not...
C'mon, c'mon!
It's fixed!
Densha!  I've returned!
I've been...  Totally shut out by Hermes...
...this time, it's the end...  For real...
What happened...
...while I was away?
The details!
Densha Otoko
Subtitle timing by chandlerkim@gmail.com
Translation by Masakun
Scripting by Masakun
Editing by Masakun
For subtitles with asterisks on them
check the ending credits
See, I told you not to spill the beans on this board!
It's Densha's choice.  There isn't much we can do about it.
Why didn't I stop him from telling her...  I'm such an idiot!
Is it because you told her about this place?
By the time I got there, she had already found out.
It seemed like her brother told her about this.
Shit, she found out on her own!
Her younger brother?
I can't believe this board found its way so close to her!
Well, even a middle schooler like me knew about this. (*1)
Who built up all the excitement about this board!?
That would be us...  and you.
I'm so sorry, momma.  (*2)
So, in other words, is Hermes reading this board?
Wow I sat up straight when I realized Hermes might be looking.
Hermes!  Oh, um, I should get changed!
I really don't think she'll be looking here.
Both Hermes and her younger brother...
...didn't like this board one bit.
I guess it can't be helped if they're inclined to think that way.
That's how girls usually feel about us.
I feel relieved, but also kinda sad...
I guess I can write here a little easier.
How'd she turn you down without having even looked here?
I think it was a bit much for her when she realized...
...that she was being talked about behind her back.
I tried explaining but my words fell on deaf ears...
You have to set the record straight - there's still hope.
You went out to tell her about this place, anyway.
Come on, you can't give up here!
Just keep explaining it to her until she understands!
We are now departing for the House of Hermes!
It's impossible.
Her younger brother...
told me that Hermes and I come from different worlds...
...and that really made me feel like I'm not someone...
...who is suitable for Hermes.
Even if I she understands about this board...
...someone like me won't be able to keep her happy...
...in a relationship...
...even if I got that far.
I thought I was struggling for her...
...when I threw away my otakuness...
...but I was working hard so she wouldn't dislike me...
...and it wasn't an effort to get her to like me.
...it really wasn't.
I only realized this after she asked me...
...to not show myself to her again.
I don't think there's going to be...
...anything more between the two of us.
Hey!
Are you really okay with that!?
It's too early to throw in the towel!
Give it another shot!
Come on, we've got your back!
I think that's enough.
You did really well.
At first, I looked down on you, Densha.
Getting all worked up all over a phone call to thank her...
...it was like we all had to push you up and give you support...
but...
...now you're way ahead of the rest of us.
After all this, if you think it's time to give up...
...then that must really be the case.
You did really well.
Take care. (*3)
I guess guys like us...
have no right to second-guess the choice you made.
It would just be an exercise in futility.
This time around, it's a lot more than you lying to her.
I know it's tough, but use this as a lesson and go look for someone else.
No way!  It's too frustrating to see it end like this!
Densha, let's go back to the home of the Single Man.
Densha Otoko...  You're a real man!
And to think that a newbie like me built a bomb shelter and was hiding in it...
Me too!
Give it another shot!
You did well.
You gave courage to all of us.
Thanks to Densha, it looks like I'll fail my entrance exams again.
For now...  Just build up your muscles!
Thanks for the World Cup-class feeling you gave me!
Last stop...  Last stop...
Densha, I'm sure you'll find a wonderful person soon!
Hey I've been dumped 15 times in a row.  No worries!
Densha, I really liked you.
I'll treasure the three months I spent with you, Densha.
I don't think...
I'll ever write here again...
...but I'll never forget you guys...
Thank you so much.
Shoot, I can't find anything to do again...
(you know he's crying for real when there's snot coming out of his mouth...)
Matsunaga...  Matsunaga...  Matsunaga...  Matsunaga...
You mean the sea turtle?
Yeah.
Actually, he isn't just a sea turtle.
He's a sea turtle who gives birth to money!
Apparently he owns a lot of land in Nagoya.
He makes $300k a year without lifting a finger!
Can you believe this?
I found a treasure somewhere I didn't expect.
Hey hey hey, look here.
His handsome eyebrows and his bangs that aren't parted anywhere...
They hint at the look of a heir to a noble family!
Senpai, are you really going after Sea Turtle?
After we get back from our business trip to Italy...
...we're going on a date!
Do you have no sense of pride?
I threw that out to the sewer as soon as I hit 30.
Sorry
What's wrong?
You're usually not late to work, Saori.
Here, your plane tickets.
What's wrong?
It looks like you cried.
Did something happen between you and Yamada again?
I've decided not to see him anymore.
Huh?
This time
it really is the end.
What do you mean?
What's up with him?
He said something about a love rivalry he started on his own and lost.
I see...
Hey, so it's true that Yamada and Saori broke up?
What?  They broke up?
It's not like they were going out in the first place
That Densha...  What the hell is wrong with him?
I've gone through so much shit because of that guy.
Hm?
Wait a minute.
That means that Saori is available again.
Looks like I have some loss time left!
(it's a footbal, ahem, soccer term for all you Americans out there)
Hey
So what happened?
Saori isn't telling us anything.
You um...
have a couple of minutes?
You told your sister about the BBS right?
What exactly did you tell her?
I just told her the straight and simple truth.
Tell me what the straight truth is!
God damn it, tell me!
You're playing a totally different role...
This is the real me, bitch!
And?
He was posting up all these stories about her...
making fun of her every problem and making a fool out of her.
Did you even actually read the board?
I couldn't even get myself to read it.
Unbelievable.
This is why I hate boys!
What the hell do you mean by that?
Read the board, dammit!
What is that?
So what's this board she's talking about?
Sorry.
Misuzu san!
Aladdin~ Channel~
Saori and~ Yamada~
It has the secret~
To their breakup~
Now what's up!
We're going to Italy for work
But we might as well have a good time there.
It'll be a good break for us.
Yeah.
Sorry!
Too much to drink
last night.
You're late!
Okay, let's go.
That dumbass Yamada!
Calling in sick for 3 days in a row...
Okay you know what I can fire him.
Mrs. Yamada?  Hi, this is Kuroki, his boss...
I was wondering if Yamada was home?
Yes, yes.
Well I was hoping to get him to write his 2 weeks' notice
Yes, yes, yes.
I got disconnected.
Oikawa?  What is it?
I...  I don't dislike him, you know...
Well, Oikawa, even if it's you, I can't let you...
...speak out against my decisions based on your likes or dislikes.
Well, I guess I have no choice.
What?
Hello.
Jinkama-san...
Why are you...
Just let me in.
(literally she is saying, "serve me tea")
Huh?
So you got dumped?
How did you..
Oh it was just a rumor going around.
I see.
Well, I mean, it's not like a guy like you had much of a chance.
Look.
It's like "The Lady and the Otaku."
It's even less conceivable than "Beauty and the Beast."
Dammit, I hate these depressing moods.
Take your clothes off.
Huh?
Well, it's partly my fault too
Looks like I have no choice.
When you lose someone, you gotta find someone new, right?
Wh...  What are you doing?
Just shut up!
Let me do my thing.
Spare me, please!
How long are you gonna drag this on for?
There are plenty of girls like that out there.
No...  There aren't.
Someone so lovely...
There isn't anyone but her.
So you're saying I'm different?
Then I'll show you...  With my body!
Please...  Anything but that!
Nice to meet you.
Same to you.
Sorry to bother you two.
Hey what's that you're doing?
Oh.  It's nothing.
There's the food.
(Notice how she said 'kita, kita' like the BBS...)
Oh wow, that looks really good!
I finally put the pieces together.
I had some stuff going on and was away from the board for a while.
I'm finally caught up.
Looks like Densha got dumped.
Yeah.  I'm so sleepy...
Not as many people come here anymore - it's deserted.
With the lead character gone, nobody is gonna come in.
Why'd you guys let him off the train early?
At this rate, he won't be any different from before!
Densha closed the curtains on his own free will.
He evolved into oru army's deadliest weapon.
And then, he became a star.
It's true that he took a pretty nasty fall.
But, all of us were hoping that Densha
would be able to work things out with Hermes!
We don't need a rookie like you to tell us that.
Some things in this world just can't be helped.  That's just how it is.
We all did the best we could, I think...
I didn't think that it would work for sure.
But I just don't want him to leave any regrets.
He still hasn't told Hermes how he feels about her!
He can give up after he does that, right?
It's too late for that.
He won't appear on this board again.
I guess we were all only connected by a telephone line...
That's why you guys are stuck here.
There's no way we could help Densha if we can't even change ourselves!
Isn't there anyone who says that we have to take him back here
and convince him to tell Hermes how he feels?
It's useless to say such things.
I'm upset too.  But if Densha is like that...
Maybe I'll give it a try...
Hey hey, you're just gonna hurt Densha again.
No!
If you're scared of getting hurt and run away...  That's just like us!
Densha is our final weapon.
This is an illusion.  He's already reached his limit!
Did you forget about the power of that destructive weapon?
Who's going to help Densha if we don't?
Only the guys who want to help him out should remain here.
You guys are all...  So stupid!
I call a toast to all of you who are rushing to die.
We have to inject Densha with all of our powers!
Mr. Strategist, I hope you have a plan.
Of course!  Tomorrow is Sunday.
There's a good chance that a depressed Densha will go to Akiba!
How about an Akiba Infiltration Plan?
Densha was telling us before that he lives near the Chuo line
Let's wait for him there!
I'll announce it at the station!
I'll have a live street performance at Akiba!
I'll scream "Densha" in the middle of Akiba! (*4)
(You ever hear of 'Sekai no Chuusin de Ai wo Sakebu?)
I'll call out to him from 3000 ft. in the air
I'll write and publish a book about Densha!
I'll recruit soldiers at Akiba!
I'll buy up they city of Akiba and look for Densha that way.
I'll set up multiple traps on other message boards
You guys are all such good people.
Working so hard to help out someone else...
If I had guys like you around...
...my life would've been more fun.
What are you talking about?
We're your friends, too.
When you run into a wall you can't overcome yourself...
We'll be there for you.
I'm a total loner, but..
I'll make some flyers for Densha and put them all over Akiba!
That's a good idea.  Just make sure you get the city's permission!
Then I'll put myself on TV and call out to him!
Okay, we'll put him back on this board for sure!
Well, I guess I should start making some leaflets.
(He's calling out train stations like a conductor)
Daddy
So who is this Densha guy?
Heck if I know.
Hey, it's Yamada!
You know that person?
Yeah, he helps me out with my video games.
Oh yeah, I memorized the Nanbu line.
Let's hear it.
Tachikawa, Nishi-Kunitachi, Yaho...
No.
After Nishi-Kunitachi, the next stop is Yagawa
Tachikawa, Nishi-Kunitachi, Yagawa, Yaho...
This is scary.
It's so bright...
Sorry, sorry...
[Densha Otoko!  Come back to the board!]
[A Channel members]
Densha-san, don't give up!
[Densha Otoko, read the board!]
Even if Hermes doesn't like you anymore
Just take another look at the message board
Shall we hold hands?
He...  He...  Here...
That caught me off guard, you sighed before saying hi.
Mr. Matsunaga, I know you don't have luck with women, but...
shaking hands like that with a guy...
...is a little too fishy.
How dare you!
It's not like I don't have a girlfriend, you know.
A girlfriend?
Mr. Yamada!
It's been a while since you decided to meet up with us.
[Densha, tell her!]
Here you go.
He is at the 15th hole...
Hey, are you looking at this?
Densha, come back to the message board!
Stay tuned for the next episode of Mina!
Densha
It's too bad...
but while you're sulking around like that...
my lethal weapon has found Hermes within striking range.
Oh
He's so handsome.
The weak-hearted Saori...
...she couldn't refuse her mother's suggestions...
I was so surprised to hear that you were my date, Kazuya.
I was shocked too.
To hear that you were Hermes...
I'll have to thank Densha.
Thanks to him, our love has grown...
Look there.
It's so hot.
What the hell?  Messing up in my fantasy?
Wait a minute!
Things never went according to my plans, so..
..does that mean that this time, it'll work?
Densha
Sorry.
This time, for real, Hermes will be mine.
What're you doing?
This is...
Sorry.
I heard from Keisuke.
But even then...
Saori, listen to me.
You know, I...
When I first heard of this board, I was really upset...
and thought about confronting Yamada.
You know I didn't like him at all, right?
He was such an Otaku...
But, Saori...
This message board...
take a look.
On here...
Stop it.
I can't stand it.
Saori!
Why a radio show, even when there aren't any guests?
I heard that Karin Takeda, who's been out of the spotlight for a while
will be a special live guest via internet.
For real?
I'll need to record this!
This is...
a sudden notice, so only a handful of fans know about...
Why?
Okay, so we're about to start this show...
with our on-site exclusive secret guest!
Looks like everyone in front of the studio might know who she is.
To everyone listening on the radio...
we're really sorry - and be a little jealous, will you?
On air we have, from Los Angeles,
via internet video feed, Karin-chan!
Karin-chan?
Yes?
How's everyone doing?
We're all doing great!
Right now, Karin-chan is
studying acting, and
that's why she's in LA, but...
why did you decide to do a radio show all the sudden?
Well, that...
I wanted to send a message...
to someone who guided me...
Mr. Yamada, we sure find that hard to believe!
And so, who is this person who guided you?
I knew him from an internet message board.
And...
I've actually never seen what he looks like.
That person...
helped out someone named Hermes...
from a drunk man on a train, and because of that...
he falls in love, but...
Is this...  my...?
Your what?
And what is it that you want to tell him
Densha Otoko-san, you...
gave courage to me...
someone who wasn't able to live on her own.
But
You still have some unfinished business left.
Please read the message board.
Everyone is looking for you.
Looking...?
Please, read the message board soon!
Densha Otoko...  You mean -that- Densha Otoko?
Yeah it's been a hot topic lately.
That Densha Otoko...  Unforgivable!
[Densha, tell her how you feel!]
Densha...
Tell her how you feel!
[Densha Otoko, come back to the message board!]
Everyone...  For me...
I'll bet that Densha guy is nothing!
He probably looks like this!
Yes, I concur.
I'm sure he's this ugly.
No no, more like this!
Mr. Matsunaga, you're good!
[Densha Otoko, come back to the message board!]
[Densha Otoko, please come back!]
[Come back to the message board!  Venoa!  Zaspa!]
[Densha Otoko, come back soon!]
[The newest work from Yasunari Kawahashi:
"Come back to the Message Board, Densha!
Out on September 17th!]
[Read the message board, Densha Otoko!
From the Supporters of Densha]
Hey, are you watching, Densha?
Densha, come back to the message board!  You haven't done all you can...
[Densha Otoko!  The message board...]
[Densha Otoko!  Come back to the message board, man!  We're all waiting for you]
[Densha Otoko, come back!  I can't pass my exams without you!
-Straight to Meiji University]
[Densha Otoko - Banzai!]
(yet another form of slang...)
[Densha Otoko, we're waiting for you to come back.]
[Densha Otoko, get back to the message board!]
[Densha Otoko, come back!]
[Densha Otoko!  Read the message board!]
Bonna sera?  Ma'am, are you alone?
Yuko...
I heard from Kaho.
You know, I don't think Yamada meant any harm...
with what he wrote on the message board.
So it's okay to do anything if you don't mean any harm?
I can't forgive him.
Well...
I don't think you have to forgive him.
But...
You should at least try to understand
how he was feeling when he wrote what he did.
Kaho was saying...
after she read that message board...
she realized she was wrong about Yamada.
She said she was really moved.
And to think that she hated Otakus so much!
Maybe
he wrote something that really struck a chord with her, you know?
[Densha, tell her how you feel!]
[A Channel]
Densha, you reading this?
I'm the guy who flamed this board a while ago.
Back then, I had a leg injury...
and was told that I couldn't play basketball anymore...
and was really pissed.
2 months have passed since then
and I got taken out of my team...
but I've been going through therapy for my leg, and it's getting better.
I really enjoy every day of this.
Someday, I'll make it back on the basketball courts.
If it weren't for you...
I don't think I could've taken that step forward.
This time, it's your turn to take that step.
For a while
I watched over your relationshp with Hermes.
Those three months...
made me realize, once again...
that I wanted to alawys be with my wife of 10 years...
the first woman whom I loved from the bottom of my heart.
I'm really glad
I was able to meet you.
I'm sure a lot of us feel the same way.
As a representative of everyone...
let me say this.
Densha
For our sake too...
Tell Hermes...
How you really feel.
I...
I travel to foreign countries a lot...
and it's tough sometimes, but more than that...
I think it's more difficult...
to make a trip to Hermes's house.
They don't sell tickets to Hermes's house
at JTB.
Nobody is gonna tell you
what you need to do in order to find yourself there.
But you somehow managed to pull that off, right?
If you've come this far only to hem and haw about silly things...
I'm gonna beat the crap out of you!
Densha
Romance is different from sports or academia.
For sports or academia...
You need talent more than you need effort...
But with romance...
it's effort over talent!
You have to think that you're never gonna give up
and really wish hard for Hermes!
Nobody knows how it'll turn out
But just so you won't leave any regrets
You have to try harder than you ever have before!
Well, I'm...
not going to push your back anymore.
Up to this point
everyone around here has done more than enough of that.
At least for this last time
with your own courage...
Give it a shot!
Densha
This romance hasn't ended yet!
I'm a girl, but...
you haven't reached the finish line yet!
(what does that have to do with her being a girl?)
Hermes
needs you, Densha.
I...
I've shared both happy and sad moments
with Densha.
So when you're down in the dumps...
you're not alone!
We've got your back!
Everyone...
Why are you all
Such great guys?
Everyone...
Thank you so much!
Your every word
pokes at my heart.
I'm
really glad I found this thread.
I'm glad I spent time with you guys.
I'll
just one more time...
make my last stand!
Sir...
[2 weeks' notice]
O...  Oikawa-san?
I'm manager Oikawa now.
Huh?
Right, Assistant Manager Kuroki?
Yes, that is correct.
So...
This has no place here any longer.
It's not that.
Well, I...
I have to wait for someone, and I'm not sure
when I'll even be able to see her.
Then use some vacation time.
You only used some for surfing, and you have some left, right?
You sure it's okay?
Yep.
Right, Assistant Manager Kuroki?
Of course
Manager Oikawa.
Canned tuna, check.  Sleeping bag, check.
Change of clothes, check.
Canned tuna, check.
I'm going to call her now.
I'm sure I'll just get her answering machine...
These feelings...  I'm gonna tell her everything!
That's the first time I've seen someone so worked up over a voice message.
I didn't know that guys ready to go down were so magnificent!
It's okay.
I'm sure Hermes is thinking about you too, Densha.
Calm down...
[Tsuyoshi Yamada]
L...  l...  long time no talk!
Pl...  pl...  please read the message board!
E...  Everything about me is crammed into that place.
P...  P...  Please.
Please read it until the end.
At the very end
I've written a message for...
you, Aoyama-san.
It was a bit different than I expected
but I told her I wanted her to read the message board.
Now, I'm gonna write a message addressed to her.
Dear Hermes-san,
After reading this message board
I'm sure you're surprised, in many different ways.
For me, I'm feel embarrassed...
Nostalgic...
And a little funny.
But...
There are no lies or tricks
in the words you see here.
That...
is something that's true for the guys on the internet
I don't know their names or faces
but they...
For me...
are truly my friends.
If there's one thing
that I could be proud of...
it's that I was able to meet them.
I can say that without a doubt.
It was because of those guys
that I...
never gave up on you.
It's because of those guys
that I...
was able to make up my mind and tell you how I feel.
Tomorrow...
I'll be waiting for you at our secret spot.
I'll wait until you show up.
Finally...
About having written here without your permission...
and in doing so, having hurt you...
...please forgive me.
Densha Otoko.
Now...
I'm leaving home.
It's the final match...  Do your best!
Go Densha!  Hit her with everything you've got!
Densha, go now!  I'll make sure you won't leave any regrets!
Even if Hermes doesn't work out...
you won't be one of these bitter, single guys again.
You're shining so brightly, Densha!
We'll wait for you at the last stop.
Who cares about the results?
If you tell her how you feel, that's good enough for me!
Okay, I guess I should wear an air raid helmet just in case.
Venoa~
So this day has finally arrived!  It took long enough...
I'll look back on those days we smiled and cried with Densha...
I guess people can change in 3 months.
I'll give you my energy, if you're okay with how weak it is.
Um excuse me, I'm already crying here...
I'm not gonna cry yet...
but I'll wail after Densha comes back!
Densha
We aren't just...
connected by some telephone wires.
We're connected with our hearts.
Guys
Thanks so much
For these three months.
To get here...
it's felt like an eternity...
and at the same time like a heartbeat
It's a strange feeling - I'm not even sure
if it's a dream or reality.
Honestly...
I'm more nervous than anything.
But...
I'll do...
What I have to do.
Today...
will probably be the day...
that's a turning point in my life.
I'll fly out
from this sheltered life
I've been living up until now.
And...
I've taken in
Everyone's hopes and wishes.
I won't return without completing this.
[The world is here for the two of you!]
Well then...
I'll be on my way.
Going anywhere?
I have to start my new life, right?
Now that I'm divorced, I feel so much lighter and I can see everything clearly now!
You never said that before.
I guess that's thanks to Yamada-san.
Saori.
With love...
you can overcome anything.
Canned tuna, check.
You did well, Densha.
Sorry, but you were a little too late.
Now, the tables are gonna be turned like you've never seen before.
Sorry I'm late.
I'm Yuki Aoyama.
I'm Sakurai.
And Saori-san...?
She won't be here.
Well, but today's date is...
It'll be me.
Ma'am, you're funny.
P...  P...  Please read the message board!
Everything about me is written there...
P...  Please
read it until the very end!
At the end
a message for you, Aoyama-san...
[A Channel]
Special Thanks:
Greyhorse
tianj
d-addicts.com
Happy Birthday to Binkley!
*1) Chuubou, written as 'kitchen' is 'middle school boy' in 2ch lingo.  'Chuugakusei no bouya' or 'Chuugakusei no bouzu'
*2) "Maman" is a phrase used by Jonathan from Yoshiyuki Tomino's "Brain Powered."  It's one of his more recent works, but probably not one of his better ones.
*3) "Otsu" is short for "Otsukaresama deshita"
*4) "Sekai no Chuushin de Ai wo Sakebu" is a famous J-drama starring some guy and Ayase Haruka.  A must see!
If you want to watch a movie with Miho Shiraishi (Jinkama) casted, check out Calamari Wrestler! (Ika Resuraa)
September 19, 2005
Masakun