Happy..
Birth...
day...
Yamada-san!
Are you ok?
Yamada-san?
Wha- Wha-
What the heck's going on with this thing?!
I broke something again.
Crap.
Yamada-san, hold on.
Yamada-san.
Kazuya-san.
Let's get him to the hospital.
[Yamada Tsuyoshi-sama, Admitted: '05, 8/21]
Densha, where are you?
He'd usually be back by now...
Maybe Hermes didn't show up and he's wading into the Ocean?
Maybe he was successfull and they stayed the night?
I want to hurry up and know what happened!
It's too bad.
I guess I gotta tell them what happened.
[Densha Otoko]
I, I'm Densha.
I j, just got back.
I tried telling her again, but it I failed.
I've been dumped for good.
Don't worry about me any more.  Byenara.
That's the end of this thread.
I wonder if Densha is in yet?
I'm going to wait until he get's back.
This is a job for night owls like me.
The last train left, but I'm waiting for Densha.
Why won't people respond?
I took the time to tell them what happened.
Wh, why are you ignoring me?
I, I've already gotten back.
Hermes-chan had a fiance with looks like a model.
He's really smart and cool.
So now that I've been dumped, there's nothing more to say.
Byenara.
He's worse than that flamer.
Can't he figure out we're ignoring him?
Shut up you fake!
How can they tell I'm a fake?
"I'm Densha?" it's so obvious.
Hermes-chan?  That's lame.
Fiance? In your dreams.
This guy has no literary talent.
Byenara?  What age were you born in?
Forget him guys.  His dumbness will only spread.
Those bastards!
Whoa.  Close call there.
Nevermind.  I'll take it out on Densha then.
Densha's too late.  Is he still waiting for her?
I'm so worried about Densha I can't keep my eyes off this thread.
I'm bored, someone talk to me.
Anyone have any grown-up games?
He's sleeping soundly.
What are you doing here?
I thought you might be worrying about
things you don't need to worry about.
How about work?
I took the day off.
Really.
It was my fault.
Saori, could you put this in a vase?
Sure, sorry for not noticing.
You awake now?
My name's Sakurai.
Maybe it'd be faster if I told you I was Saori's fiance.
You've been dumped.
If you keep hanging around her, you'll just be bothering her.
Give it up.
It's ok.
He doesn't even want to see your face.
He says he wants to think about things by himself.
Let's go.
The Train Man
Original Story
"Densha Otoko"  by Nakano Hitori
Script:
Takefuji Shougo
Openning Theme
"Twilight" by Electric Light Orchestra
Itou Misaki
Itou Atsushi
Shiraishi Miho
Sudou Risa
Satou Eriko
Hayami Mokomichi
Kishibe Shirou
Toyohara Kousuke
Akiyoshi Kumiko
Openning Anime Production       Character Design
GONZO                               OKAMA
Director
Takeuchi Hideki
Story 8
This is something my brother picked out
for you after a lot of searching.
Before that, he kept bugging me
for advice on what he should get.
They're all broken.
How pathetic.
You know, ever since I can remember,
I've hated my brother.
But lately,
I find myself liking him sometimes.
It's probably because he met you.
My brother changed for you.
Nowadays people might say it's not their scene.
I thought it was amazing though.
I wouldn't ever say it if he was around of course.
So,
if you're just playing around with him,
stop hurting him anymore.
Please.
Enter your gender and a 2 character keyword, and it'll respond!!
OK, ok, got it.
Gender: Male
Keyword: Armpit Hair
Pretty cool.
Awesome.
Gender: Male
Keyword: Georgeous.
Disappointing, but you'll never meet anyone like that.
It could be.
Hey!
Gender: Male
Keyword: Battle (Japanese homonym =  Public Bath)
Ahh- That was a wonderful bath.
It's not that sentou!
Commensing fire!
This guy's pretty tough.
Keyword: Hair Transplant
Huh?
Keyword: Boredom
Yeah, your life looks pretty boring all right.
Murder.
Want me to crack your head in two!!
I'm sorry.
Jinnkama-san,
I can't do that.
I'll give you a shot now.
Ok.
It was just a dream.
Why do you react so violently all the time?
What are you doing here today?
I came here to ask you for a favour.
Favor?
Yeah, it's about Oikawa who works for your company.
What about Oikawa-san?
I figured since he was the son of a CEO,
I'd be cool to sleep with him.
But he's pushy.
I'm not talking about his personality, but the other thing.
The other thing?
So I was wondering,
Could you tell him for me?
That I don't really like him or anything.
I couldn't say anything like that.
What are you doing?
Don't worry, I'm just hiding.
Where do you think you're touching?
Yamada,
did you just see Jinnkama-san?
No, didn't!
I know what I saw.
You're hiding somewhere!
You have a pretty good thing going there.
Huh?
Uh...well-
Hey, Oikawa-kun's here.
This is how it is.
Oikawa wants to take over as Jinnkama Misuzu's supervisor.
Isn't that right, Oikawa?
Can I take over Jinnkama-san's case?
Sure, if you want.
No, that's no good.
Which is it?
Jinnkama-san...just not that.
What?
Yamada,
listen to Oikawa-kun's reque-
Scary!
If it's that important...
I don't really want it.
Oikawa-kun, Oikawa-kun wait for me!
That was close.
What're getting hard for!?
I'm sorry.
Saori, you met Yamada to break up with him right?
I thought if I didn't make it clear,
it would just hurt him more later.
That was good.
I'm proud of you.
Really?
It was the right thing to do.
She made it clear that she hates people who lie
and made a clean break with Yamada.
But that means you haven't changed at all.
See, your gut reaction to lies will probably stay forever.
It's kind of mean, but it's like a disease.
So instead of just letting it ruin your relationships,
shouldn't you be trying to get over it?
Get over it?
Gender: Male
Keyword: Details
Kibonne, Kiborine.  Shouldn't you get over it?
What's with that chicken?
When I entered muscles, it said "fake"!
How am I supposed to enter "erotic" with just 2 characters?
When you enter it as a female, it gives you softer replies.
When I entered chick, it made cute crying sounds.
It's just a chicken,
but sometimes it shows this wonderful glimpse of kindness.
It's annoying, but it's actually pretty accurate.
A chicken?
This...
Keyword: Munetaka
That's the name of the guy who created the Aladdin Channel BBS.
Keyword: Ryoko
The administrator's waiting for your reply.
Reply to the Single Men's thread.
To the board's administrator:
Maybe you'd recognise me if I said chicken-girl.
I was surprised.  I didn't think you'd still be on this board.
You might call it a miracle.
It was a thread you liked,
so I thought you might be following it but...
I'm sorry for using your Chicken without your permission.
Isn't there something else you should be sorry for?
Like suddenly disappearing from sight,
and even changing your cell.
You should have said something.
I could tell you that my business partner took off with our money
and then how I stopped trusting people.
But that would just be an excuse.
There's some shipping going on on the board.
Do this in the couple's thread!
There's nothing going on right now.
Let's see where this goes.
I heard about what happened from Keiko.
Did you find your friend?
No, I haven't looked for him.
I wouldn't know what to tell him anyway.
He was someone you trusted wasn't he?
I wonder how much he took?
Idiot, it's not about the money.
I wonder how long ago this was?
Have you started a new company?
If I had that kind of courage,
I wouldn't be approaching you like this.
The guy can't move forward yet.
How sad.
Are you still angry?
He seems to want to get back together.
The chicken tactic was pretty crazy.
He probably isn't serious.
I was furious for around a month.
I couldn't figure out why you'd suddenly disappear.
I understood when I heard the reason though.
I want to meet you again.
Good on you.
Come on guy, answer her!
Don't take this seriously.
The guy probably wanted to do something,
but the chance never came up.
I'm sorry.  I'm still not ready.
Why guy?
You're almost there.
I know how you feel.
Don't you feel sorry for your girlfriend who wants to meet you?
By 'yet', do you mean you still want to?
Here's an idea.
If Densha-san's relationship,
-the first relationship on this thread-  succeeds...
Will you meet me?
So if it doesn't work, we don't meet?
I guess so...
All right.
What is this delicate atmosphere I'm feeling?
Ok.  I guess we have to cheer on Densha even more now.
Even if it's a lie, I want to believe it's true.
The girl's awesome.
All right, let's all wait for Densha to return!
I see,
so she likes men who can surf...
What's this?
Keyword: Marriage
It'll never happen.
You'll be single forever.
Your right hand will be your only friend.
Shut up you f*@k'in chicken!
See here?
I'm left-handed.
Doh, I spilled my beer.
Huh?
Matsunaga-shi, what are you doing here?
The original Eva Unit-00 looks smarter
than the later releases doesn't it?
If you become an Otaku again,
I could consider giving it to you.
I don't really want it.
This guy's heart-rate seems to tell all.
Kawamoto-shi, when did you-
Never sold in stores, this is an alarm clock that uses Mina's voice.
I don't need it.
And this!
Soma Megumi, Memories Off; the Second Concert version.
And this is Asuka Langley's summer bikini version.
Wicke-
He's close to giving up!
And this is really rare.
Mina's pilot episode DVD!
I...don't...ne-
Yamada-shi!
Yamada-shi, what happened?
Isn't this what they call a cardiac arrest?
What'll we do?
Calm down.
I think we're supposed to-
Heart massage?
I think his arm is getting rigid.
Next I think we're supposed to-
Mouth to mouth?
What are you doing?
I'm so relieved.
He's alive!
No need to thank us.
Argh, it was all soft.
[Yamada Atsushi]
I don't want to see your face.
Let me think about this by my self for a while.
If you're just playing around with him,
stop hurting him anymore.
Gouf.
Zaku.
Dom.
You've been dumped.
If you keep hanging around her, you'll just be bothering her.
Give it up.
It's been a while.
I have news.
Densha, we've been waiting forever.
To all personnel! This is not a drill!
I repeat, this is not a drill!
Give us the details!  I'm not giving it up yet!
I was able to meet Hermes-san,
but I fell sick and hardly got to talk to her.
Then while I was in the hospital,
I met someone who says he's Hermes-san's fiance.
I was told that I was just bothering her, so I should leave her alone.
You're writing that lightly, but that's serious news.
An emergency occured
while we were playing with the chicken!
You fell sick and were hospitalized?
Hermes' finace?
I thought she didn't have a boyfriend.
No, we weren't sure.
Densha, you're not panicking with the recent turn of events?
I was preparing for a bomb, but this is too much.
What kind of guy was this fiance?
Did you talk to Hermes while you were at the hospital?
She came once, but I never got to talk to her.
And the fiance was really good looking.
I was released, but the pain in my heart keeps getting worse.
What's broken here?
Densha, I'm not going to give up.
I'm going to return for you.
Hermes is going to come to understand Densha,
and they'll share a kiss in his arms...
What the- hot, hot!
Densha, as an Otaku your chances of
going out with Hermes were less than 1%.
You knew that and still made it this far.
So what if the fiance is good looking.
Don't get bogged down in something so normal!
But he's her fiance.
I don't want to bother Hermes-san either.
That's just an excuse to run away.
I can't think Hermes wasn't serious about you.
It's a cunning trap laid by the enemy.
Maybe it was that fake Densha?
Then it should be easy.  He seemed really dumb.
I could just be something their parents are interested in.
Who cares about some fiance.
Trust what's in your heart.
I sincerely hoping your relationship
with Hermes works out successfully.
But more importantly,
I want your relationship to be something you're proud of.
Your courage makes the impossible, possible.
I want to believe in your courage.
I don't want you regretting anything.
Talk to Hermes properly.
This isn't the end of the line for you.
Yeah, let's imagine a future where you two are together!
Don't ever give up on your relationship with Hermes.
Work at it like it's the most important thing in your life.
Don't lose to yourself!
Why are you guys so good to me?
Caring so much for a guy like me...
I'm so scared.
I already running away.
But it's also pathetic.
To run away and end it here would be pathetic.
Everyone,
Aren't you upset that Densha's suffering like this!
Of course I'm upset!
Everyone!
Densha!!
I upset too.
Damn it.
[Aoyama-san]
We're going to block Yamada's calls.
So long, Densha.
I'll make her forget you even existed.
What happened?
There was a small bone on it.
Hey, why don't we go to the ocean tomorrow.
The ocean?
I thought it would be good for a change of pace.
I haven't surfed in a while either.
Hello?
You've reached the Aoyama residence.
Pleased to make your aquaintance.
I, I, I'm Yamada.
Is S, S, S Saori-san home?
I'm sorry,
but I couldn't quite hear what you said.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Um, this is Yamada calling.
Saori-san is a friend-
or at least on good terms,
well, maybe not, but-
I think she might at least remember me.
Oh, you want to reach Saori?
She hasn't come home yet.
I see.
Would you like to leave her a message?
What should I do..
Um... Could you ask her,
the reason why she hates me now?
I don't think that's the type of thing you leave as a message.
Oh, that's true.  I'm sorry.
So Saori doesn't like you anymore.
Yes.
I'm sure she has her reasons...
What are you going to do knowing why?
It could be something you can't do anything about.
I still want to do something.
I want to do everything I can.
I'll change what I can,
Even things I can't I'll do my best to change anyway.
So please, could you-
You can plead with me, but I can't do anything.
Huh?
Oh, of course.
I'm sorry.
You didn't by any chance lie to Saori did you?
Lie to her?
It could be something so small you didn't even notice.
I did.
I told her I had work,
but went out with some guys.
That has to be it.
My daughter is really sensitive to lies.
Really?
The reason for it isn't something you need to know about,
but she was traumatized by what happened.
Now she can't trust men.
Is that what it was.
So that means,
it was because you lied about work?
So it wasn't because you were an Otaku.
You had to lose your Otaku anyway.
Actually, I was looking around my room earlier
and felt something was missing.
I tried, but I can't stop being an Otaku.
But if I hide that I'm an Otaku,
I'll be lying to her.
You're taking it too seriously.
Everyone has things they have to hide.
Quit talking like a wussy, and lose your Otaku again!
There's no need to hide it!
An Otaku is what makes you who you are.
The question isn't whether you're an Otaku.
What's important is trying to be sincere to Hermes.
Trying to lose your otaku shows your sincerity.
No it isn't. It's telling her that he's an Otaku.
Is there any hope doing that?
I couldn't do it, but you shouldn't be ashamed of your Otaku.
Hermes doesn't care whether you're an Otaku or not.
So you shouldn't press the issue.
"I, I'm an Otaku."
That'll get you rejected for sure.
Even Hermes will hate you if you're an Otaku.
It doesn't matter.  Show her the true spirit of an Otaku.
Everyone, thanks for all your replies.
I know it's a crazy gamble,
but I can't lie to her anymore.
I'm going to come out to Hermes about my Otaku.
Densha, bravo!
I can't be responsible for what happens.
Kudos for a Densha-like decision.
You fool.
That's the Densha I love!
Get ready for war and prepare bamboo spears!
Bamboo?
What are you going to do with that?
Us men are getting ready to rock!
Head off into the sunset you suicide bomber!
Don't worry, we'll be here to pick up the pieces.
Please, Hermes.  Don't betray Densha.
No matter what happens, come back proud.
All right.
Yamada-shi,
I was waiting for you to say that.
Thank you.
So I was wondering...
Um.
Those figures I gave you..
could I have them back?
Certificate of Non-Otakuness returned.
I was waiting for this.
Thank you so much.
Matsunaga-shi,
return it.
Huh?  It's light.
What's this?
I wonder what it could be.
Was it like this?
Yeah, that's the way it was.
So there was something there!
Not Soma Megumi...
Soma Megumi!
[Yamada Tsuyoshi]
So instead of just letting it ruin your relationships,
shouldn't you be trying to get over it?
Saori can I have a minute?
Sorry, but I have to go to the ocean.
I have to talk to you about your Father.
Have a seat.
Your Father's coming back to Japan.
We'll probably officially divorse then.
Really?
Hey,
The reason why you can't trust men.
Was it us?
No, that had nothing to do with it.
Ok, that's all.
I'll be going then.
There's not a man in the world who doesn't lie.
But lying doesn't necessarily mean betrayal.
I think it's ok forgive a lie told to you
by someone who really cares about you.
I couldn't forgive your Father's lie.
And so...
Take care now.
Welcome back.
3 more minutes to go.
The next request is from Sakurai Kazuya,
to Saori with love.
Fantasy.
Sometimes you can't see what's right in front of you.
I'm sorry I didn't see how beautiful you were.
What?
Like that lighthouse there,
I want to watch over you forever.
Let's get married.
Yes.
It's perfect.
Quit wimping out.
Sis, it's heavy.
Hold it properly!
Hello?
Sorry to bother you during a date.
Keisuke?
I got a call from Yamada just now.
He's been trying to reach you on your cell,
but couldn't get through.
He says there's something he just has to tell you.
Got it.
Thanks.
Later.
I...
was lying to you.
That's why,
it's not a lie.
I think it's ok forgive a lie told to you
by someone who really cares about you.
Hm? What happened?
I'm sorry.  There's somewhere I have to go.
To Densh- Yamada's place?
Wait a minute!
Sometimes you can't see what's right in front of you.
I'm sorry I didn't see how beautiful you were.
Like that lighthouse there,
I want to watch over you forever.
Hey, hey, what're doing with my Evo?
This is serious!
Oh, the ring.
Argh!  No way!
My Evo!
Saori!
Ring!
Come back!
That was the 25th busy call.
Is this really the end?
It's hot?
Yeah, it's hot.
Who is-
It's a dream.
It's gotta be a dream.
It's not a dream.
W, what should I do?
First some proper clothes-
That's right.
Ok.
I'm sorry for visiting you so suddenly.
It's ok.
I couldn't reach you on the phone,
so I thought I would never see you again.
I got a call from Keisuke.
I see.
You said you had something to tell me?
Yes.
This one's salty.
No it isn't.
Here, try this.
Pleased to meet you.
This way.
Your mother's become younger.
What do you mean?
That doesn't happen.
I'm sorry, but I'm almost ready.
Ok.
Please,
come in.
It was during highschool that I started watching anime.
Then...
I started collecting games and figures.
During college, I started going to Akihabara.
And I started going to events featuring voice actresses.
And to get hold of limited edition posters,
I'd stay up for 3 days straight.
Instead of talking to people,
I liked playing games and watching anime by myself more.
And so I started being called an Otaku from people around me.
But...
Because I still loved games and anime,
I couldn't stop.
That's the kind of guy I am.
I'm...
an Otaku.
If I'm called lame,
or gross,
They have every reason for it.
But,
I can't live any other way.
I don't want to lie to you anymore.
So...
even though I'm really embarrassed,
I wanted you to see me as I am.
If you don't mind that it's me,
can we be friends again?
Yamada-san.
That's not fair.
You said what I wanted to say before I could.
Really?
I think it's a wonderful room.
It's very unique.
I like it.
Would you make up with me?
Yes.
YES!!
[Thank you for your courage]
That's awesome!!  Awesome!!  Densha!!
I'm proud of you, you're the best.
I'm crying and I can't stop.
[Aoyama-san]
Yes?
Thank you for the birthday present.
Not at all.
You really don't mind getting something like that?
It's really cute.
I've already set it up in my room.
Really?
I'm glad you liked it.
You can only buy it in Akihabara.
[Aoyama Kengo]
We'll be giving out a 100 CDs containing
the Densha Otoko original soundtrack.
For your chance to win, please send us a post card
to the following address.
Next Week
This peice of fiction was based on a true story.