P...  Please read the message board!
I...  I've put all of myself into it.
Pl...  Please!
Please read it until the very end.
At the end, I have a message for you...
After going to an event in Akiba today...
there was a drunk on the train who was harassing everyone.
I had to do something about it...
so I summed up some courage...
and yelled at him...  a little.
Stop it.
S...  I...  I said stop it...
My voice was probably shaking.
I never fought with anyone before...
Are you okay?
Man, I looked really lame.
Oh...oh...oh...oh shoot!
Th..th...the young lady sent me
a thank you package...
along with a letter!
Can you tell from the writing
if it looks like you even...
have a chance with her?
Your courage
moved me very much.
Well, that's what it says...
Isn't this too good to be true?
And he's going crazy.
Everyone, don't take this guy seriously.
The...the...the shipping receipt has her cell number!
Call   her   up!
I can't I can't I can't I can't
Just pick up your cell.
I have the phone in my hand...
but I can't dial the number!
This is taking more than the time on the train!
My hands are getting all sticky
My face is getting warm
My heart is doing jumping jacks...
Damn, now -I'm- getting worked up.
Don't be fooled.
This has to be some kind of dumb joke!
Let me say just one thing.
The lady on the other end is alone
but you have everyone supporting you.
Everyone...
thanks a lot!
I'm getting choked up...
How kind you all are...
and how pathetic I am...
I want to change.
Oh, and do you know what brand the cups are?
It says "H E R M E S" on the cups...
Hermes!?
Hermes!?  Wow...
It's pronounced "ERUMESU"
(this is closer to the real deal than the American way...)
E RU ME SU!
Hermes as in the purse?
I think...  she wouldn't have sent Hermes cups...
If she was just grateful...
Why don't you ask us while you talk to her?
We'll stand by to listen.
You've got nothing to lose, right?
[Give it your best, Densha Otoko!]
I'm...  gonna call her now.
Kita~
I just realized something really important.
Our conversation snowballed and I ended up
making plans with Hermes...
but she'll just look down on an otaku like me.
What should I do?
Don't worry.
The problem here is your looks.
If you get rid of those clothes...
(kibakaji = Akiba Casual = Otaku gear)
she won't find out you're an otaku.
Changing how you look on the outside...
will change you on the inside.
From clothes to conversation,
it's possible that we'll tutor him on everything.
Looks like we all have to get together to
primp and preen Densha.
Densha Otoko Modification Project
First...  The hairstyle!
Blonde hair is a fashion faux pas
but you should get some highlights.
I think you can let the employees decide.
Want to have some impact?
Go for some corn twists or locks!
Short hair will give her the best impression.
Aren't you gonna panic when the employees ask?
You can overcome this...
For Hermes.
U...um...
How...
do I look?
Actually, I wasn't thinking so far ahead...
where I envisioned us going out or anything.
But...
I'm definitely being drawn closer to her.
If I see her...  I'm definitely gonna fall for her.
Of course, she might be with someone...
and if I still end up liking her,
I might end up getting hurt.
You know, it kinda hurts.
But..
a bitter bachelor like me
being able to think like this
is quite a feat
and I owe everyone for that.
Everyone...
thank you so much.
Thanks for your kind feelings.
I...
I'll push myself.
I was practically a nervous wreck...
over walking side by side with a woman.
If I walk normally
I end up leaving her behind.
To top it off..
She looks better...
than when I saw her last time.
A guy like me...
with a girl like her...
walking together...
I really worried that we didn't look right at all.
I mean, look at us.
She's way taller than me.
I felt like everyone was staring at me.
It's okay.
I'll hold on to you.
I was so surprised...
I jolted and cringed a little.
Why the heck did you let go?
Hold her hand!
I'll hold on to you.
I mean, I wanted her to hold on...
Actually, I told her I'd rather her hold my hand.
Hi.
Mr. Yamada!
The first lot limited edition Mina DVD box...
Did you forget it was coming out tomorrow?
The first lot, as a special feature...
has the storyboards for the legendary episode 7!
At this rate, it'll be sold out in the blink of an eye.
I'm sorry.
I have a more pressing matter to deal with.
I'm really sorry.
Well...
I mentioned this before...
but because of a small communication lapse...
she thinks I like to go surfing.
No worries.
I'll bestow upon you the art of quickly learning how to surf.
If you just have to stand on a board,
it'll work out, I think.
Okay, let's Google some info and give Densha some tips.
Everyone, thanks.  I'll give it a shot.
It's okay if you can't surf.
Just keep in mind that you lied to her.
What's important
is that you think hard for Hermes's sake
and come up with a solution.
I'm sorry.
I...
don't know how to surf.
I lied...
to you.
Lied?
I'm really sorry
about deceiving you.
You know...
I can't deny my otaku-ness.
If I hide my otaku-ness
I'd be lying to her.
You're worrying too much.
Everyone has secrets.
There's no need to hide it.
Your otaku-ness defines who you are.
You'll be loyal to her by telling her that you're an otaku.
Everyone, thanks for your serious replies.
I know it's a hopeless gamble.
But...  I can't lie to her.
I
I'll show Hermes
my otaku side too!
I'm...
an otaku.
I know it can't be helped
if people think I'm lame
or gross.
But...
this is...
the only way I know how to live.
I didn't want to lie to you.
So...
I wanted you to see
who I really am.
[Jinkama-san]
Hello?
Where the hell are you?
I'm staying late at work and you don't even show up to say hi?
Get over here - it's not too late.
i'm sorry.
I've got something really important going on today...
Huh?
You gonna talk back to me?
You know...
I'm priority #1 for you!
Today is no good.
I have...
the most important promise of my life to keep.
Huh?
I'm really sorry.
That's the first time he said 'no...'
On this message board...
I've written down everything that's happened between us.
From her point of view...
that might be a terrible thing.
But...
If I hadn't posted on this message board...
I would never have been able to see her alone.
I never would have...
learned to like myself so much.
And, most important of all...
I wouldn't have met so many wonderful friends.
Because you guys were always there for me...
I was able to push myself to this point.
This message board
is something I'm really proud of.
And that's why..
I'm gonna get up
and tell Hermes
about this message board.
My feelings...
Everyone's important thoughts...
I want her to understand it all.
Dear Hermes:
I'm sure, after reading this message board
you were surprised in many different ways.
I myself feel embarassed...
nostalgic...
and a little funny.
But
There are no lies or deceptions
in the words you read here.
And that
I can say about everyone on the 'net
I don't know their names or faces...
but the guys and girls...
I really...
think of them as true friends.
If I could choose
one thing that I could really be proud of
it would be that I was able to bump into them.
I'm so proud of that, too.
It was because of those guys
I...
didn't give up on you.
It was because of them
I...
made up my mind to tell you how I feel.
Tomorrow
I'll be waiting at our secret place.
I'll be waiting until you show up.
Finally
I wanted to apologize
for writing about you without your permission
and hurting you as a result.
Densha Otoko.
[Final Episode]
Densha
you really have grown up.
I'm awed, even as your enemy.
But...
I'll let you know that even then
there's a wall too high to be climbed.
This...
is the FINAL ROUND.
Hello?
Bad news - Saori collapsed.
What?
She's at the nearby hospital.
She was calling out your name while coming
in and out of consciousness.
Please go to her.
I'll be right there!
Who was that?
Oohhh okay okay, there we go...  Ouch ouch!
Sakurai...  Heading out!
(Go go Gundam 0079!)
Saori
Kazuya-san...
You in a hurry?
I'll give you a lift.
Thanks.
Hey hey!  For tonight's special guest,
live from a concert stage
Sambo Master will be playing a brand new song!
It's actually a song
for a guy named Densha Otoko
on the now famous A Channel.
All right, Sambo Master
Let's hear your cry for love and send out some courage
for the Densha Otoko somewhere out there!
I don't know your name...
I don't know your past...
I don't what kind of guy you are!
For a guy like you...  You know it!
That's what the world calls love!
Hey listen to Nippon Broadcasting!
They're playing a song that someone wrote for Densha!
Such a good song...
I can't stand how weak my tear ducts are these days
I hope Densha and Hermes are listening
Not just Densha, but we're getting patted on the back, too!
Our duty is to wait for Densha until he comes home
and reports to us.
Is there a chance that Hermes still hasn't read these posts...?
There's a huge chance it hasn't happened!
Normal people wouldn't look!
If she reads this...  I hope she'll...
Hermes...  Please come to the secret place!
Can you stop the car?
Thanks.
Okay...
the climax is just around the corner.
These are Yamada's...
Hi, this is Yamada
I'm at the hospital where Saori was taken to
but I was told that she wasn't here...
Huh?
Wait wait wait
This has to be some kind of mistake.
Sis just left the house not too long ago.
Really?
Yeah.  She had a really serious expression on her face
and left pretty quickly.
'pretty quickly?'
Got it.
Hey, you know...
Yes?
I read the message board.
Oh...
I really understood
that you're pretty serious
about my sister.
I'm sorry about punching you.
I'm sure she'll understand.
Thank you.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
So this is the secret place...
Maybe Yamada
thought that he wasn't good enough for you...
and ran away...
Wha...  Saori
Okay
For now
things are going as planned.
[Densha Otoko, come back to the message board!]
[Densha Otoko, please come back to the message board!]
Hello?
Saori
I found Yamada.
He's at the train station platform.  You have to come now.
Okay.
Where's Yamada-san?
Yamada...
said he wasn't good enough for you
and left.
Saori
Let's get married!
As he was leaving, he told me this.
I'm leaving things up to you.
Please make Saori happy.
Kazuya-san...
Saori
What the...
Saori!
Yamada...
told me that he wasn't good enough for you
and left.
Saori
Let's get married.
Aoyama-san...
Kazuya-san
Thank you.
Nah...
Yamada
Now it's up to you.
Make Saori happy.
Shoot, I might as well take her by force...
This is real!
Seriously!  We're so lucky!
It's so hard!
Wait a minute.
Hey, you girls are...
Shit!
That diamond ring!
Sorry sorry!
Watch it asshole!
It's an emergency!
(잘 모르겠네요..ㅠㅠ 거기서 정도인가? -.-;;)
Dammit, that's my Lancer!
("Lanevo" = Lancer Evolution)
Dammit!
Shit!
I'll have to use my No. 2
What're you doing!?
Where are you taking it?
Ring!
Lancers!
Hermes!
Come back!
Um...
We finally meet
Densha Otoko.
Densha
He's still not back...
I haven't gotten an ounce of sleep
because I've been watching this message board since last night.
is everyone awake?
I'm fading in and out of consciousness...
But this is for Densha!  I'll wait...
Sleepy...  So sleepy...
I can't...  I have to sleep.
Peace out.
The legendary heroes fall one by one.
Feeling the weight of their anguish,
a lonely bachelor...  falls asleep.
I want to welcome him home for the last time
So that's why I'm up, but...
I can't hold out any longer.
I just got back home.
Densha?
Is that really you?
He's back!
I wonder how long it'll take me to write everything down
So sleepy...
I know you're sleepy, but please tell us what happened!
Yeah - we were chatting for half a day while waiting for your return!
My having waited 15 hours...  Makes me a winner!
Sorry for the wait.
Should I tell you the result first?
Nono, the main point should be at the end!
Please...  Please toy with us slowly and painfully!
Please report the results at the last stop.
Everyone...  Let's go together!
My pulse is going out of control!
I'm so nervous I'm making my computer desk shake!
Now, the largest and most powerful bombing in this thread
one that will surely go down in the annals of history
shall begin...
Then I'll start.
I stayed at the spot since noon like I said
and visualized how I would tell her how I felt.
Then, someone called and said that Hermes collapsed.
That was actually not true
I left the hospital quickly
and went back to my hideout.
And then...
By sheer coincidence
I bumped into Hermes
at the train station.
This is so dramatic.
It really seems like you two were destined to meet.
Good job on the description!
Good job to whoever gave Densha that falese info!
Don't mention it.
She and I
decided to go back to our secret place.
During that time
Hermes stayed silent.
Of course, me too.
And then
the silence was broken.
I read the message board.
Yeah.
After reading that message board
I understood how you felt
in really depending
on the people there for a helping hand.
And...
I also understood
how you felt about me
thanks to the posts.
It made me happy.
Yamada-san,
the fact that you thought about me so much
really made me happy.
The people on the message board
are really kindhearted.
Yes.
So...
I came up here because
I wanted to hear from you
how you felt about me.
Could you please tell me?
Yes.
Here it comes...  Here it comes!
Hermes moe~
"Could you please tell me" means that, now...!
It's confession time!
The train is suddenly climbing up!
An attack that no trench, air raid hat, or fallout shelter can shield
is about to hit us!!
For the first time in my life,
the feeling you get when you're about to finish an RPG
has come back to me in real life!
Everyone, after the next hit, I probably won't be around anymore.
So let these be my parting words.
I love you guys!
O~!  I'm gonna run through the city naked!
I'm so excited, words are asdfa;dslkj;aldkjf
Let's see what you got!
For a while, time passed by without a word being uttered.
I was so nervous..
that I couldn't speak.
I..  have something very important to say.
Yes.
When I'm with you, Aoyama-san...
everything really shined.
All the meaningless time
I...
I was spending until now...
The unchanging cityscape...
and my really pitiful self
from back then...
Everything
suddenly started to shine
like a spell was cast.
Aoyama-san...
it's because you let
light shine on me.
I've received so much from you, Aoyama-san...
But...
I...
don't have anything to give.
There's nothing I can do for you.
But...
these feelings I have...
these feelings i have for you, Aoyama-san...
nobody...
feels this way more than I do.
I...
You can do it.
Aoyama-san...
I really like you.
I...
feel the same way...
about you too, Yamada-san.
So...
From now on...
will you be with me...?
Yes
Thank you
Always...
Please be with me...  always.
Yes.
I'm sorry
I...
I really...
Aoyama-san, I really...
I'm sorry.
No girl
has ever treated me nicely...
Not once...
Now you've...
started to make me cry.
You kissed her!!
After telling you how I felt...
I like you even more now...
No more!
i have no regrets in my life!
Now I'm starting to cry!
I'm ALREADY crying!
My tears, for once, are shining like pearls.
With all these tears, I think my body is losing all its water!
If my dad came in right now,
how would I explain these tears to him?
Spring has arrived~
Where has it arrived~?
It arrived for Densha~
It arrived for Hermes~
To the bachelors...  Venoa!
Densha
Congratulations
To everyone on this thread
We all did well.
You're the greatest!
So did you do it?
Did you do it!?
This year's MVP goes to you, Densha.
Your hobbies and interests don't matter anymore.
The truth is
that two people fallen for each other are right there!
It doesn't matter if you're an otaku...
or an ex-bachelor.
Make her happy as best as you can
and you be happy, too!
I'm crying in real life now!
Tears are falling from my eyes, too.
Densha's anxiety
his life up to now
and his life going forward
I think everything is there
for the sake of her happiness.
Thinking about what happened is making me cry again.
Don't worry - I've cried twice as much as you have.
This is the first time someone else's story has made me cry.
There's something coming out of my ear
But nobody's here to wipe it off.
Are there really girls as pure as she is in Tokyo?
(I doubt it...)
Is this the 'Japanese Dream?'
Cute?  Pure?
Older girl who'll take care of you?
Are they really out there?
Will there be some left for me?
Is Hermes the last one?
The final weapon has finally arrived!
(for like the 3rd time in this series)
I stop by to look, and there's nobody there!
Am I...  still...  alive...
You're really the man.
Congratulations!
Let us know where the wedding is!
Sergeant Densha, are there any unfinished items left?
Yes, there are...
but Mina is about to come on
so I'll finish this up later.
We have to wait for an anime now?
It's cruel to have an intermission here!
You got us there.
You really are an anime otaku!
Hey, so what's Mina?
"Moon Surface Bunny Weapon Mina"
You can Google the rest.
I really love you, man!
To think that he found Hermes thanks to me...
That piece of shit Densha...
Who cares about an anime break?
He should put himself in my shoes!
Teasing us all along...
I'm gonna beat him to a pulp when I see him again.
But I really do want to see what it's like...
A romance with such a fateful beginning...
Hey, you!
The hell are you fiddling with your cell for?
(if you saw the episode of "Trivia no Izumi" where...)
You should try to fidget with me down here!
(they studied otakus in Akihabara...)
You're 10 years too young to be with me!
(then this guy is really familiar...)
Stop!
Can't you see she's bothered by what you're doing?
He's scary!
What the...?  I was being beat up by this girl, and...
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Have we met before?
I was thinking the same thing!
Is this...
Fate?
I didn't get anything...
She and I
left our special spot
and wandered around for a while.
Eventually, we came to a park.
And then, we sat on an empty bench, but...
was there a time when we sat so close to each other?
Probably not.
All of the sudden...  Kita~
And it's begun again!
It's an attack like firing from a ship
to an enemy camp under truce!
I love Densha and how he starts again
like nothing happened!
This
is a present I got you from when I went to Italy for work.
Please open it.
This...
looks really expensive...
Not really.
I really appreciate this.
It's so nice...
Thank you.
Really...
Thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
Could you please put it on?
Huh?
Thank you.
It looks good on you.
We're matching now.
Huh?
No "yeah they're matching now!"s
or "she got him a present!"s?
No reaction?
Well, honestly...
I wasn't imagining this far ahead...
Our thought processes can't keep up anymore
Or like, the enemies are too strong...
I'm getting more pissed.
Do things like this really happen?
Not in my life.
With things calmed down
we talked about things we couldn't say before.
Like how we ended up liking each other
or what we were thinking...
no matter how much we talked
it seemed like we couldn't run out of things
to talk about.
At this point, I notice something strange.
One of my contacts
is missing...
Well, for a little while
things felt a little strange...
but I think that's it.
Well, we should look for it then.
Oh, it's disposable, so it's okay.
I see.
Yes.
Well, I can't see anything anymore.
Can you not see how I look like anymore?
I could actually see...
but...
No, I can't see it.
How about now?
You knieving trickster!
Hermes-tan!  This person lied to you!
Damn you for your continuous bombing!
You wanna kill us all?
Wait a minute, guys!
Am I the only one here who feels like
something isn't right?
We can't hold our own!
The bombing is closing in on us!
The final blow is about go come!
Abandon ship!  Abandon ship!
This time
Densha-san, you take the...
Not there.
Right here.
Maybe it was for 2 to 3 seconds
to think that there was something in this world so soft...
That's what I thought.
For the first time
I got a really good look
at her face.
It's as if I could see myself
reflected on her eyes...
We're being bombed!
What's with this honeymoon atmosphere!?
I'm departing for the afterlife...
Goodbye!
I'm done for.
After that...  She...
"I really care for you so much...
Densha-san"
She whispered that into my ear...
and she kissed me again.
The Hermes in my mind is crumbling apart!
If she told me "I care for you so much," I...
And then
our lips met several times
and finally...
we exchanged a grown-up kiss!
Wait a minute
what's a grown-up kiss?
Everyone's being shot from behind!
And that sums it up.
Everyone... thanks!
Now, I'm gonna get some rest.
See you later!
Give peace a chance!
What do you mean,
"We can't go out?"
If you're a man, just say it!
Well, your ankles aren't sexy, err..
Your ankles aren't my type!
Are you saying that my legs are fat?
Well, yes, if you want to be so bold...
Normally, a guy like you...
I would reject without a second thought!
I hate myself for having compromised so much!
Sorry to call you out.
Actually...
before I listen to what you have to say
I wanted to tell you something.
Sorry.
I
didn't think about your feelings
and was pushing my opinions on to you.
Like, in a way,
I felt like I was the one protecting you.
But that wasn't really the case, was it?
I was the one
who was afraid of relationships
and forgot about what was really important.
That's not true.
Kaho, because you were so concerned about me
I was able to face up to Yamada and see him eye to eye.
Saori
I was going to tell you about me and Yamada-san...
but I guess you already know.
Congrats.
Hermes-san.
Hey onii-chan, put your figures somewhere else!
(onii-chan = big brother)
The Tsuyoshi there...
Hurry up and sit down!
Matilda?
(pwned by Gundam references...)
Hey, what kind of nonsense are you talking about?
Oh it's you, mom.
Your voices are so similar!
We have to talk.
Sit down.
Well
Your mother...
is pregnant.
It's true!
Congratulations.
Um, when?
Well, the last time I came to stay
for my monthly night at home...
Yeah I...  Worked a little hard.
Amazing.
Watch yourself.
So what'll we name it?
Well, don't you think it's a little early?
I had an idea earlier...
if it's a girl...  How about Matilda?
I second that.
Matilda...  That's great!
How are you gonna write that in kanji?
I'm sorry.
I came here a little late.
Hermes sent me a text message...
she said:
"If only it was Sunday every day"
I'm...  So happy.
Sorry to butt in, but
post that on the couples forum or something.
Your time here is over, isn't it?
We don't have the time to listen to you brag.
You should go away before this thread gets 1000 replies.
Huh?  Is it just me,
or is everyone kind of cold?
Densha, listen up.
You're not single anymore.
In other words,
it's time for you to graduate from this thread.
We've decided not to look after you anymore.
It's a shame, but it's time to part our ways.
But I don't want to be separated from you guys.
I'll show up from time to time.
So...  Please don't be so cold to me.
I don't want to listen to your whining.
It's only bothersome if you're here any longer.
This thread is limited to bachelors.
You have no place here anymore.
Why?
I thought we'd all become a group...
That's so sad.
Don't you realize that we're telling you this
-because- we're your friends?
You must take a new step forward.
You're not alone anymore!
Be strong!
If you don't protect her,
Who's gonna protect Hermes?
Okay, I understand.
I'll depart.
Well said, Densha.
You'll be fine without us.
Let's give him a warm farewell with the
remaining 300 posts we have.
Everybody...
Tell him how you feel!
It's a bachelor graduation ceremony!
Densha, watching you,
I realized something.
I can't always be at the sidelines.
I'm gonna step up to the field
and have a relationship that everyone will envy!
You guys...  Venoa~!
I'm always soft on Hermes...
But today, Densha was my hero!
I'm not gonna lose to you.
I'll throw away these loose socks...
(loose socks = socks worn by Japanese HS girls)
...and work on a pantyhose fetish!
Last stop.  Last stop.
Best wishes for Densha and Hermes.
I'm gonna keep hard at my day job.
From platform 2,
the train bound for happiness is departing.
Hey, we only have 200 replies left.
"Densha, you taught us that
men aren't just about their outward looks.
You're definitely for real."
Okay, so that was just a test.
Thanks.
The reason why the jumbo jet carrying
the two was able to take off
was that you guys were always there
to refuel and maintain the plane.
I'm really glad I found this thread.
I felt drawn to your straightfoward personality
and cheered you on.
Young man,
enjoy life to its fullest!
Even I can help Hermes from a drunk.
But...
You're the only one for Hermes!
It's not a miracle.
You got through to her
with your own strength!
Just go to the couples forum.
I'll be encouraged the most
if you never have to come here again.
Heh, this is out of character for me.
I hate Densha!
and...
I hate myself even more for wishing for...
your happiness from the bottom of my heart!
Shoot, we're down to 100.
Too soon, too soon!
I guess everyone here wants to thank Densha.
Say it to your heart's content!
Good job, Densha.
I neglected my studies to cheer you on
which makes me depressed
to think about myself from now on.
But I think these 3 months
gave me something important in return.
I'm gonna get into college
and enjoy the campus life there too.
I love Densha and everyone else!
Me too.
I really
love you guys.
People have called me a slacker or a moocher
But for the first time,
I felt really involved in something
it's a landmark not only for Densha,
but also for me.
Well, that's a bit extreme,
but let's leave it at that.
These 3 months I spent with you all
It was loads of fun!
All hands, disarm yourselves!
Communications officer of the
8th youth infantry of the Yamada army
will now return to the base.
I'd like to share my appreciation
for having survived
with everyone here today.
Salute Densha!
Densha
I'm sure we'll see each other
on this thread again, right?
Then, I'll bet
you'll be coaching someone unsure of himself
like you youself were in the beginning.
I'm not saying good bye.
See you later, Densha.
And to all my comrades!
I really liked your personality.
I like how pure and straightfoward you are.
And more than anything
I like how much you care for Hermes.
I can't keep up with him
But I want to take care of my girl too.
After getting to know Densha
I really understood that guys
aren't just about looks.
My guy is pretty lame
but he's a really warm-hearted person.
I realized that after we were
cheering you on together.
I'm really grateful for that.
Me too.
I'm really grateful...
Something really trivial started this off
but with lots of courage
and a little minding of others' business
and your hard work and growth
must've brought forth this miracle.
You take care of her forever,
you hear?
Thanks to you,
I found myself back in a relationship
I had given up on.
Thanks for everything.
I guess this is good-bye.
I have to admit,
after I started to root for you
I started liking you.
I wouldn't have minded being
the first to sleep with you, you know.
The details please
on Densha and Hermes's future!
It'll be lonely after parting with you!
With hopes that I'll see you somewhere...
Towards a new day...
I'm off.
While watching over you two
a lot happened to me as well.
The most important thing
was that I got married.
And thanks to you,
my feelings for my wife really grew.
I'm really grateful.
My meeting you
is my pride and joy.
Everyone too...
You're my...
Pride and joy.
When I read Densha's report
I was glad that I set up this thread.
Not because it's the first time
a couple was formed
but, because I think you
brought smiles to a lot of faces.
Densha
You guys
Good work.
These 3 months were really something.
More than my regular life
the time here felt more real.
I guess as life goes on, memories fade
And this thread will disappear someday...
But I don't want to forget what happened here today.
Real life has all these messy problems...
but I guess there's some good too.
I think my time here made me realize that.
Some day, I want to see
what you're seeing
So I'm gonna walk forward
on my own terms.
So in the meantime,
you guys can show off to the couples forum!
I dropped out for a while
but I managed to see things
through to the very end.
You couldn't tell left from right at first
but thanks to everyone
but you're graduating now
as a true man.
Densha
don't let go of her hand.
No matter what happens.
From this day on
you'll experience a lot of things.
When things aren't going well,
remember this place.
What you've been doing...
What you've been told...
and, how you felt
facing Hermes through everything.
Best wishes for you two.
And to everyone here...
Thanks for the precious moments.
Damn...
Shoot.
I can't stop crying...
You guys
Thank you so much.
I'm so happy
and feel so courageous
and so grateful.
All these feelings are coming out
in the tears I'm shedding.
I'll never forget you guys.
Guys...
I love you!
I love you too man!
Now, I can rest in peace.
I'm crying more than a real graduation!
Everyone get ready - 50 to go!
I guess there'll be no new Densha thread.
This heartache...  It's so painful...
What am I gonna look forward to
from tomorrow on!?
Let us know when you get married.
To your everlasting happiness.
Let's stop posting here.
That way, we'll always be with Densha.
...yeah, I know that's not gonna happen...
I'm glad I won't have to hear
how affectionate you two are.
965.  In the end, Densha was our hope.
966. Densha...  I love you man!
Don't go!
967. The thread is almost over!
968.  No more Densha from now on.
I don't want that!
969. Why, for someone I don't even know
am I crying so much?
970. Soon, days without Densha will begin.
971. I'm getting choked up over
how much you guys care for Densha.
Densha is a really lucky guy.
972. Densha, you fill in the 1000th reply.
980. I can post the 1000th reply?
982. Densha, in the end...
Please send us a message!
984. It's time to say goodbye.
I can't even see what I'm typing...
985. I figured out what I'm gonna write.
These thoughts...
I've had all along.
986. I'm curious, but I don't want to read it!
987. ...because that'll be
the last we see of him!
990. Farewell, my friend!
991. I guess this is time...
992. Everyone, Densha...
I wish you well!
993. Everyone's too kind.
I was really moved!
994. Last post.
Densha, see you again somewhere.
995. Don't forget about us!
996. I guess this is...  the end...
997. If I get post 999 I'd confess
to someone too...if I had someone.
998. The departing whistle
is about to be blown!
Happy...
Graduation.
[Densha Otoko, congratulations!]
1000. This thread...
It's way too magical...
I hope the light will shine on you guys...
[1001. This thread has 1000 posts.
Please set up another one...]
it's because of these people
that we got together, right?
Yeah.
Keep it up...
Densha Otoko.
I guess I go out
and buy a few things...
Going out?
Yep.
I'm going out with Tsuyoshi-san.
Saori.
You're looking bright and cheerful.
You too, mother.
See you later!
I'll be on my way.
See you!
Bye mother.
[Broken Heart Restaurant]
(it's also an album released by Kentarou Shimizu)
Long time no see.
You hanging in there?
This is called a restaurant,
but we only serve coffee, dumbass.
Then I'll have one.
Misuzu-san...
Why'd you leave without say anything?
Hey
Misuzu... as in, Misuzu Jinkama?
You too, huh?
Sa...  Sakurai-san...
How long were you here?
For a little while.
Hey, so...
did she make a victim out of you, too?
Victim?
You too?
Not just me.
We...
Thanks to that woman...
Got our lives messed up!
I spent so much money on her...
My boss was into her too
Thanks to that, I fell off my career track!
My wife found out and we divorced...
I changed flights just to see her!
I bought her a lot of brand name shoes!
I...
Okay, then.
Let's for a 'Victims of Misuzu Jinkama Club!'
Yeah!
I have to find someone new.
[I'll departing.  Thanks for everything!
-Misuzu]
Sorry I'm late.
Shall we get going?
They were really nice people.
Yes.
Translation, scripting, blah blah by Masakun
Original timing by chandlerkim@gmail.com
Special thanks to my friends for
the encouragement and comments.
You know who you are.
[Densha Otoko - the other ending!
A 30-minute extended version on Oct. 6!]