We're baaack
Something's wrong with Akihabara!
You're kidding!  Let's go check it out!
Transform into reentry mode!
Right on!
"You're wondering who I am"
"Secret secret, I've got a secret"
"Machine or mannequin"
"With parts made in Japan"
"Secret secret, I've got a secret"
"I am the modern man"
Atchan, what food can't you eat?
Almond tofu and green peas.
Roger that.
Sorry to keep you waiting, master
"The Legit Maid Cafe"
-Getting around has been so difficult lately-
Now that Normal People have overrun the streets
Otakus like us have been scrutinized with their curious stares
If you walk around in Otaku gear...
You'll end up falling prety to those people!
On my way here...
I was targeted by so many camera lenses
Akihabara
It was once the Holy Land
of all Otakus
However, with the Otaku boom,
Normal People started to flow in
The Otakus were losing
their place to call home
Time passed by...
2006 AD
The Otaku Holy Land of Akihabara
has changed drastically in the past year
Today we'd like to see how Otakus feel about this
There they are!
Wearing backpacks and tucking in their shirts
Excuse me, if you don't mind
Is this an interview?
In recent days, Akihabara has changed drastically
...has any good come out of this transformation?
There's nothing good!
Okay
In that case, we'll show you the crisis faced by Akihabara!
Maid cafes, unfortunately,
have become tourist attractions!
Now, not only couples come...
but even kids taking a break from class trips!
Say cheese!
In this...
foreign place, us Otakus can't feel at home!
The oden cans, an Akihabara specialty,
are not only bought by Normal People
but are regarded as scenic spots,
and we can't go buy them anymore!
It's an otaku!
Wait!  Hold on!
O.T.S.
(otaku smell detection system)
What the fuck?
Where'd that person go?
Just between you and me...
Some legit otakus who're tired of today's Akihabara
are seeking refuge in the underground maid cafes
Are you not going?
No way!
I still have my otaku pride
Even if I'm the last one left on this planet
I have no plans to let the spirit of my otaku culture wilt
Please stop!
I'm not some animal from the wild...
What is it going to take to satisfy...
your need to destroy our Holy Land!?
Damn ota
("Ota" is short for, well, you know)
Magnificent view
President Maezono
Would you please reconsider just once more?
Yamazaki-san
My answer is 'no,' regardless of how many times you ask
Please go back
Hello, Mr. Maezono
I warmed your seat for you
What did you want?
Well, you see...
My dad's company went under,
and the bank took the bar that I managed
and well, money...
I can't help you
Don't be a dick, man
I helped you out when you were in LA, remember?
Yes, I guess you did
That's right
Isn't that coat mine?
Whoa, uhh, that's right
Okay, if you can give me something I could never get on my own...
I'll think about investing in your business
Oh really?
They don't call you the Wizard of Stocks for nothing
You make the most eccentric comments
Oh wait, wait, there is!
Something you could never get for the life of you!
Hermes
No, not the Hermes brand
Densha Otoko's Hermes?
So you know about her...
Information is everything for our industry
Of course I'd know about her.
Well, then let's cut through the chase
Even you stand no chance...
against Densha Otoko
I'm not that handsome
Mr. Yamada!  Where were you?
You had a chance to be on TV
Uh, well...
Oh shoot, it's Densha Otoko!
They even made a movie about him...
but even now, his true identity remains a mystery
Guitar Otoko exposed himself, but nobody really cared
How dare you!
Damn you, Mr. Kawamoto
Miina Kick!
Akihabara has really become...
difficult to live in
Will we otakus continue to be labled as outcasts?
Excuse me, but I have something important today
Was there an anime episode today?
No, it's not that, but
Excuse me.
Oh wait, we have something important to do today
You're right
Today is the day Densha Otoko will propose to Hermes
Hey wait a minute
What if Mr. Yamada is Densha Otoko
No way, no way!
Okay
Sorry I'm late
No it's okay, I just got here too
Shall we go?
Sure
Densha still isn't back
My girlfriend is tired of waiting
I hope Densha's proposal goes well
We cut our date short and are standing by
My wife and I are wondering where Densha is
My wife too, but she went to her parents' home to have our baby
Hey...
Aren't there lots of couples in this thread now?
Images of your triumphant smiles flew by my head
This is where single guys spit out their bitterness!
Weren't we gonna be single to our death?
Traitor!
Cut out the affection crap!
Don't pout, you virgin
Man, a girlfriend...
I got home just now
Densha
He's back!
Densha Otoko DX
The last Holy War
The visions dancing in my mind
The early dawn, the shades of time
Twilight crawling through
my windowpane
Am I awake or do I dream?
The strangest pictures I have seen
Night is day and twilight's gone away
With your head held high
and your scarlet lies
You came down to me
from the open skies
It's either real or it's a dream
There's nothing that is in between...
Twilight, I only meant to stay awhile
Twilight, I gave you
time to steal my mind
Away from me.
Timing by  ¢ÓKenSin¢Ó
http://hermes.mireene.com
http://jung6093.cy.ro
http://blog.naver.com/jung6093
English subs by Masakun
http://www.cornpotage.com
masakun@gmail.com
Like I announced earlier,
I set out today..
To propose to Hermes
Should I start with the results first?
No!  Tease us like you did when you confessed to her!
We're all masochists here
Surely it went well this time
They say the third time is the charm
I can't wait for the good news
Just to double check, Hermes isn't reading this, right?
He couldn't write here if she was
Right check, left check, you're all clear to go!
The energy level is going up!
Gimme the details, please!
I spent 3 months' worth my salary on an engagement ring and set out
And took her to where you told me to...
Joel Robuchon
After our meal was over
my nervousness maxed out
Is something wrong?
Is there something on my face?
N, no
Uhm...
I, I, I have something to say to you
W, w, w, will you
b, b, b, b, b...
b, b, b, b, b, b...
b...  b, b, b, b, b...
believe in blood type fortune telling?
Y, yes
I actually like it
Is that so?
Yuko told me an interesting story a few days ago
People's fates are decided before they're born
I see
Of course, that includes romance
There's a country where your love life is inscribed...
in a pearl
Romantic, isn't it?
Yes, it is
Your pearls and mine must have...
the same writing inscribed on them
Uh, um...
I have something important to say to you
Will you...
m, m, m, m, m, m...
m, m, m, m, m, m, m, m, m...
m, m, m, m, m...
m...
marry me?
Who the fuck would marry you?
You gotta be kidding
I...
haven't changed a bit
What are you saying?  You fought well
Proposing is totally different from confessing
Don't rush -- take things one step at a time
Thanks
I'll do my best!
I'll leave the rest to you
Hello everyone
We're looking to find the wherabouts of Densha Otoko
We'll give 10 million yen ($100,000 US) to anyone who can give us his whereabouts
Details will be posted on CyberNext's website
We await your information
Cyber Next, isn't that...
the new IT company everyone's talking about?
10 million...  Kitaaaaa
It's a website of a legit company, so this isn't a fluke
Didn't Densha talk about himself before?
I'll copy and paste what he wrote...
"I'm a regular Akihabara otaku
Age: 23, annual income 3-4 million yen
($30k - $40k US)
typical house, no car, fits right in to Akihabara"
That means he's now 24!
If we all help out, we can expose him
Let's all exchange info, and agree not to hate on whoever catches him
I heard a rumor that Densha frequents...
...a maid cafe called Pinafore
(it really does exist)
How weird...  Before it was just couples and schookids here
Aren't people really edgy, too?
Whoa, it's Densha Otoko!
Aww man
Densha Otoko sighting at the 6th Ishimaru Denki store!
Let's go!
Did something happen?
For today, we have an extra special guest...
Karin Takeda!
Hello everyone
Say hello, everyone
I heard Densha Otoko is a huge fan of Karin Takeda
Okay okay, so you finished studying abroad in Los Angeles
but did you hear about Densha Otoko?
Yeah, a lot of people there talked about it too
Okay, so what if..
What if he was here in this crowd today?
Hmmm...
I'd like to tak him to my room and chat with him until morning
Just the two of you?
So, Densha Otoko, what are you gonna do?
I'm Densha Otoko
No I'M Densha Otoko!
Oh wow
We can't tell who's the real Densha!
If you're the real one, please smile and keep on jumping
If you're the real Densha, hold your breath until I tell you to breathe
Karin...
Karin?
Uhh...  Karin?
Um...  Karin...?
Until next time!
Karin-chan!  Tell them they can breathe now!
There's a good chance he uses the Chuo line
Hey...  hey!
Wasn't he at Takeda Karin's radio show?
He was, he was
He might be Densha
Age: 23
Annual income: 3-4 million yen
No car, normal household, looks like he's from Akihabara
It all fits
It would appear to be that way
Hey wait!
Shit!  Where'd he go?
Go look over there
I'll check this way
Sounds like a plan.
There's 10 million yen on the line
10 million?
Something about Akihabara weirded me out today
I heard a lot of people say "Densha Otoko" and "10 million"
You guys know anything?
Please, serious replies only!
You're finally back
You won't believe what's happened
Cyber Next is offering 10 million yen to whoever can find Densha Otoko
Cyber Next?
Win 10 million yen!
Find Densha Otoko!
What is this?
I found a guy at a maid cafe who fits Densha's description
There's a good chance that Densha wears glasses at Akihabara
We saw someone suspicious at Karin Takeda's radio show
We lost him at Musashi-sakai
Aren't these guys...
Let's all go to Musashi-sakai tomorrow
We have to find everyone who fits Densha's description!
We'll call this...
The Hunt for Densha Otoko
The Hunt for Densha Otoko?
Why are they doing this...
You're definitely a celebrity now
You're the star of hope for all otakus
Plus, they find you and get 10 million
I bet Cyber Next is using you to raise their stock price
They have no morals -- they're totally making fools out of otakus
In any case, you'll be done for if they find you
What's so bad about being found?
You dimwit!
Terrible things are gonna happen
Photos of you and your private information might float across the internet
Not to mention Hermes's photos
Then, without a doubt, you can kiss your private life good-bye
Strangers' inquisitive eyes will stare at you all day long
Your family members and coworkers might run into trouble too
Yonesuke is gonna show up and eat your dinner!
(Yonesuke is a Japanese comedian)
Of course, Hermes will be targeted, too
She'll show up in otakus' fantasies
Fantasies?
Hermes...  Hermes...  HERMES
I can guarantee she'll be the target of everything on the internet
Sickos who imagined Hermes as their girlfriend...
might show up one day and stab you!
Oh no...
Now you understand?
These are hypothetical situations, but not entirely unreal
Always anticipate your enemies' next move
End all phone conversations in 30 seconds to fend off wire tappers
If you're going to go out, be extra careful
Can't wait until tomorrow's movie
Conversations in 30 seconds...
Sorry to call you so late
No it's okay -- is something wrong?
Tomorrow's movie...  Can we cancel it?
That's fine, but did something happen?
It's just that you rarely bail out on me at the last moment
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry
No, it's okay
Um, okay, so...  Good night!
29 seconds...
That was close...
Hey, this...
Is this some kind of joke?
I'm doing this to protect my family
You're troubling that very same family
What the hell is going on here?
What are you talking about?
Oh yeah, next Sunday
can you lend me...
your Hermes teacup set?
Hey, what the hell?
What do you want?
Enoki
Tsudanuma
Funabashi
Ichikawa
Hey Village Elder, what's with that outfit?
Help us out with this game, Village Elder
You can't cross here with the boat
You have to go back to the tower of shadows...
He's running away
That's Densha Otoko!
Densha Otoko?
10 million!
Wait!  10 million!
We will offer 10 million yen
What the fuck do you mean,
'capture Densha Otoko!?'
Why didn't you tell me?
I did
I asked you to tell me who Densha was
I didn't know about the 10 million yen offer
So what if you knew about it?
Is it not too late?
Huh?  Am I not hunted anymore?
Cyber Next's website had a post saying they called off the search for Densha
Awesome
But why did they call it off after only a few days?
Wasn't that just a PR stunt?
They're just trying to inflate their stock price
You think someone found out Densha Otoko's identity?
What am I gonna do?
If they found out I'm Densha...
Calm down, it's just a possibility
Even if that were so, don't you think they would...
contact you before releasing the info to the public?
If there was a winner, they might release Densha's info on the internet anyway
There still might be scavengers after the prize money
With or without the money, people might be interested in who Densha really is
We still don't know Cyber Next's motives behind this
I think you'd better hold off on seeing Hermes for a while
I understand
I'll hold off from seeing her a little while longer
Grandpa
What happened?
Come inside
No, no
Right here is fine
I have a favor to ask you
Me?
I want you to accompany me to lunch with a client of mine
That's a blind date for sure
You think so?
You said no, right?
My grandpa begged me to, so I couldn't say no
Did you tell Tsuyoshi Yamada?
I wanted to talk to him, but...
He hasn't been able to see me lately
Nobody following me
You're finally back
This is Saori-san's grandfather
Excuse me
It's embarassing, but even at this age I had another child
Please, enjoy
Matilda!  Matilda!
Saori-san's grandfather...
N, nice to meet you
I...  I'm Saori-san's...
Are you Densha Otoko?
How do you...
Well...
I had a request of you
Can you break up with Saori?
Someone told me about the Densha Otoko hunting
Does Saori-san know?
I could never tell her
It would only frighten her
I'm sorry
If something happened to my granddaughter, it would break my heart
Please understand
But...
Then let me ask you, do you have the confidence to protect Saori, no matter what?
In the end, I couldn't reply back
Grandpa Hermes, huh?
Now that's a dark horse for you
It's a new obstacle between you two
What'll it take for him to accept you?
You have to convince him that you're a dependable guy
I think I couldn't respond because I'm not confident in myself
I can't be a dependable guy...
Then build up that self-confidence
Become successful at your job
Join the army!
Drink some protein juice!
You'll feel more confident if you go to Tenjiku and obtain the sutra
Go to Iskandar and obtain the anti-radiation device there
What about obtaining the black pearl of fate?
The black pearl of fate?
It's a hoax that floated around the internet for a while
When you hold it up to the sun, you see your future in romance inscribed...
on the inside of the black pearl
Your first love, bitter separation, a new love
and marrying the one dearest to you
It's all inscribed in the black pearl
Our pearls must have...
the same writing inscribed on them
I heard about that before
So is there a black pearl that tells the future of my love life?
Of course, there's a black pearl for every one of us
How romantic?
When you tell your name and birthday to the sage who guards them
You can obtain the black pearl
It's as unbelievable as the Loch Ness Monster
I've never seen anyone who actually has one
But wouldn't it be great if it said that you were going to marry Hermes?
Where's the black pearl?
Whoa, don't take us seriously
Apparently a sage who lives deep in the jungle of Tahiti...
watches over the black pearls,
but not much is known
Where's Tahiti?
It's a French Polynesian island
in the South Pacific
it's a paradise that's a popular honeymoon spot
Good job on the info
It sounds like you have to go there and find out
Don't take this rumor seriously
There are some shady ones out there
And you don't know if the outcome will be good
Think of something else
Actually, there's been a part of me that wondered...
if I'm fit to be Hermes's husband
And then today
her grandfather asked me
and my insecurity only grows
So now, I would really do anything I can
I want to look for the black pearl and find out...
the future that awaits us
If the result is good, I'll be confident
I'm going to Tahiti...
to find the black pearl!
300...?
(100 yen = $1)
Loveless Restaurant
The Misuzu Jinkama Victim's Club...
has gone global
China
Thailand
India
Iran
Saudi Arabia
The Vatican
Spain
Oikawa-san
I need some quick cash,
so I'd like to work part-time after hours
Sure, that's fine
Thank you
Take those shutters away!
Jinkama-san must be in Germany right now
Yamada!
Bring the monkey wrench!
Here you go
Man, you're slow
Just go home
Here, here's your payment
30th anniversary
Raffle tickets
Am I fired?
Hey Carl!  Bring me the pliers!
It was nice working with you
Now that's an otaku if I ever saw one
He'll never have a girlfriend
Excuse me
Um, what can we do for you?
Where's Tsuyoshi Yamada?
Yamada just left
I see..  Thank you
Excuse me
Forgive me for prying...
but you two are...
He's my boyfriend
Thank you, come again
Show us your raffle ticket
for your chance to win big!
Right over here!
1st place -- an LCD TV!
Take it home
It's yours now -- go for it!
The red ball for the TV
If I sell it I could fund my trip
Okay 3 times
Good luck!
Sorry
Here, a sponge!
Try again
Your last chance -- good luck!
Oh crap, no TV
You win!
You won the special prize...
Tickets for two...
To Tahiti!
To Tahiti?
Congratulations!
Here are your tickets
Long time no see
Jinkama-san
Weren't you in Germany?
Well, the German frankfurters...
They weren't as great as I had hoped
You got tired of eating them?
Tahiti, huh?
The last paradise?
Sounds pretty exciting
No, give it back please
You're so annoying
Give it back!
Here, I'll scrub you with the sponge
Ouch!
Jinkama-san
Canned tuna, check
Swimming trunks, check
Matilda, check
Canned tuna, check
Swimming trunks, check
Matil...
Hello?
Sorry to call you so late
No problem
I was just about to call you too
Well...
I'm going to that South Pacific island...
Hitachi
Hitachi?
You sure it's not Tahiti?
Oh...  You're right, Tahiti
Are you going with someone?
Well...
It would take me a while to explain...
I see...
Saori-san, you wanted to talk to me?
We can talk when you come back
Please enjoy your trip
I takled to Hermes just now
I couldn't tell her my reason for going to Tahiti
Should I have told her?
Don't worry about it
You're going to boost your self-confidence
Just tell her after you come back
Just think about Tahiti for now
Have you ever been overseas?
N, no...
Come to think of it,
I was so focused on the black pearls...
I didn't think that far ahead
I...  What should I do?
Take it easy.
I figured as much, and looked stuff up for you
I bought a guide book at the book store
Go to Narita airport, not Haneda
Just make sure you don't get on
"Super Hitachi" (a train)
Joban line...  Kitaaaaa
Make sure to check beforehand if you need to tip people
Put the curtains on the inside when you shower
Don't take a dump on the bidet!
You have your pickled plums?
You brush your teeth?
You do your homework?
See you next week
"Don't finish yet,"
he exclaimed.
If you listen to what we tell you,
you'll for sure be fine
Henceforth this will be...
Densha Otoko Overseas Travel Project
Densha Otoko
Overseas
Travel Project
Travelling overseas carries many dangers
As soon as you set foot on the airport,
think that everyone is your enemy!
Nobody's gonna steal your stuff!
There's no way to be certain
There are many things in here...
that I value more than my life!
This dirty figure too?
I took this because I didn't want this Matilda to be eaten by the Matilda at home
I'm not sure what you're talking about
but don't get on the wrong flight
What?  We're not boarding together?
Of course I'm not riding economy class
Take off your shoes when boarding the plane
...is something even a child wouldn't do
It's a plane bound for Tahiti, so...
What a coincidence!
I'm going to Tahiti, too!
...shouldn't be said
The windows won't open!
Uh, excuse me
Could you let me know when we see...
the International Date Line?
To wish Densha Otoko well on his travels
All hands...  Salute!
I HATE this...
Couples everywhere!
Hold my stuff, will ya?
Excuse me
Can you take a picture for me please?
Sure
Say cheese
Thank you
Excuse me
Can you take a picture of me please?
Thank you so much
Misuzu-san is mine!
How dare you, right on our honeymoon!
Unforgivable!
Shot 2!
Unbelievable!
What the hell!
You piss me off!
Why me?
What are you doing?
You have such an otaku body
Why don't you learn a thing or two from those guys?
What are you...
You know, I heard something
There's a Man of the Black Pearl in this country
His balls are supposed to be amazing
What are you doing?
Ouch!
Tsuyoshi!
You'll for sure find the black pearl of fate!
The tour to find the black pearl of fate
will depart in a few moments
Um, so if I join this...
Can I find the black pearl of fate?
Yes, of course
Yamada!
Why are you in uniform?
The black pearl of fate might be in the ocean
Okay
Okay, here are your black pearls of fate
Yamashita-san
They're not in the ocean?
Matsuda-san
Yamada-san
This is the fated...
black pearl!
Happiness forever
in Tahiti?
Excuse me
My black pearl doesn't have anything about
my future love or my romantic fortune
There's no way a pearl this small would show that!  You're such a clown
They've got a lot of meat
but not where it counts
Jinkama-san...
What're you doing?
Yeah, I was doing it...
but they can't compare to
the Man of the Black Pearl
Speaking of a black pearl
did you see one around here?
You mean this?
Yes, that!
Can you give it back please?
Yamada?
Me?
They say that there are 3 people in the world who look like you...
but he really does resemble you
Enough of that
We have to administer CPR
Why the fuck do I have to do that?
It's you're fault he's like this!
Okay
I'll do it, I'll do it
What're you doing?
It pisses me off to look at his face
He's saved!
T...  Thank you
You bet
If I didn't save you
Hey wait, you speak Japanese?
Yes
I'm TuyoTam, a travel guide
Bullshit
A fake?
Many black pearls of fate
made for tourists they are
Real ones difficult to get
Where are the real ones?
Deep in mountains
Deep deep in mountains
But
dangerous it is
I really want it.
Please tell me!
Why want it you do?
That...
I want someone to push my back
I want to know that even someone like me
can be with the woman I love
I want that kind of confidence
My house, has map it does
Go find pearl you can
Black pearl
Found at Tahai island
Road to cave where sage is,
very scary, dangerous
Jungle
Feared even by locals
But, okay it is
Everything written down I have
Read it carefully
Thanks, TuyoTam
Okay...  I'm off!
You know so much about it
Yes.  Get black pearl, once I did
So, is the Man of the Black Pearl there too?
Not there
Then where?
Right here
You've gotta be kidding
At the base of that mountain...
The black pearl!
Tahai people
Guardians of island
Very hostile to outsiders
Sacrifice you they will
if you commit a mistake
Skulls you may find
This is the 21st century
There's no way that's real
Phew, what a scare
I'm so nervous, I'm about to leak
Tahai man, to protect his territory
urinate on his tree he will
If someone else should urinate on it,
sacrificed they will be
Check the smell you should
Not here
And here!
Saori-san
I have to climb here?
I leaked a little
I can't hold it in anymore!
I can't stop
The river...  Very important
Beat shit out of you they will
...if you taint it
Hail the virgin!
All hail...  the virgin!
Dance
Dance!
You want me to dance?
Matilda-san?
Tsuyoshi, retreating!
Shoot, I left my bag behind
I don't have my map
What am I gonna do?
Help meeeeee
Help me...
I can't do this anymore...
Grandpa...
This is a blind date, isn't it
I'm sorry
At this rate, our family...
...and my 3,000 employees
would be left stranded
But...
Are you Ms. Saori Aoyama?
Nice to meet you
I'm Maezono
You weren't up for today's date, were you?
That's not true
But for me, it was very good
I've only spoken to you for a few hours
But it hit me
You're the woman I'm destined to be with
I'm sorry, I'm currently seeing someone
I know
but
I'm definitely being drawn...
to you
It's the cave!
Saori-san...
led me here!
These are
the black pearls of fate!
Mr. Kuroki??
Kuroki?
Kurokki!
Kurokki?
Oh um, I want my black pearl
My name is Tsuyoshi Yamada,
my birthdate is...
Silence!
You don't need to tell me.
Uh, Japanese?
Thank you so much!
No problem
I finally found it...
Timing by  ¢ÓKenSin¢Ó
http://hermes.mireene.com
http://jung6093.cy.ro
English subtitles by Masakun
http://www.cornpotage.com
masakun@gmail.com
TuyoTam, I found the black pearl!
Jinkama-san?
What are you doing here?
I got it too...
The black pearl
I never saw one so convoluted
I'm staying here for a while
TsuyoTam is out in the back
Jinkama-san
so cute she is
TuyoTam!
I found the black pearl of fate!
Wow, amazing it is!
What does this say?
22 years old, will be with woman, no no no
Afterwards,
meet someone out of his league he will
Help him his many friends do
and his love, realize it will be
but...
What's wrong?
Tell me
Before their one year anniversary
While he away from Japan
love of his life, for many reaon
finds another man she will
She then be happy
Another man?
I don't know
But, what's inscribed here always comes true
No...
But then me and Saori-san...
That can't be!
I...  As black pearl said...
woman I loved in the past
left me behind
Us two... our face
our hearts...
very alike
So understand your pain I do
Thanks
I might break up with Hermes
What are you talking about?
There really was a black pearl of fate
but on the black pearl given to me by the sage
was inscribed words that foretold the end...
of the relationship I have with Hermes
And on my way back home
something unbelievable happened
Need a lift?
Huh?  A blind date?
Let me get to the point
Give me Saori-san
I can make her happy
I can say that with confidence
I can make her happy too
Well, it's difficult for me to say this, but...
her grandfather's company
isn't doing well these days
and needs some help from my company
In other words,
from a financial standpoint as well...
I can protect her and her family
Can you do the same?
I was shocked
Not only that Hermes went on a date
but also that I couldn't protect her and her family
The guy really might be able to keep her happy
Snap out of it!
Hermes is only interested in you!
Hermes did it to save her Grandpa's face!
Cut her some slack!
But what's this about Hermes's family
being in dire straits?
That doesn't matter!
Densha's feelings can overcome anything!
Who cares about the black pearl!
Who cares about the blind date?
Let me ask you this
Densha, can you break up with Hermes?
Can you give Hermes to that other guy?
Densha, think carefully
You should know what is best for Hermes
Tsuyoshi
You have a guest
Sir...
Sorry to come by again and again
There was something else to
what I told you the other day
You mean the blind date?
You knew about it?
I know this is a lot to ask of you
But...  I can't take this anymore
It's beyond my control now.
Please
For the sake of Saori and our family
and also our 3,000 employees
please break up with Saori
Please
I beg of you
Before our one year anniversary
The woman I love the most,
due to a variety of circumstances
will be with someone else
Financially as well,
I can care for her and her family
For my family...
...and 3,000 employees
Would you please break up with Saori?
Saori-san
I broke up with Hermes today
Uh...
W, w, w, w, w, w, w, what are you...
Red alert!  Yamanashi prefecture
8th combat unit communications officer
We're under attack!
G, g, g, g, give me the details!
I'm sorry...
to call you out here all the sudden
It's okay
I wanted to see you and clear up some things
I was going to ask you before
I...
can't...
make...
you happy
Please...
break up with me
Why?
Is it because of Misuzu-san?
Did you go to Tahiti with her too?
I knew in the back of my mind...
Our phone calls became very short
and you weren't able to see me
I could sense that
your feelings weren't with me
I'm so sorry
That's why
I don't...
I..
love...
love you anymore
Being with you...
was what made me happy
Good bye.
Even when you love someone...
There are things beyond your control
If I leave, her family...
and more importantly,
she herself will be happy
This is how it should be
That's bullshit!
How can you say that it's for her good!?
You're only worried about money!
Don't betray us because of some money problems!
It's true that my financial weakness
is one reason
I can't protect her
And the other guy can
But...  Our looks and who we are...
I wasn't up to her level
And in any case,
I don't think it would have worked out
What the...
This isn't like you, Densha
You're already talking like you're over her!
Were your feelings for her that weak?
You're despicable!
You stomped on not only our feelings...
but those of Hermes as well!
Densha, you're just being a coward
Why don't you try to make Hermes happy on your own?
The Densha we know...
Would have pushed such obstacles aside!
If I think about her life
This is the best choice for her
As long as she's happy,
I'm fine with that
Please try to understand
You're only trying to look good
You can still do something about this
That's unacceptable!
What the hell happened to you Densha!?
I want Densha and Hermes to stay together!
We'll help you out the best we can, too!
Don't lose to some hotshot president!
You've stood up to so much up until now!
It's not hopeless!
Get back with her!
Densha, you're a hero for otakus like us!
Hermes is waiting for you, Densha
If there's anything we can do...
Let us know!
You overcame so many obstacles
This time, you can come out strong too!
It hurts...
Reading all your posts...
hurts me so much...
I'm sorry
I don't think I can live up to your expectations
Thank you
Thank you so much
For all your help
But...
I...
I'm finished
I'm glad I came here
I suddenly pictured your sad face
And this...
are you sure?
With things like this,
someone's gotta take care of it
I'll safeguard it for now
Thanks...
for doing all this
No worries
The Miina figure
The tazer gun
A pair of chokers
Dammit, when she gave him this,
they exchanged a grown-up kiss...
How's my Densha Otoko Museum?
It's perfect.
I'm arranging all this, after all.
I'm leaving this to you
The Densha Otoko Museum is going to get
my foot in the otaku industry's door
I know!
This isn't someone else's business for me either!
I put all your 10 million yen into our stock
If this works, Cyber Next's
brand recognition will shoot straight up
And the stock price will go up 100 fold,
no, 200 fold!
I can finally kiss my pennysaving days goodbye!
Now witness the miraculous comeback performance of Kazuya Sakurai!
...and you're already gone
Are you really okay with this?
Yes.  Maezono-san seems like a kind person
He kind of reminds me of your father
He's kind of cold-hearted...
and I can't really tell what he's thinking
Is Yamada-san really all that bad?
It's fine
This way,
grandpa's business can get back on track
I...
I don't care if I live in a studio apartment
Mother...
I died again
Tsuyoshi!
You have a guest
Jinkama-san
You've been pretty busy, haven't you
You have Saori-san, and yet...
But when I was young,
I met many young girls and...
You fucking talk way too much, old man!
Weren't you in Tahiti?
I got tired of Mr. Black Pearl
I heard rumors of a really great man
in South America
Is that so?
What's with the long face?
I broke up with Saori-san
It's just as the black pearl foretold
To protect her grandfather's company,
Saori-san...
went out with her grandfather's client!
That's not what it's foretelling
This is your real black pearl
What do you mean?
It was all a ploy
When TuyoTam read your black pearl...
he thought it was strange...
that the fortune was cut off in the middle
When we confronted the Sage about this
He told us that a Japanese man bribed him
into giving you a fake black pearl
Who would...
Some creep named Maezono
He did it to cause a rift between you two
Maezono-san did?
What are you gonna do?
What do you mean?
You pulled back because
you wanted her to be happy, right?
You think she can be happy with Maezono?
Sheesh...
Tsuyoshi Yamada is here to see you
Let him in
It's about time you came here
You tricked me
Giving me a fake black pearl...
Look who's talking
It's your fault for believing something like that and breaking up with her
Densha Otoko
How do you...
You still don't know?
Cyber Next...
Indeed!
The brains behind
"The Hunt for Densha Otoko"
Also, the one who put her grandpa's company
on the line in exchange for her hand
is also me.
How could you...
Of course
to take Hermes
She's a mighty fine woman
She knows it's a political marriage,
but for her grandfather's company
she'll sacrifice herself
Well, you can't save the Aoyama family
So then
I'll give you a chance
Cyber Next
Densha Otoko Museum
Cyber Next presents:
Densha Otoko Museum?
Exactly
If you go up on stage tomorrow and tell everyone you're Densha Otoko
I'll release her from her obligations
Of course,
I'll invest in her grandfather's company
What do you think?
It's up to you to come or not
Tomorrow is opening day
We haven't started but the stock price is already shooting up
Densha Otoko is taking center stage
Everyone will be talking about it
Densha is?
He's really coming here?
He'll come by for sure.
Why are you so confident?
I told him that
I won't marry Hermes if he comes on stage
You're giving up on Hermes?
If he goes up on stage,
he'll be at the center of media attention
If so, the person
who'll be most troubled is Hermes
He understands this
So even if he exposes himself,
he won't get back with Hermes
So either way,
Densha won't be with Hermes
In this world...
true love never becomes realized
Densha Otoko, if you expose your identity,
I'll let go of Hermes
It's so hard to get tickets!
Mr. Kawamoto!
The phone!
What are you breaking my phone for?
What are you doing?
Apparently at the Densha Otoko museum,
his true identity will be revealed!
What do you mean his identity?
You know who he is already
Yuko, what do you mean?
Since Densha Otoko is Tsuyoshi Yamada,
there's no point in us going to see!
Hello?
Mr. Yamada!
Yuko told us everything
To think that you were Densha Otoko...
I'm sorry I hid that from you
Are you going to show yourself to the public?
Yes
Why?
It's the condition for him to not marry Hermes
But I thought you left Hermes on your own
It was all a scheme
This is the only way...
to save Saori-san and the Aoyamas
I'm sorry
Mr. Yamada?
Mr. Yamada!
He turned off his phone!
What are you gonna do?
If Mr. Yamada comes out as Densha Otoko
The media is gonna get him,
and he'll be ruined!
We have to stop him somehow
...hey what do you think you're doing?
I see it!
So you were in deep contemplation
Long time no see
This is Guitar Otoko
Guitar Otoko?
I found some information about Densha
As a condition for Hermes to be let free
he's exposing his identity at
the Densha Otoko museum!
You're kidding...
So it was in Maezono's plans to have
Densha break up with Hermes!
It was all going as Maezono planned!
Is Densha going to expose himself
for Hermes's sake?
If he shows himself,
the Densha haters will ruin him!
Densha...  Come back!
But the probability of him reading this...
Is 0%!
So long as he isn't reading this thread,
there's nothing we can do
But if he decided this without
talking to us first...
does that mean he doesn't need us anymore?
It was like this when he broke up with her, too
Densha is already somewhere way beyond us
He can go on his own without our help
It's kinda lonely...
But...
The one most lonely...
is Densha, isn't it?
Yes...
You're right
Everyone
listen up
A part of me thought that
Densha doesn't need us anymore
But...
Densha and us...
None of us are strong people
That's why we all help each other out, right?
You guys...
Can we let Densha go to battle alone?
You're right
If we don't help Densha in his time of need,
who will?
He's ready to give up everything
Isn't this the time to give back to Densha
what he gave to all of us?
Don't fall victim to
Cyber Next!
I won't let people making fun of Akihabara
walk all over me!
But what should we do?
Chief, you have a plan, right?
Of course
There's only one thing we can do
Cyber Next
Densha Otoko Museum
Sorry to come by all the sudden
It's okay
Here's Yamada's black pearl of fate
I forgot to give this to him
...so I thought if you could
Yamada, he...
went out of his way to find that for you
but...  He...
I thought he was into you...
No way!
If I was misleading you I'll apologize
but Yamada doesn't even look at other women
And that Maezono guy...
He has his feet deep in some shady business
Take her to dinner in return for the cup
Hermes's famous sayings
I'm not letting go
It's okay
Densha Otoko!
Read the message board!
Densha!
Confess to her!
I...
Aoyama-san...
I like you so much!
Densha Otoko
Museum
You want to call off the engagement?
My grandfather told me everything
about you, too
What a fool
But it looks like you found out too late
Thank you for attending
"Cyber Next Presents:"
"Densha Otoko Museum"
Thank you very, very much
And now
The true identity of Densha Otoko
will be revealed on the special stage
Everyone please look forward to it!
Don't hate me, Densha
Cyber Next stock is up again!
Why...
Densha Otoko is a good source of money
It's hard to come across a love story
so pure and emotional
The more you wave this in front of people
foolish people will twist this into
an ugly love story
So I...
will put an end to this story
For business purposes only
And the door is locked, by the way
It's showtime!
Momentarily,
Densha Otoko's identity will be revealed
We ask that our guests please head over
to the special auditorium
I'm sorry
but I can't let you pass here
This road has been sealed off!
I won't let you pass!
I bet those guys
are fighting for Densha right now
Fight for my sake too!
Move out!
Wait wait
No, stop!
Hey!
Hey, get whoever's in charge over here
Please don't pass the white line!
Densha won't be here!
Shit!
I should have worked out more!
It's okay as long as nobody comes in!
Please don't pull on my hair
Not letting anyone in even when
Densha walks up to the stage...
is that really possible?
We know that's impossible...
But please make it work!
Please don't push!
Today's show has been cancelled!
What the fuck are you guys doing?
What's going on here!?
Densha!
Sit down!
Let me go!
Hey, when is this show starting?
Hurry up and show him to us!
How long are you gonna make us wait!?
We've been awaiting you
Come this way
Densha Otoko
Museum
In a few moments!
I hacked into the system
And you?
Almost there
Open up!
Get out of there!
You're...
Hey!
Long time no see!
What the hell?
Please make them stop!
I beg of you
Oh, it's too late now
Huh?
What's wrong?
Thread for single guys to talk shit
Hey, our thread is showing on the curtain!
It worked
Densha,
we're at the entrance to the special auditorium
We're posting from our cell phones
Our plan failed,
but everyone can see what we're saying
Post up, everyone
This is being fed to the auditorium?
Is Densha reading this too?
Densha
Your buddies came to the auditorium
just for you
We wanted to make it so
nobody would be here when you came
We're sorry, Densha!
We all wanted to protect you
but I guess we're just otakus, after all
We couldn't do anything
We know your situation
It's for Hermes, right?
Do we have no choice but to chew our
fingernails and watch you embarass yourself?
I hate myself for being so powerless
Please everyone
Go home!
Guys, just because you see who he is...
What's that gonna do
He's just an otaku
You'll only be disappointed if you see him
It's useless to say anything to these people...
who are poking fun at Akihabara
I just hope that people are considerate
and won't look at him when appears
Why does Densha have to deal with this?
He just wants to be with the one he loves
Their relationship will be ruined
Leave him alone if you really care about him
I'll go up there instead of Tsuyoshi-san
What are you doing?
Stop them!
I won't forgive anyone who pokes fun at Densha
I'll beat the shit out of anyone who stares at Densha
I know I can't say the same
but I can't think of anything else to say
Densha, we know how you feel,
but please go away!
Please don't show yourself to us
To be honest, I want to see
...but I won't!
If everyone sees,
those two won't be able to stay together
I'm sorry
We're all so powerless to help
Everyone...
I hate the person who's making money
off of our feelings!
Hey everyone watching this...
you're just doing as he wants!
It doesn't matter what Densha looks like
or how he lives
We all saw how strongly he felt about Hermes
and we cheered him on
Please don't shut off our hopes and dreams!
The legend isn't over yet!
We want to see this story until the very end!
It won't be Densha who gets up on stage...
It'll be me!
In that case, we can all go up there!
Shit
I'll hang on to the curtain
if it'll keep Densha's identity a secret!
Everyone at the auditorium
Let's all get up on stage!
That way,
they won't know who Densha really is!
You guys!
Densha isn't some freak show!
Do you guys have the right
to steal Densha's happiness away?
Just let Densha and Hermes have
a normal relationship!
You don't feel sorry for Densha?
Thanks to Densha,
I was able to take a step forward
I'm sure everyone here
also got something from him
He's risking everything for Hermes
by standing up on stage
How can you stand by and not help him?
Is there nothing we can do?
I believe in the miracle...
that everyone will bring!
That's what the world calls love!
(Title of the end theme song)
You guys...
Thanks...
Hurry up and raise the curtain!
You want to turn your stocks
into pieces of paper?
Open it!
Open it!!
If you reveal yourself
do you have any idea
what'll happen to you?
I do.
I won't be able to...
see
Saori-san anymore
You...
You know full well what'll happen...
This is...
to protect Saori-san
What a show-off
Hey...  What the fuck are you guys doing?
Hurry up and start it!
Raise the curtain now!
Yes
What's going on here?
They did it...
Densha Otoko and Hermes-san...
We wish you the best
We're all rooting for you two
I want to see Densha
but I won't for their sake
No matter who Densha really is,
he's still my hero
Their love story still has
a long way to go, right?
Stay happy forever
I'll find a love like Densha did!
Thank you...
So this is the power of Densha Otoko
No wonder I can't have you
I think I know why...
you're so into Densha Otoko
I lose
Thank goodness
Thank you so much
You're welcome
And Maezono-san...?
He left
He said he was sorry
I see
I saw everything
It made me so happy
Everyone pushed my back
I'll always have
their friendship
I feel very confident now
That's...
This is your black pearl of fate
Unfortunately it's in Tahitian
So I can't read our future
No
I know what it says
Um...
I have something important to say
Will you...
M...
Thanks to the Chinese softsubs,
this took me 'only' 6 hours
Happy birthday Binkley
I wouldn't have worked for free otherwise
Everything but timing done by:
Masakun
Next...  Peru
Everything but timing done by:
Masakun
I love the sound
Special Thanks:
¢ÓKenSin¢Ó (original subs)
D-addicts.com
chiisana_tantei (for the raw)
Miho Shiraishi = the hotness!
Masakun = the awesomeness!
You win, Densha
If you read these subs and enjoyed them,
feel free to let me know
I need to change, too
If you read these subs and enjoyed them,
feel free to let me know
http://www.cornpotage.com
This is the last time I'm doing this...
Grad student at UCSD = no time
Shit, it's him again!
This is the last time I'm doing this...
Grad student at UCSD = no time
My car!
This is the last time I'm doing this...
Grad student at UCSD = no time
I'm eternally grateful for
many, many things
Especially my parents, my healthy body,
my friends, and also...
Cyber Next's stock price plummeted
Especially my parents, my healthy body,
my friends, and also...
No!
the internet, which lets me download
shows like this and watch them
My 10 million in stock!
the internet, which lets me download
shows like this and watch them
Wait!
the internet, which lets me download
shows like this and watch them
All I have left is that...
I'm pretty sure this is the last time
Fuji TV is making anything Densha related
My car, my life...
I'm pretty sure this is the last time
Fuji TV is making anything Densha related
My 10 million yen!
But we have the Miina anime
to look forward to in January
Come back!
But we have the Miina anime
to look forward to in January
I just wonder when...
we will see another quality J-drama
There are things that...
I just wonder when...
we will see another quality J-drama
money can't buy
There is usually one per year
but so far, 2006 hasn't done well
but so far, 2006 hasn't done well  =(
Is this really okay?
There is usually one per year
but so far, 2006 hasn't done well  =(
Speaking of 2ch...
The owner disappeared...
But your company...
Speaking of 2ch...
The owner disappeared...
It's fine.  A promise made is a promise kept.
Speaking of 2ch...
The owner disappeared...
because of all the lawsuits he was facing
Thank you
So there may be no more 2ch...
Was this really okay?
The maid cafe "Pinafore" really does exist...
I worked so hard too...
And the maids really dress like that
I wore this, bought pearls in Tahiti...
I've been there before,
so I'd know
I told you not to suck on your thumb
I've been there before,
so I'd know
I told you not to suck on your thumb
I've been there before,
so I'd know
Off to the meeting we go-
I have to say, I'm envious of this guy
No!
We're going if I say we're going!
I would like a hot secretary as well
Understand?
Yes
I would like a hot secretary as well
I can't hear you!
Yes!!
Oh yeah, my e-mail...
If you want to send me love letters
It's a lovely view
Yup
or even hate mail...
masakun@gmail.com
So why does she not have a ring?
Love and Peace!
9.24.2006
San Diego, CA