I, I'm glad to see you again.
Thank you so much on the train.
Not at all.
Uh.. How do I look?
I think it suits you.
Really?
Yes.
I actually wasn't wearing my contacts that day,
so I couldn't really see you.
S, so you couldn't tell that I was an Ota-
how I looked that day?
Not very well.
I'm sorry.
No- not at all.
All right, all right.
Nothing, it was something else I was thinking about.
Shall we go?
Ok.
Aww, when's Densha Otoko going to be back?
A first date huh?  I hope it's going well.
Maybe he's...or could it be the're...
Hermes...
[Basketball]
[Team Japan: The European Tour Special]
[Tezuka of Team Japan]
[Will his fractured leg keep him out of the game for good?]
[out of the game for good?]
ID: Densha Otoko
I just got back.
Densha's back!
He's back!!
Do you know how long I've been waiting?
Hurry up and tell us how it went!
Tell us the details.
I'll tell you what happened, as I relive it in my mind.
The Train Man
[We were supposed to meet at the station at 7.
I got more and more nervous as the time passed.
7 o'clock rolled by and still she wasn't there.
It was 5 after, when she arrived...
There's a lot of people out.
Weekend's are always like this.
I was incredibly nervous,
just walking beside a woman.
When I tried to walk like normal,
I kept leaving her behind.
Trying to match her pace,
I think I was walking all stilted.
And the thing is,
she looked even cuter than last time.
She actually did dress up for this.
I thought it would look odd, a guy like me,
and a girl like her being together.
I was so worried.
She's so much taller than me too.
I thought everyone around us was staring.
There were just so many people,
and my pace was all off.
And it was then when I turned back for the third time...
It's ok.
I'm holding on.
I'm sorry.
Uhh..  no no.  It's ok.
Why did you let go?
Let her hold on to you.
I'm holding on, I'm holding on,
I'm holding on!!
Hermes, you rule!
Shall we go?
Ok.
This store has a nice atmosphere doesn't it?
I like it a lot too.
Do you have any recommendations here?
Today our-
Um-
I'd recommend the guinea fowl with grilled seasonal vegetables,
the rock-salt baked Iberico Pork,
and also the crunchy potato and ox-tongue salad.
It's what I usually have.
Then I'll go with that.
Ok.  And to drink?
I'll have a vodka tonic with grapefruit.
And I'll have a...
vodka tonic with kyohou grapes.
Ok.  Your order will be here shortly.
Uh, is there something wrong?
I thought you wouldn't drink.
Oh, I'm sorry.  You didn't have to join me.
No, no.  I like a bit of alcohol, so it was actually good.
So everyone, this is what is date is like?
This is a date?!
Densha's so without guile,
it's so easy to cheer for him.
Oh man... Hermes is such a nice girl!!
Raaawwwk!
And the conversation?
What did you talk about?
We talked about a lot of things,
but I was so nervous I don't remember.
I think it was mostly about what happened on the train.
But it was around the time we finished eating...
Yamada-san, do you go to stores like this often?
It's only recently that I became interested in restaurants.
Really?
I often go looking for good stores like this
with a friend from work.
I see.
Then, have you been to the Taillevent Robuchon?
Yes.  It's now called Joel Robuchon isn't it?
J, J, Joel?
How about La Tour D'Argent?
The duck there is great isn't it?
You seem to know a lot of good stores.
Not really, I've really only heard about them.
My friend recently got a new boyfriend though,
so I haven't been able to eat out like this for a while.
So I really enjoyed being with you tonight.
I really enjoyed being with you,
I really enjoyed being with you.
Going good there, going good~
Man, it's going so well I'm getting jealous.
But it was then that it happened...
So what do you do in your free time?
Uhh, in my free time?
Yes.
Yay! You fell for it!
It was a joker.
Yamada-shi, smile!
Congratulations!!
I do a bit of surfing on the net.
Wow, that's wonderful!
I've heard it's really hard.
It's not really, if you get used to it.
So how long have you been doing it?
Around 5 years now.
Then you must be an expert by now.
Is there some trick to it?
How you position your fingers...
I thought it would be your stance.
Your stance has nothing to do with it.
I can do it lying down.
Isn't that really hard to do?
I also go to the beach a lot,
but I've never seen anyone riding lying down.
Huh?
I really admire anyone who can surf.
Surfing...
What should I do?
Umm...
Any ideas?
That's a pretty tall order...
Asking us about a healthy outdoor sport is really pushing it...
Yeah, it must be really hard seeing her smile
when she says that.
We later left the store and headed for the station.
I'd been running these scenarios through my head where
we'd head to the next store,
and decide what nicknames we'd use for each other.
So it hurt to think of leaving her for the night.
I was feeling miserable.
"I'd like to see you again."
I wanted to say it, but I couldn't.
So we walked in silence to the station.
I think that time, I was able to match her pace.
Usually,
I think people would ignore what happened on the train.
I don't know about that.
But you helped me.
I'm still not sure what I did was correct.
Even if I hadn't done anything,
that man might have done nothing further.
What you did was correct.
I'm really thankful for what you did.
You really are an honest person.
I know that now, after today.
That's not so true.
With you here, I'm not afraid of riding the train.
Um.
The next stop's mine.
Thank you for today.
No, no  I should be thanking you.
Good night.
Um.
I'll call you.
It came out on impulse.
I don't know whether she heard me,
but I thought I saw her nod.
It's like some teenage drama.
This goes way beyond my imagination.
What's this water coming out of my eyes?
Salt water?
Why...?
So, did you call her?
No, not yet.
I don't even know if she heard me.
So is this the end?
This is the end.  If she liked you, she would have called.
Can you let it end?  What does your heart tell you?
It's late.  You should think about it properly tomorrow.
It's been an honour knowing someone
who's gone on a fancy date like you have.
It's all down to how you feel.
What are you saying after all that's happened?
You're calling her tomorrow.
So how was it yesterday?
Was he like Tom Cruise?
Well...not completely unlike him.
Oh, so not even close huh?
So you're done with him right?
Hm?
Well of course you are.
If you see him after this, he'll think you like him or something.
Really?
Definitely.
Did you already say you'd see him again?
That's good.
You have to be careful around men.
How about you?  How is it going with your new guy?
That's it, back to work.
Back to work?
Wow, but she has an awesome butt.
I took you to dinner just once,
quit acting like you're my girlfriend.
It's annoying.
It's annoying, how you phrased that.
Ok.
I don't want to see you again.
You're ugly.
It's ugly, this cartoon you drew.
Ow, my finger, my finger.
What are you think of?
What are you thinking of, drawing a pictures like that.
I'm sorry.
I thought it would be relaxing.
You're pretty good.
I'm actually really tired.
You should be.  But we're live here!
Everyone's come out for you!
Thanks everyone!
Yay, hooray!
Let's get this going!
Sorry I'm late.
You should have quit work early.
I left Nagoya last night,
and stayed up all night to keep this spot.
That's incredible.
Here we go!
Our first caller is in need of advice.
I'm an anime otaku that loves Akihabara more than anything.
I really like this one girl, but we have nothing in common.
Is there hope for someone like me?
He should be ashamed, not having pride in being an otaku.
It takes time before you stop caring how people think of you.
I like people who can lose themselves in a hobby.
How about people who have posters
and anime figures all around the house?
That's a bit of a problem.
It'd be ok if it was games though.
I'd like to learn how to play them too.
Ok then, here's a question for you.
Karin, do you think you could date this Otaku?
My friend was saying,
and this is really a friend we're talking about,
but she was saying...
She was saying...
Repulsive,
gross,
annoying,
Do your worst...
Impossible, totally wrong.
For country and emperor.
Repulsive.
Gross.
Annoying.
impossible, totally wrong.
See you next week!
I'm back.
Oh, you're here.
So what's wrong, you look down.
Nothing.
Where's Mom?
She's taking a bath.
No peeking.
I won't.
Did anything happen?
Not really.
Actually I was wondering,
how did you and Mom start going out?
What is it, all of a sudden?
I want to know too.
Anyway you look at it, you two have nothing in common.
That's a little harsh don't you think?
It's true I had to call her everyday,
to try to get through to her.
You called her everyday?
Yep.
Well, I was really shy back then,
so I always hung up before I couldn't say anything.
Silent phonecalls?
That's not all.
I hung around her house, guarding her for 3 days straight.
I also bullied her boyfriend, until he got depressed.
Yeah, I did a lot of things back then.
You were a stalker?
I obviously asked the wrong person here.
You were lucky the laws were less strick back then huh?
Hm?  Wha? Why's that?
How can you say that?
Doesn't it matter how I feel?
Now stop calling me!
Welcome back.
Was it Father?
I'm having some tea.
Ok.
You'll regret it if you date someone your parents don't like.
Are you talking about yourself?
You know I can only teach by example.
You're awfully hard on your yourself.
You could be right.
But you know,
that's why I don't want you to become like me.
Then that's ok.
I don't plan on dating for a while.
It's not ok.
Don't you ever plan on marrying?
It's been two years already.
How long are you going to drag this on?
Isn't it time you got over him?
I know he decieved you, and you were hurt badly,
but it's your fault you didn't-
Stop it.
You don't know what happened.
Then tell me so I do understand.
I don't want to talk about it with you.
Saori?
So how's it going?  I still haven't called yet.
I can't help thinking she'll think I'm a bother.
I know how you feel,
but it'll be rude not calling after saying you would.
The more you wait, the harder it's going to be.
Out of rounds huh?
I'm a girl,
but don't you think Hermes-san is waiting for you
to ask her if she wants to go restaurant hunting with you?
That's too good to be true.
Isn't it?
Is there any chance for this?
I'd say so.
It's the first thing I'd think of.
Everyone's sure things will turn out well.
That's why we're telling you to call her.
Was that how it was.
Then how should I ask her?
"If you want to have good food,"
"come with me."
"I'm not good around women,"
"but how about me?"
Which totally lacks style.
"I want make restaurant hunting my hobby too."
Something like that?
"If you're looking for a restaurant friend,
do you mind if it's me?"
and then see how it goes.
"If you're looking for a restaurant friend,
do you mind if it's me?"  Is that the FA?
Final Answer!
All right.
Hello?
This is Yamada calling.
It's her.
Thank you for yesterday.
I had a lot of fun too.
What I said yesterday on the way back...
I remember.
I was wondering if you were going to call.
Oh really?
I called t, ttoday because,
I r, r, remebered you said you liked to look for restaurants.
A, a, and, if it's ok with you,
I was w, w, wwwondering
W, w, w.   W, w, w.
w, would you mind it if I was your friend for that?
Hm?
I.. Uh..
You seemed to find it hard to ask your friend,
so if it was ok that it's me...
Oh...
that'd be ok.
Huh?
I'd like it if you would go with me.
D, does that mean?
It's ok?
Yes.
I actually wanted you to ask me that yesterday.
I was leading you that way from the start.
Yamada-san?
S, sorry.
I didn't realize.
Don't apologize.
I thought it would be fun if you could go with me.
That was all.
I'd be an honor.
Next time it's my turn to look for a store ok?
So how does next Sunday sound?
I'd love to!
Uh.. Yes.
So see you then.
Good night.
No waay!!
I'm seeing her again!
Yes!!
[Densha Otoko passes to the next level]
Yes, yes!
I think I'm going to cry.
Densha, you're our hope,
you're our future, you light the way.
They're pouring in.
I can say it here.
I've never gone to dinner with a girl.
When I asked, she asked me why she had to
eat dinner while looking someone as ugly as me.
(Give us the details.  Part 2!)
She says there's a store she wants to go to,
so that's where we're going next time.
Thank you so much.
Everything's moving like clockwork.
Densha Otoko, you've passed beyond my realm...
You guys are pampering him.
Densha Otoko, you don't think for yourself.
Your continued existance
just serves to create more people like you.
There's still flamers on this forum.
Don't worry about it.
People like you are going to be bitter for the rest of your life.
Tezuka: Will he retire?
6 months to full recovery, too late to return to Team Japan
Shanghai
Working late?
Sakurai-san, what's going on?
I forgot some papers.
It's been 3 years since you left Japan isn't it?
You're going to be busy.
Not really.
I might be the manager of store 1,
but the people on site will take care of everything.
I'll probably be bored.
Then how about this?
It's this site with all these single men.
Things are really taking off between this young otaku
and a beatiful office girl.
Just maybe,
we could see the most beautiful miracle in the world.
Densha Otoko
Congratulations!!
If you want, I'll store it in your browser's favorites.
Thank you for your business.
World System, Research and Development Department
Jinnkama Misuzu
Good day.
Jinnkama-san?
Yamada?
Yes.
You really changed huh?  It surprised me.
Really?
I'm eating lunch with you aren't I?
It really surprised me too.
I didn't think you'd do that in an elevator.
That was just a greeting.
A hug, a hug.
Hug?
I'm warning you, but that's a secret.
He's in the opposite camp as the manager,
but it looks like he's moving up in the ranks.
You had it already?
Well yeah.
How was it?
It was really good.
It was so hot.
It really thick wasn't it?
Oh yeah, it was so juicy!
I should have ordered the Tonkatsu Meal too.
Huh?
Oh, you were talking about that?
What did you think I was talking about?
Eat with this.
So?
Did you already do that girl you were after?
No yet huh?
Don't ask-
No matter how you change on the outside,
at the most, you'll probably just be a good friend.
Do you think so?
Things could be different if you had an interesting hobby.
Thanks for lunch.
A interesting hobby huh?
I really admire anyone who can surf.
There's one.
You already made plans?
I thought it would be bad asking you,
now that you have a boyfriend.
What?  It's my fault?
Yeah.  We're all here because you're bringing your boyfriend.
I didn't call you.
Is that so?
You're not serious are you?
What's this about?
This has nothing to do with you.
Aren't you being mean?
Then let me meet him.
I want to see if he's really the guy you say he is.
You're so loud, I can't-
Dad, my brother's broken!
Back, right.
Aoyama-san
Hello?
Sorry for calling so late.
There's someone who really wants to meet you.
Eh?
If it's ok,
can we both meet you at the restaurant next time?
Oh.. I see.
That'll be ok.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
I'll see you next Sunday then.
Ok, then.  Have a good night.
Wait...
This is a problem isn't it?
There's someone who wants to meet you,
but can we both come?  Now what?
There's no reason to refuse.
This one's hard to call.
It could be a guy too.
You're right, it could be a guy.
There's still time.
Call her and tell her no.
Call her and cancel.
I can't do that, she'll hate me then.
Refusing her also takes courage.
If it's a girl then she could be there to check you out.
A woman has a really critical eye.
Don't freak me out.
I'm getting worried.
Think of it as a trial.
You're going to get caught out for sure.
That's the plan all right.
Don't think too much about it.
It could be fun.
It doesn't help to think negatively does it?
If it's a guy, then at most you have a miserable time.
What if the friend finds out you're an otaku?
What then?
You're never going to see her again.
Densha, what do you want to do?
I don't know.
If I refuse, then I'll look bad.
If I go, then I'll probably mess up.
What should I do?
What are you doing, depending on a bunch of
immature forum members?
To them, you're just a toy.
You're so dim you can't see it.
You're going to be used, and make a fool out of yourself.
Get lost already.
Get off the pulpit, you fool.
We're all honestly rooting for him.
Find some other forum to flame at.
Ignore anything this guy says.
Getting back on topic,
why don't you settle for being a friend?
I think that's good enough.
You're aiming that low?
It's part of being an otaku.
Dating her is going to be tough.
Even if she hates you for it, you should refuse.
I agree.
Don't try to handle too much.
Densha, how do you feel about her?
I'm too scared to say.
What'd I tell ya?
He's a total loser.
If you have time to help a loser like him,
use it to deal with society.
This is that guy from before.
Ban him forever.
I was annoyed with Densha's lack of decisiveness too.
Don't listen to them.
Is there any point to this board?
This has nothing to do with you.
Densha, you're our hope.
If you're not going to support him, get lost.
Even if we do support him, and he does succeed,
nothing changes in our lives.
Densha needs us.
Ok then,
can you take responsibility for what you tell him?
If something goes wrong,
you're just going to slink away.
You guys see a part of yourselves in Densha,
and are just enjoying the ride.
What's important isn't the result,
but the what you learn through the process.
To be honest, I don't think I could take responsibility.
Everyone calm down.  Densha gave us all strength, didn't he?
That's just a delusion.
This loser doesn't have that kind of power.
More to the point,
this whole story is probably someone's delusion.
People like you who have no faith, will forever stay single.
Gullible people like you will also forever stay single.
Is there any point in a bunch of losers
trying to do something together?
This is as far as this ragtag group can go.
Is there nothing we can do?
Hopeless single men really turn me off.
Men are about heart.
If that's what you think then your heart's gross too.
We're all just a bunch of ugly losers.
So you finally realized.  Took you long enough.
This is really dumb.
I'm leaving.
What's this droopiness I feel?
It's time this forum closed.
Wait a minute.
5 seconds to destruction.
Bring it on.
I've had enough.
Stop it already.
I'm sorry everything got this way.
I was depending on you guys too much.
I'll think about this on my own now.
About what I really want to do.
I need to answer that for myself.
So where's your boyfriend anyway?
He should be here soon.
You're late.
Sorry.
He's cute.
Here, sit down.
Your boyfriend was Keisuke?
Is it wrong?
How can you ask me that?  He's my-
He doesn't belong to you either.
He's seeing both of you?
So the reason you didn't want to come was
because you were meeting Keisuke?
I guess.
So you two are really going out?
What are you talking about?
Don't pretend you don't know anything!
You cheater!
I have no idea what's going on here.
But you were seeing Kaho weren't you?
I was asking for her advice.
Advice?
I was thinking of working for Sakurai-san.
Then make it clear that you're only seeing Saori.
You can't do it?
That's impossible.
Well then someone's gotta do something about that.
Keisuke's my brother.
Huh?
Keisuke, are you ok?
Not really.
Brothers, you mean like family?
Yes.
You look alike!
You said Sakurai, but is that Kazuya you're talking about?
He's coming back to Japan.
Tokyo's night sky's filthy.
Densha, how do you feel about Hermes?
Please stop.
Stop it.
What?
I, I, I'm telling you to stop.
Applause for our brave forum member.
You did good.
You've definitely leveled up.
What if the friend finds out you're an otaku?
What then?
You're never going to see her again.
A women has a really critical eye.
You have Otaku written all over you.
From top to bottom, you're pure Otaku.
You can leave my stuff alone.
What you did was correct.
Long time no see!
He should be ashamed, not having pride in being an otaku.
Gentlemen, would you like to write your wishes for this year?
I'd like to get transferred to a different division at work.
That's not the type of thing you're supposed to wish for.
[I'd like to get transfered out of sales
Yamada Atsushi]
What does your heart tell you?
Densha, what do you want to do?
[LOVE]
It's been three days since Densha left...
All because of someone's big mouth.
This board's sure gone quiet.
If that's all it takes,
he wasn't going to get far anyway.
That goes for me too.
It's been a while hasn't it?
Densha.
I'm going to see Hermes and her friend tomorrow.
Based on your recommendations,
I've decided to wear a cutsew and jeans.
What's a cutsew?
These past three days away from the forum,
I've had a chance to really think.
What I found was how I really felt about Hermes-san.
The more I thought about her, the more anxious I got.
I hardly know all of you,
but you gave me courage.
Both Hermes and this forum
have become a part of my life.
I know that now.
I don't know what's going to happen tomorrow,
but I can tell you this;
I'm glad it was you.
Thank you!
I'm going to ask you again,
but do you love Hermes?
[LOVE]
Yes I do.
I think of her all the time;
both in my dreams and when I'm awake.
In my dreams and when I'm awake...
....Tezuka, Tezuka, Tezuka...
Mom!  We're going to rehab!
I'm heading out.
You can leave my stuff alone.
Saori.
Kaho, you're early.
A little.
Yamada-san?
Hi.
This is my friend, Sawazaki Kaho.
Pleased to meet you.
We've met before haven't we?
Next Week
This piece of fiction was based on a true story.