What happened?  You look angry.
You've been played by that guy Yamada.
That bastard...
has been writing about you on the Net.
He wrote about the day you met him, and your trauma.
He's been laughing at you, having a great time.
Oh, no.  It can't be.
What a bastard.
He totally stabbed you in the back.
Look.
The stalker, Mom and Dad's divorce,
and other private things...
It's here for the whole world to see!
Stop it!
That's not all. He fantasizes about you
in some twisted kind of way.
Saori, Yamada-san is at the door!
That bastard.
Keisuke!
Good morning.
Wh-What?
You wrote about my sister on the Net!
What?
Keisuke, stop!
Let me talk to him.
I just heard about the board.
Did you really write about me there?
W-well..That...
So it was true.
A-actually, that's the reason I'm here-
Did you enjoy it?
What?
Joking and laughing about me...
..did you enjoy it?
That was never my intent.
I went on that board because I had no idea
how to date women...
I don't want to hear it.
I was a fool to believe you.
Please...
don't come here anymore.
Wait!
You and my sister live in two different worlds.
Wait, honey, stop!
It's not like I dated her.  We were just talking.
You okay?
No, I'm not okay.
Dumb question.
SHUT UP!
It's fixed!  It's fixed!
Densha!
I'm back!
I've been completely rejected by Hermes.
This time, it's really over.
What, what?  What happened?
Details!
Translated by Densha-lover
Timed by Sirynx77
Special thanks to chiisana_tantei
for providing the episode raw file.
I told you not to tell her about the board!
It's what he decided to do, it can't be helped now.
I should have stopped him!  Stupid me!
So the reason she rejected you is
because you told her about this board?
She already knew about it by the time I got there.
Somehow her brother found out and told her.
She found out BEFORE you told her?
Damn the brother!
Who would have guessed someone that
close to her would know about us...
Well, even a junior high school kid
like me is in this chatroom...
Who made this board so popular?!
It's all of us, honey...
Sorry, Mom...
Does that mean Hermes is reading this right now?
Wow, just that thought made
me sit up straighter!
Hermes!  Wait, I need to change clothes!
There's little chance of that.
Both Hermes and her brother
seemed offended by this board.
If they have that kind of bias,
there is nothing you can do.
I'd say that's a pretty normal
way for girls to look at us...
That's a relief!  But also a shame...
Well, this way, at least we can keep writing
the way we normally do...
Why did she reject you
without even looking at this board?
I'm sure she was shocked that I was
talking about her without her knowledge.
She wanted to end it
without listening to my excuses.
So if you just clear up her misunderstanding,
things will work out, right?
That's what you were planning
to do in the first place!
Don't give up now!
Keep talking to her till she understands!
Time to go back to Hermes' house!
I can't.
Her brother told me that Hermes
and I live in different worlds...
..meaning I have no business dating
a girl like her.
Even if I could somehow get her to
understand about this board...
Satisfying her to the point where
we could be in love again...
..is impossible.
I thought all I had to do to go out
with her was stop being a nerd, but actually...
It's painfully clear to me now that making an
effort for her not to hate me...
..is not the same as making an effort for her to like me.
She told me not to come near her anymore...
..and I think it has finally sunk in.
She and I...are finished.
Hey!  Are you ok with that?!
Don't give up!  Keep trying!
We're still behind you!
Ok, you've done enough.  You were amazing.
At first, I made fun of you. You were so hopeless
when it came to just calling her to say "thank you".
That made me feel like we all had to support you...
...but you are way ahead of me now.
If a guy like you thinks it's really over,
I guess you are right.
You really were amazing.  Good job.
I'm sure that our words don't mean anything
to a brave guy like you.
This time, it's more complicated
than just a little lie...
Well, don't worry.  You will find someone else.
No, no!  I can't accept this!
Densha, welcome back to the fold.
Densha!...the end...
Oh man...I'm just a newbie,
but I was on standby making shelters!
Me too!  Me too!
Come on, try again!
Good job.  You've given us courage.
Thanks to you, I'll probably
fail my exam again this year.
Anyway, just put on some muscle!
This has been like the World Cup!
Thank you! Benoist!
Last Stop!  Last Stop!
I'm sure you'll find
a wonderful person soon!
Don't worry!
I got dumped 15 times in a row!
I'm sorry, Densha-san.
These 3 months are something
I'll always keep with me.
This is probably the last time I'll write here.
I won't forget you guys...
...Thank you all so much.
Nothing to look forward to again.
Matsunaga, Matsunaga, Matsunaga, Matsunaga...
That sea turtle?
Right, but he wasn't just any sea turtle.
He's a totally rich sea turtle!
His family owns a lot of land in Nagoya...
He makes $300,000 a year without working!
Can you believe it?
Talk about finding a diamond in the rough!
Here, here!  Look, look!
Those cool eyebrows, those mysterious bangs,
you can see "heir" written on his face!
You're seriously going after Turtle-boy?
After I get back from Italy,
I promised I'd date him!
Don't you have any pride?
Of course not, pride went out the window
when I turned 30!
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Saori, you're never late.
Here you go, the ticket to Italy.
What's wrong?  Have you been crying?
Something happen with Yamada again?
I've decided not to see Yamada-san anymore.
What?
This time, we're really finished.
What do you mean?
What's wrong with him?
He said he completely lost a fight
for the love of a girl.
Hey, is it true that Yamada and Saori broke up?
What?  Broke up?
It's not like they were really dating.
What the hell is he doing now?
Don't you know how much effort
I put into stopping you?
Wait...that means she's free!
Time to make up for lost time!
Hey, tell me what happened.
Saori won't talk about it.
Listen...can we talk?
You told your sister about the board, right?  Why?
I just told her the facts.
Then tell me what the facts are.
Did I stutter?  TELL ME THE FACTS.
Wow, you've totally changed!
This is the REAL me.
He talked about my sister, making fun of her.
Did you actually READ it?
Why would I?
Unbelievable.  This is why I can't stand KIDS.
What does that mean?
Read the damn board!
What was that?  What did she mean by the board?
Sorry.  Misuzu-san!
On Aladdin Channel...
You will find... How Saori and Yamada...
Broke up, baby...
Serves him right! Yay!
I know it's business, but we're going to Italy,
and it should be a nice change of pace, right?
Sorry, I drank too much last night!
You're late!
Let's go!
Stupid Yamada!  This makes 3 days in a row!
Ok, he's fired, he's fired, he's fired!
Hello, this is Yamada's boss, is he home?
Yes, yes, I expect his resignation..yes, yes.
Oh, someone hung up!
What's wrong, Oikawa-kun?
I...don't dislike Yamada.
Well, whether you like him or not,
you'll need to go along with my decisions.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
Wh-wha-what?
Yes?  Jinnkama-san...why-?
Get me some tea.
Huh?
She dumped you?
How did you-?
Oh, just a rumor...
I see.
Anyway, it's not like she would date a guy like you...
Come on...a nerd and a princess...
we're talking about Beauty and the Beast here.
Oh, I can't stand this kind of sentimental BS!
Take it off!
Huh?
I feel some responsibility for this,
so...this is the only way.
The cure for a broken heart
is to find someone new, right?
What are you doing?
Be quiet. Hold still.
Please, stop it.
How long do you plan to stay hurt?
There are plenty of women like that out there.
No, there aren't!
There aren't any other women like her.
Are you saying I'm not good enough?
Let me show you something!
Hello!
Hello.
Excuse us!
What are you doing?
Oh, just a second.
That looks good!
Ok, I think I understand now.
Due to unfortunate circumstances,
I was away from this board for awhile.
It seems that somehow Densha
has had his heart broken.
That's right.  Oh, I'm sleepy.
There's almost no one left on this board now.
There's no reason to stay, with Densha gone.
Why did you guys let him quit?
He's not going to change if this goes on.
Densha decided it was over on his own.
He developed into a super weapon.
And now he's gone.
I know he's been hurt.
But we were supposed to make sure
his dream of falling in love came true!
Who do you think you are?
We are all fully aware of that.
We have to accept that some
things in the world are not meant to be.
We did what we could.
It's not like I'm guaranteeing we'll succeed.
But I don't want his feelings to linger.
He never told her, did he?
He could at least do that before he gives up.
It's too late.
Densha said he'd never come back here.
This is the only way we have to contact him.
That kind of thinking is the reason we are losers.
If we can't change ourselves,
how can we hope to encourage Densha?
Let's get him back to this board, and
get him to tell Hermes how he feels about her!
This pep talk won't work.
It bothers me too!  But Densha said...
Count me in.
Hey, hey...you're just going to hurt Densha again.
NO!!  Saying we didn't want to hurt him
was just an excuse for us to take the easy way out.
Densha is our ultimate weapon.
Come on, guys.  He's had enough.
Have you guys forgotten what havoc
this will wreak on his life?
Well, if we can't support him, then who can?
Anyone who doesn't want to
support Densha can leave.
You guys...are so crazy!
Back to work, fellas - Cheers!
Let's inject Densha with some "loser guy" power!
Soldiers!  We need a strategy!
Obviously, there is a high probability Densha will go to
Akihabara tomorrow since he is so dejected.
That means we need to scour Akihabara for him.
Densha said that he lives on the Chuo Line,
so I'll wait for him at the station.
I'll make an announcement at the station!
I'll do a live performance there.
I'll go to Central Akihabara and start
yelling "Densha"!
I'll call out for him at 3000 feet!
I'll publish a book about him!
I'll call out for him too!
Then I will buy up Akihabara itself while I look for him.
I'll set traps for him
at other boards to bring him back.
You guys are amazing.  Doing all this for someone else.
I bet if I'd had friends like you around me,
my life would have been more fun.
What are you talking about?  We're your friends too.
Anytime you have a problem, you know you can talk to us.
I haven't left my room in ages, but I'm going
to put up notices for Densha all over Akihabara.
That might just work.
Make sure to get permission!
Ok, I'll get on TV and see what I can do.
Alright!  Let's get him back here!
Time to make those notices.
(Station Names)Inage, Tsudanuma, Funabashi, Ichikawa,
Shin-Koiwa, Kinshichou, Bakurochou...
Dad, who is Densha Otoko?
It's better not to ask.
Oh, it's the Oracle!
You know him?
Yeah, he teaches me all
the tricks on games.
Really?
That reminds me, I memorized the Nambu line.
Let's hear 'em.
Tachikawa, Nishi-kunitachi, Yaho-
Nope! After Nishi-kunitachi,
we stop at Yagawa!
Tachikawa, Nishi-kunitachi, Yagawa, Yaho...
Scary!
And Sunny!
-Pardon me, pardon me...
-Excuse me, pardon me...
[Densha Otoko-San Come Back]
Densha-san, don't give up...
Even if you have a broken heart...
One more time...
Take a look at the board!
Would you like to hold hands?
H-h-here you go.
Ho, ho! How rude! We run into each other,
and all I get is a sigh!
Matsunaga-shi, holding hands with a guy
is a little suspicious, don't you think?
Get out of here!  I have a girlfriend now!
A girlfriend?
Yamada-shi, it's been a while
since we hung out, hasn't it?
[Densha Otoko - Tell her!]
Densha!  Densha!
This is Mina!  See you next time!
Densha-kun!  Too bad that while you're wasting time,
my lethal weapon has reached its target.
Oh! What a handsome man!
Broken-hearted Saori...will be unable to
refuse her mother's strong advice...
I was a little surprised to hear about
your interest in me for an arranged marriage...
I was surprised too.  I can't believe you were Hermes.
I'll make sure and thank Densha.
Thanks to him, you and I will be even closer.
Pardon?
Look over there.
It's hot, isn't it?
What if I fail again?
Wait!  Things have gone so badly till now...
but that just means they will take a turn for the better.
Densha!  Sorry, but this time for sure,
Hermes will be mine!
[Densha decided to end it on his own.]
What are you doing?
Is this...?
Sorry, Keisuke told me-
But I said-
Saori, listen.
When I first heard about this board, I was furious,
and I was going to go tell Yamada off.
Remember, I used to loathe Yamada?
He's such a nerd.
But, Saori...read the messages.  You'll see-
Stop it!  I can't take it!
Saori!
Why did they decide to do a show
here all of a sudden?
Actually, I heard that Takeda Karin
will be a guest on today's show through the Net.
Really?
Only the real hardcore fans of her show know about it.
Why?
Ok, and today we have a surprise guest
which can only be seen here live.
Here we go, for everyone at the studio!
We are now connected live
through the Internet to Karin-chan in L.A.!
Karin-chan!
Hello! How is everyone?
Everyone is fine, fine!
We heard that you are now studying acting in America,
but why did you decide to do this show so suddenly?
I have something to say to someone who inspired me...
Oh, who wants to hear about that?
So who is this guy?
Someone I met on a board.
I've never actually seen his face.
That person saved a girl on a train
from an old drunk, and fell in love with her.
- Wait, is this my-
- "My" what?
Nothing.
What do you want to say to him?
Densha Otoko-san. You gave me the courage to
take charge of my life.
But I believe there is still something left for you to do.
Take a look at the board.  Everyone is looking for you.
Looking for me?
Please, take a look at the board now!
By Densha Otoko, does she mean
that guy we hear so much about lately?
You suck, Densha Otoko!
[Densha, Tell her!]
[Densha, Come back to the Board!]
-All this for me?
- I bet that Densha Otoko is no big deal!
He probably has a face like this!
- Or something like this!
- More like this!
[We're waiting for you in Aladdin Channel!]
[Come Back!]
[Densha Otoko]
[Come back]
[Densha Otoko, Come Back! Benoist!]
[Densha Otoko-San Come Back!]
[Densha Otoko, Come Back!]
[Densha Otoko]
[Densha Otoko! Come Back!]
[Densha Otoko! We're All Waiting!]
[Densha Otoko - We Need You!]
[Densha Otoko]
[Densha Otoko, We're Waiting For You! ]
[Densha Otoko, Come Back to the Board!]
[Densha Otoko Come Back!]
[Densha Otoko! Take a Look at the Board!]
Miss, are you alone?
Yuko-san.
I heard from Ayumi.
I don't think Yamada meant to hurt you either.
Even if he didn't, does that excuse what he did?
I can't forgive him.
No one said you should.
What?
But you could at least read the messages
and find out what he was thinking.
Ayumi read it, and changed her opinion of Yamada.
She said she was moved.
This from a person who hates nerds!
I bet there was something there that
really touched her heart.
[Densha, Tell her!]
Densha, are you reading this?
I was one of the first on this board.
At that time, I was hurt and told
I could never play basketball again, and was desperate.
I was cut from the team, but I've been
rehabbing my leg and I enjoy practicing every day.
One day, I will be back on the court.  If it wasn't for you,
I would have quit.  Now it's my turn to help you.
I have been here with you from the beginning.
You helped me to remember falling in love
with my wife 10 years ago...
We have reaffirmed our love these past
three months, and decided to stay together.
I'm so glad to have met you.
I'm sure a lot of others feel the same.
I'm speaking for everyone when I ask you...
Please, for our sake as well as yours...
Tell Hermes how you feel.
I often go overseas, but I think that it must have been
harder to go to Hermes' house.
After all, there's no JTB (Japan Travel Bureau)
to sell you a ticket to her place.
No one could have told you how to get an invitation.
But you made it, didn't you?
I just couldn't stand it if you quit now!
Densha, in sports, you might need more talent than effort,
but in love, I'm sure that effort is more important.
Think about Hermes,
and don't live your life with any regrets!
Densha, we've pushed you all this time,
but now it's your turn to take the final step.
Don't let it end like this.
I don't think this was your goal.
Hermes needs you too, Densha.
I have shared in your joy as well as your pain.
So when you're hurt, you're not alone!
We're with you!
You guys...
Why are you guys so good to me?
Thank you all for every word.
I'm so lucky to have met you all.
I'm so lucky to have spent time with you all.
I'm...
I'm...going to try...
I'm...going to try...one more time!
Yess!!!
Chief.
[Resignation]
Oikawa-san.
I'm Chief Oikawa now.
Isn't that right, Chief Kuroki?
Yes, that's right.
So you don't need this.
No!  Actually, I have to wait for someone,
and I don't know how long it will take.
Then find your courage.  There should be still some left
from when you went surfing.
Is that okay?
Yes.  Isn't that right, Chief Kuroki?
Of course, Chief Oikawa.
Tuna Cans-Check!  Sleeping Bag-Check!
Change of Clothes-Check! Tuna Cans-Check!
I'm going to call her now.  I'll probably get her answering machine.
But I'm still going to tell her everything!
This is the first time I've heard you sound
so confident about leaving a message.
So this is what it's like to be ready
to fight to the last man!
It'll be fine.  I'm sure Hermes is thinking of Densha too.
Calm down.
[Aoyama-san]
[Yamada Tsuyoshi]
-Hello, this is Aoyama. Please leave a message
- It's been a long time.
P-p-please take a look at the board.
My whole life is written there.
P-p-please.  Read all the messages.
At the end, you'll see a message-
...written for you.
It didn't go exactly as planned,
but I told her to look at the board.
This message is for her.
Hermes-san, after reading these messages,
I'm sure you were surprised in many ways.
I myself feel embarrassed, nostalgic,
and other strange emotions.
But I don't think you'll find any lies here.
I might not know the names or faces
of everyone here on the Net...
but for me, they are true friends.
If there is anything I am proud of,
it would be meeting these great people.
Thanks to them, I never gave up on getting together with you.
They have given me the courage to tell you how I feel.
Tomorrow, I'll be waiting for you at our secret spot.
I'll be there till you come.
Finally, I'm sorry to have written about you on this board
without your permission.  Please forgive me. --Densha Otoko
[Yamada Bicycle Shop]
Ok, I'm leaving now.
Fight to the finish!
Do it, Densha!
Good luck, Densha!
I don't think you'll be a loser anymore.
I have a good feeling about this, Densha!
This is the final train, Densha!
Don't worry about how it turns out.
I'm sure you'll feel better after telling her how you feel.
I'll get a shelter ready, just in case.
Benoist!
Finally, the day has come!
It's been awhile since we got this excited!
A guy can really change in 3 months!
You can have all my positive energy!
Oh, I'm in tears!
I'm not crying yet.
I'm holding it in till you come back!
Densha, we're not just connected through electronic signals.
We're connected through our hearts.
Guys, thank you for these 3 months.
I don't know if it was long or short, real or just a dream...
To be honest, I feel uneasy.
I'll do what I must.
I think the course of my future will be determined today.
But I'm done with my old, dark way of life!
Your support has made all the difference.
One way or another, things will finally be settled!
[The World is Here Waiting for the Two of You]
Thank you.  Ok, I'm heading out!
Going somewhere?
I'm starting a new life.
After getting that divorce,
the world has opened up for me.
That's not what you said before.
I have Yamada-san to thank for that.
Saori,
If you have love,
you can overcome anything.
Tuna Cans-Check!
Good work, Densha-kun.
Too bad you're a step behind me.
You're about to see a complete reversal of fortune.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
I'm Aoyama Yuki.
I'm Sakurai.
And Saori-san?
She's not coming.
But today's meeting is for-
Me.
Oh, that's funny.
P-p-please take a look at the board.
My whole life is written there.
P-p-please.  Read all the messages.
At the end, you'll see a message-