P-p-please take a look at the board.
My whole life is written there.
P-p-please.  Read it to the end.
At the end, you'll see a message...
Today, on my way home after an Akiba event..
an old drunk on the train was harrassing people.
I worked up some courage, and called out to him..
S-stop!
Huh?
I s-said s-stop!
I'm sure my voice was shaking..
I'd never been in a fight before..
Are you all right?
I was so lame..
Guys! What should I do?
The young lady on the train..
sent me a letter and
some cups as a "thank-you"..
How did she write the letter?
Is there hope for you?
"I was moved by your courage on the train."
This sounds too good to be true.
Aren't you just deluding yourself here?
Don't take this guy seriously.
H-h-her cell phone number!
Call her now!
I can't, I can't, I can't!
Start by picking up your phone...
I've got her number, but I can't dial it!
I need more courage for this
than I needed on the train!
My hands are shaking, my face is hot,
my heart is pounding like crazy..
Damn, even I'm getting nervous here!
Don't be fooled.  This guy is playing you..
One thing you should remember.
The girl you like is alone, but..
you have all of us supporting you.
Thank you all.  I'm getting choked up here.
You're so kind, and I'm so lame..
I..want to change!
By the way, do you know
what brand the cups are?
It says "H E R M E S"..
Hey, that's "Erumesu!"
"Erumesu!" Yes!
It's pronounced "E ru me su"!
You mean the same brand as the purse?
I think this is more
than a simple "thank you".
Why don't you ask us for advice
while you're on the phone?
It's not like you have anything to lose!
[You can do it!]
Ok, I'm calling her!
Yesss!
[You're a man among men!]
[Go for it!]
[You're amazing!]
I just realized something..
I got caught up in the momentum
and made plans with Hermes-san, but..
when she sees what a nerd I am,
she'll completely lose interest..what do I do?
Don't worry..you just need
to take care of your looks.
Get rid of those nerdy Akiba
clothes, and you're fine.
Change your clothes, and
you'll change your attitude.
From clothes to talking to her,
we might have to teach him everything.
Alright, let's get him ready then.
Densha Otoko Revamping Project
Let's start with his hair.
Forget blonde hair, but get some highlights.
I think you should let the stylists decide.
Want an impact look?
Go for dreads or corn rows!
Come on, cutting it short will
make the best impression.
Aren't you gonna panic when
the sales people talk to you?
If you think of Hermes..
.you can be a better man.
Um..what do you think?
Actually, I hadn't thought that far ahead..
.as far as dating her..
But..I definitely have feelings for her..
When we meet..
I know I'm going to fall for her..
Of course, she might have a boyfriend..
and if I fall for her, I might get hurt..
Oh, I can't take it!
But..
for a loser like me..even being able
to imagine myself with her..
is amazing. I owe it all to you guys.
Everybody..
Thank you so much.
Thanks..
for thinking of me.
I..
I'll do my best.
I was so nervous..
walking side by side with a woman.
Walking the way I normally do..
I leave her behind.
And she's even cuter than
she was when we first met!
I'm sorry.
I couldn't stop thinking..a guy like me and a girl like her
didn't look like we belonged together.
She's so much taller than me.
Everyone was probably staring at me.
Don't worry.  I'll just hold on to you.
I was surprised, and jerked my hand away..
That was your chance!
Hold her hand!
I'll just hold on to you.
I wanted her to hold on..
I mean..I wanted to tell her
I'd rather she held my hand..
Yes.
Yamada-shi, did you forget..the special edition
Mina DVD box goes on sale tomorrow?
It even has the storyboards for
the legendary episode 7!
I can guarantee they won't last long!
I'm sorry.
I have something more important
to take care of.
I'm really sorry.
Actually..because of a misunderstanding..
she thinks I'm a surfer.
Not a problem.
I'll show you how to get good fast.
Just stand on the board,
and it'll work out somehow.
Ok, let's Google it, and
see what advice we can give Densha.
Thanks guys.  I'll give it a try.
Who cares if you can't surf.
Just remember..
you lied to her.
What's important is that you think
of what's best for her..and make things right.
I'm really sorry..
I..
don't know how to surf.
lied..to you.
Lied?
I'm really sorry..
for lying to you.
I don't think..
I can just stop being a nerd.
Hiding who I am..is a lie in itself.
Stop analyzing it so much.
Everyone has something to hide.
There's no need to hide it.
Being a nerd..is who you are.
She'll see you as being sincere
if you tell her you're a nerd.
Everyone, thank you for your thoughts.
I know it's a crazy gamble..
but I've decided..
I won't lie to her.
I'm..
going to come out and
let her see I'm a nerd!
I'm..
a nerd.
I've been called lame and disgusting..
but that can't be helped.
But..
For me..
This is the only way I know how to live.
I..
didn't want to lie to you.
So..
I wanted you to see me..
the way I really am.
[Jinnkama-san]
Yes?
Where the hell are you?
Here I am working overtime,
and you don't bother stopping by to say hi?
You can still make it.
Get over here.
I'm sorry.  I have something
important to do today.
Huh? Are you actually
talking back to me?
Who gave you permission to
put anything ahead of me?
I really can't today.
I have a promise to keep..
the most important promise of my life.
Huh?
I'm really sorry.
That's the first time
he's ever refused me.
On this board..
I've told you guys everything
about the two of us..
She might see that
as a terrible thing.
But..
without you guys, there is no way
we would have gotten together.
If I hadn't written you guys about us..
I never would have had any self-esteem.
Above all..
I wouldn't have met such wonderful friends.
You guys were always..
right there with me..
That's why I was able..
to make it this far.
I'm proud..
of this board.
That's why..
I'm going to go and..
tell her about it.
I want her to understand..
my feelings for her..
and all your kind support.
Dear Hermes-san..
I'm sure you were surprised in many ways.. after reading..
the messages on this board.
I myself feel..
embarrassed and nostalgic..
It's all so strange.
But..
I don't think you'll find..
any lies here.
And I speak..
for everyone on the Net..
I might not know their names or faces..
but for me..
they are..
true friends.
If there is anything..
I am proud of..
it would be meeting these great people.
Thanks to them..
I never gave up on getting together with you.
I..
have the courage to tell you how I feel.
Tomorrow..
I'll be waiting for you
at our secret spot.
I'll be there till you come.
Finally..
I'm sorry to have written
about you on this board..
and causing you pain.
Please forgive me.
[Densha Otoko]
[Final Episode]
Densha, you've really come a long ways..
I'm impressed even as your enemy.
However..
you'll find there are some walls
that can't be climbed.
This..is the Final Round.
Yes?
Come quick.  Saori has collapsed.
She's been taken to the hospital nearby.
She's calling out your name,  going in
and out of consciousness..Go to her now!
Ok, I'll be right there!
Who was that?
Ok, ok! Come to daddy! Ow, ow, ow!
Here I go!
Saori!
Kazuya-san!
In a hurry?  Hop in.
Thank you.
Translated by: Densha-lover
Timed by: Sirynx77
Special Thanks to pocemit, for providing the raw file
Greetings to all the Densha-fansubbers:
Greyhorse, aviness, OTL & masakun.
Hey, hey! Tonight's special guest..
Sambo Master, will play us a new song!
It's a song to support Densha Otoko
on that A Channel we've heard so much about.
Ok, Sambo Master, let's hope your song inspires
him with courage, wherever he may be!
I don't know your name..
I don't know your face either..
I don't know what kind of guy you are!
But hey, who cares!
The world calls that..love!
When I see some light through my tears..
I'll tell you the things I've kept to myself
If even then our voices go unheard, my brothers..
Until morning comes, I at least want to find someone to sing with..
If you say that wasn't the real you yesterday..
I'll just put it behind us..
The ones who decide our new future..
Are the new you and me..
We'll figure it out somehow..
The world calls that love!
The thing that connects our hearts..
I had no idea it would be this scary..
You and I, together..
Put our past behind us and sing!
Hey, Listen to the Japan Broadcast Radio guys!
They're playing a song for Densha!
That's a good song.
I've been crying a lot lately.
I hope Densha and Hermes are listening.
It's like the song's encouraging us too.
It's our duty to wait for Densha to come home.
Is it possible she hasn't seen these messages yet?
Of course it's possible.
Normal people wouldn't read them.
If she does read this..
I hope..
Hermes, please go to the secret spot!
Stop.
Thank you.
Ok, here comes the climax.
Yamada-san.
This is Yamada.
I'm at the hospital Saori was taken to, but
I was told she isn't here.
What?  Wait, wait, this
has to be a mistake.
She just left the house.
Really?
Yeah, she seemed pretty serious,
and left here in a hurry.
In a hurry..
I see.
One thing..
Yes?
I read the board.
What?
Oh.
I know now you were
serious about my sister.
Yes.
I was wrong to hit you.
I think she'll understand too.
Thank you very much.
I have to go.
So this is the secret spot.
I bet Yamada..
didn't think he was good
enough for you..
and ran off.
Wait, Saori!
Okay..
It's not going exactly
as planned, but..
[Densha Otoko, Come back to the board!]
[Densha Otoko, come back to the board!]
- Hello?
- Saori, I found Yamada.
On the platform at the station.
Come quick.
Ok.
Where is he?
Yamada..
said he wasn't good enough for you..
and ran off.
Saori..
Marry me.
As he was leaving, he said..
I'm leaving it to you..
Make Saori happy for me.
- Kazuya-san...
- Saori...
- Freak!
- Pardon me..
Saori!
Yamada..
said he wasn't good enough
for you and ran off.
Saori..
Marry me.
Aoyama-san...
Kazuya-san..
- Thank you.
- It's nothing.
Yamada..
you take it from here.
Make Saori happy.
I should have just
taken off with her..
This is the real thing!
Are you serious?  Oh my god!
It's so hard!
Wait a sec...
I remember you two!
Oh crap!
That ring!
- Sorry, sorry.
- Watch where you're going!
It's an emergency.  Sorry!
That old dude is running!
I'm not an "old dude"!
Hey, that's my Lanevo!
Damn it!
I'll get you with my Lanevo 2!
What are you doing!
Where are you taking it!
My ring! My cars!
Hermes!
Come back!
Um..
We meet..
at last..
Densha Otoko-san.
Densha, where are you?
I've been glued to the board since last
night, and haven't slept a wink.
You guys awake?
Yeah..
I'm nodding off, but this is for Densha.
I'll wait for him.
Sleepy..sleepy..
I can't. Night.
My heroes are dropping off like flies..I've tried, but
much to my chagrin, I can't stay awake..
I'm trying to stay awake
to welcome him back for the last time.
Oh, I'm dead.
I'm back.
Densha, is that you?
He's back!
It's going to take hours to finish
writing everything..so sleepy..
We know you're sleepy, but
we're dying to know!!
We've been killing time for
half a day waiting for you!
I take the prize with
15 hours!
Sorry to make you wait.
Can I start with the outcome?
No, no, keep that for the end.
Tease us with it, nice and slow.
Announce the outcome at the last stop!
All right guys, let's
go out with a bang!
My heart is beating
out of control!
My whole desk is shaking!
Here comes the biggest bomb this
thread has ever seen, one that will make history!
Ok, here I go.
As promised, I was at our
secret spot the whole time..
picturing myself telling her how I feel.
Then some guy called and told
me Hermes had collapsed.
That turned out to be untrue, so
I hurried back to our spot.
And then, I saw her
there at the station.
How dramatic!
It's like you two were
meant to be together.
What a perfect setup!
We have to thank the guy that
gave you the false info. Good job!
You're welcome.
We decided to go back
to our secret spot.
For a while..
Hermes didn't say anything.
Of course, I didn't either.
And then..
she broke the silence.
I read..
the message board.
I see.
After reading it..
I came to understand how you
depended on those people..
and then..
I found out how you
feel about me.
It made me happy.
What?
I was so happy to find out..
you felt that way about me.
The people on the message board..
are very kind, aren't they?
Yes.
That's why..
I came here so you could tell me..
how you feel in person.
So..
will you please tell me?
Yes.
Yes, yes yes!
Hermes, MOE!
So, does that mean THIS IS IT?
It's time to confess!
The train is on the move!
There's no protecting ourselves from this bomb..
This reminds me of the first time
I completed an RPG game..
This might just be the end of me, guys.
So let me say it.  I love you guys!
I'm going to run through the
city without any clothes!
I'm so pumped up,
I have no words asdlkajfal..
Bring it on!!
For a while..
neither of us said a word.
I..
was so nervous..
I couldn't say anything.
I..I have..
something important to say.
Yes.
When I'm with you..
my whole world brightens up.
All of..
t-the..
time I spent aimlessly..
and the same old scenery..
and even..
my own deplorable self..
Like magic..
everything..
has brightened up for me.
Aoyama-san..
it's because..
you've shined your light on me.
You've given me..
so much..
in my life..
But..
I..
have nothing to give you.
I can't do anything for you.
But..
when it comes to..
my feelings for you..
No one's..
No one's..feelings are stronger.
I..
You can do it.
Aoyama-san, I..
really like you!
Yamada-san..
I..
like you too.
So..
From now on..
will you be with me always?
Yes.
YES!!!!
Thank you.
Always..
please be with me..
Ok.
Sorry.
I..
really..Aoyama-san..
I'm sorry.
I've never been treated kindly..
by a woman.
Now..
I've started crying.
She kissed you!!
After telling you I liked you..
I've fallen for you even more..
Enough! I have no regrets in my life!
Now I've started crying..
I'm crying already..
My tears are shining like pearls.
I'm going to get dehydrated
from all this crying!
I hope my dad doesn't come in
and see me like this!
Spring has come.
Where has it come?
It's come for Densha.
It's come for Hermes.
Benoist to all us losers!
Densha, congratulations.  And to all you guys on
this thread, you're the best.  We did it!
Did you make love to her?  Did you do it?
Densha, you're the MVP this year.
Your hobbies don't matter anymore. The only
thing that matters is that the two of you are in love.
Who cares if you're a nerd, or used to be one of us.
Make her happy, and be happy yourself!
I'm really crying now!
Me too.  I think your uncertainty and trials will turn out for
the best now.  You can make her even happier.
Remembering what happened
is getting me choked up again.
Don't worry, I'm sure I've cried
twice as much as you.
I've never cried this much just
listening to someone's story..
There's stuff coming out of my eyes..
but I have no one to wipe it for me.
Are there really angels like her in Tokyo?
Is this the Japanese dream?
A girl who's cute and innocent?
A girl who'll take care of you?
Where are they? Where are they?
Save one for me! I bet she's the last one!
Here it is, the ultimate weapon!
Wait, no one's there!
My god, am I still alive?
Magic!
You're really cool! Congratulations!
So where's your wedding going to be at?
Densha, do you have anything left to report?
Yes, but it's Mina-time now.
I'll finish up later.
You're making us wait for a cartoon!
Oh, don't do this to us now!
Oh, that's so you.
You really are an anime freak!
Hey, what is Mina?
"Lunar Bunny Weapon Mina"
Look it up.
I can't help it.  I really love you!
I can't believe I led her right to him.
That bastard Anime Freak Densha.
God, you'd think he'd put himself in our shoes!
Teasing us like that.
Next time I see him,
I'll beat his face in!
Ah, I wonder what it's like..
A love meant to be..
destiny..
Stop playing with your cell phone.
Why don't you play with this instead?
A guy like you?  Not a chance!
Stop!  She doesn't
like it, can't you see?
Hey! She was hitting ME!
You ok?
Thank you so much.
I've seen you before.
I thought so too!
Could this be..
destiny?
I couldn't focus at all..
She and I wandered
around for a bit.
After a while, we
came to a park.
And then, we sat on
an empty bench, but..
had there ever been a time that
we were so close to one another?
I doubt it.
Watch out!  Here comes another one!
Out of the blue, here it comes!
It's like a sudden attack
during a cease-fire!
And he's so nonchalant about it too.
I love you Densha!
I got this for you when
I went to Italy on business.
Open it please.
Ok.
This looks very expensive.
Not really.
It's very nice.  I really appreciate it.
Thank you very much.
Not at all.  Please try it on.
Ok.
Thank you.
It looks good on you.
It matches mine.
Guys?
No response?  Like "It matches!" or
"You got a souvenir!"
To be honest, I never imagined
anything like this, so..
We can't keep up with you now..
The enemy is just too strong..
I'm starting to get annoyed..
Does this kind of thing happen in real life?
Well, not in my life.
Gradually, we settled down, and started to talk
about things that we hadn't been able to before.
Like how we became
attracted to each other..
What we was going on in our minds..
We never seemed to run
out of things to say..
Then I noticed
something was not right.
I lost one of my contact lenses.
Really?
Something's been bothering
me..that must be it.
So let's go look for it.
Oh, it's just a disposable,
don't worry about it.
Really?
Yes.
I can't see anything now.
Not even my face?
Actually, I could see it,
but I said..
No..
How about now?
Oh, you sly dog!
Hermes-san, he's lying to you!!
Another bomb! You trying to kill us?
Hold on guys! Am I the only one
that has a bad feeling about this?
We're not gonna make it
through this attack!
Here it comes! Retreat! Retreat!
This time, it's your turn.
Ok.
Not there.
Here.
It was maybe 2 or 3 seconds.
I had no idea anything so
soft existed in the world.
It was the first time I'd
seen her face up close.
I saw myself..
reflected in her eyes.
That's the one!!
Oh, this is too much! I'm dead!
Goodbye!
I can't take it.
After that, she..
she whispered into my ear..
that she was in love with me..
and kissed me again.
My image of Hermes is falling apart!
"in love with me.."
We kissed again and again..
and finally..we even kissed like adults!
Wait, wait..what do you mean
by "kissed like adults"?
Look out! Friendly fire!
That's all.
Guys, thank you.  I'm going
to sleep now.  Bye.
Hey, take it easy!
What do you mean you can't date me?
Well..
Be a man, and say it!
Well, your ankles are not a turn-on and..
Huh?
They just aren't my type!
Are you saying my legs are fat?
Yeah..
Normally, I'd never take a
second look at a guy like you..
I can't believe it's come to this..
Sorry to call you here like this..
Not at all.  Actually..
I wanted to say something first..
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for not listening to
you and being so pushy.
And making it out to be
like I was protecting you..
But that wasn't the case.
I was the one who was afraid of love,
and I forgot what was really important.
No, that's not true.
It's because you were thinking of me..
that I was able to get back
together with Yamada-san.
Really?
I was going to tell you, but you
probably know the whole story already..
Congratulations..
Hermes-san.
Tsuyoshi, don't leave
your figures here..
Tsuyoshi, sit
down right now!
Mathilda-san!
What are you talking about?
Oh, hi Mom. You sound just like her!
(Tsuyoshi's mom is Toda Keiko, Mathilda's voice!)
I have something to say.  Sit down.
Actually, mom's pregnant.
That's right!
Congratulations!
How did that happen?
On our once-a-month sleepover..right?
Yeah..I really went all out.
At your age..
Watch that tone..
What should we call her?
Oh it's a little early for that..
I was just thinking..
if it's a girl..
how about Mathilda?
That's perfect!
I like it!
How would you write that
in Chinese characters?
I'm sorry..I'm a little late..
Hermes just mailed me saying she wished
every day was Sunday. I'm so happy!
Sorry, but take that to the Couples Board.
You're finished here.
We don't have time to
listen to your bragging.
You'll need to leave before this
thread gets 1000 responses.
Is it my imagination, or
is everyone being cold?
Densha, listen up.  You aren't a single loser anymore.
In other words, it's time for you to graduate and move on.
We've decided not to
watch over you anymore.
I know it's hard,
but it's time to say goodbye.
But I don't want to say goodbye.  I'll drop in
every once in awhile.
So please don't be so cold.
Stop your whining.
If you stay here,
you'll be a nuisance.
This thread is only for single losers.
You don't belong here anymore.
But why?  Aren't we friends?
I'm going to miss all of you.
We are friends..don't you get it?
It's time for you to take the next step.
You're not alone anymore!
Be strong! If you can't
protect Hermes, who can?
Ok.
I'm moving on.
Glad to hear it.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
We've got 300 responses
to send you off with.
Ok, this is it everyone.
Densha's graduation!
Densha, I've realized something watching you.
I can't just be a fan.
I'm going to hit the field, and
have a relationship everyone will envy.
All you guys..Benoist!!
I always thought "Hermes MOE~" but this time
you're the one who impressed me, Densha..
but I'm not going to lose to you..
I'm done with loose socks..time
to switch to a pantyhose fetish!
Last stop, last stop.
I wish you guys all the best.
I'm going to keep at it with my regular job.
The train bound for happiness
leaves from platform 2.
We only have 200 responses left.
Densha, you taught us that
men are more than their looks..
You're the real deal.  Ok, just testing.
Thank you.
Densha and Hermes' jumbo jet took off..
because you guys were there
to refuel and maintain it..
I'm so glad I found you
guys on this thread.
I liked the frank and honest
way you came across..
and rooted for you.
Young man, live
your life to its fullest!
Even a guy like me could
protect Hermes from a drunk..
but you're the only one for Hermes!
This is no "miracle". You won
her over with your own strength!
Hurry up and get yourself
to the Couples board.
I'll have the most encouragement if you
never have to come back here again.
I know that sounds corny.
I hate you Densha! And..for wishing you
both happiness.I hate myself more!
Damn! We're down to
100 responses. It's too early!
I think everyone wants
to thank you, Densha.
This is your last chance, guys!
Good job, Densha.
I dropped my studies to root for you..
which sucks when I think about myself now..
but when I think about these three months..
I'm sure I got something important in return.
I'll definitely pass my exams and enjoy
life on campus now.  I love all you guys!
Me too.  I love all you guys!
I've been called a
freeloader and a slacker.
This is the first time I've
gone all out for anything.
Densha, as your legend grew,
I know I was at least a part of it.
That might be going overboard,
but I'll leave it at that.
These 3 months I've spent
with you guys..It's been a blast!
Everyone put down your weapons!
The Communications Op of the 8th Infantry
Unit will now return to camp.
I'd like to express my happiness to all
for getting back safe and sound.
Densha, I salute you!
Densha, I'll see you
again on this thread.
Only this time, you'll be helping someone
else out who will be as lost as you were..
I'm not saying goodbye.  So long..
and the same with all you guys!
I really like how you come across.
The fact that you're so pure.  And above all,
the way you feel about Hermes..
I might not be like you, but
I'm going to take care of my girl too.
Densha, after getting to know you, I realized
there is more to guys than just looks.
My guy is no model, but he's very kind.
I realized that when we
were cheering you on.
I appreciate you showing me that.
I should be the
one thanking you.
With a tiny spark and great courage..
and maybe some butting into your personal life..
in addition to your effort and growth..
we've witnessed a miracle.
You be sure and take care of her.
Thanks to you, Densha..I've gotten back
in a relationship I had almost given up on.
Thank you for everything.
I guess it's time to say goodbye.
I guess while I was rooting for you,
I kind of fell for you too.
Enough to take away your virginity.
I want details on your future
with Hermes.
I'm going to miss you.
I hope we can meet somewhere.
Looking forward to a new day!  Bye!
While watching over your relationship,
a lot of things have happened in my life.
The biggest thing was getting married.
Thanks to you, my marriage is even stronger.
I really want to thank you.
I'm so proud to have met you.
All you guys..
I'm so..
proud of you too.
When I first saw your announcement,
I was very glad to have started this thread.
Not necessarily just because you were
the first we helped to get in a relationship..
I think you've brought a smile
to the faces of many people here.
Densha..
You guys..
Good job.
These 3 months have been great.
The time I spent here felt more real
than in my everyday life.
As time passes, memories fade..
and this thread will disappear one day.
I don't want to forget what happened here.
Real life is full of hassles..
but it looks like there are
a few good things too.
The time I spent with you
allowed me to realize that.
One day, I hope to see what you see..
I'll just do it at my own pace.
Meanwhile, enjoy yourself
in the couples forum!
I was gone for awhile..but somehow
I was able to see you make it in the end..
You were completely lost, but thanks to the advice
on this forum, you've become a great man.
Densha..
don't you ever let go of her hand..
no matter what happens.
You're going to have many experiences now..
When things are going badly..
think back on this board.
What you've accomplished..
What you've been told..
And finally..what feelings you had
that drove you to get together with Hermes.
I pray for your happiness.
And to all you guys..for these
precious moments..
Thank you..I can't..damn!
I can't stop crying!
I really want to thank you guys.
I'm so happy..you've given me courage..
I appreciate everything..
I'm overwhelmed with different feelings..
I..
won't forget you guys.
You guys..
I love you all!
Me too!
I'm glad there are no hard feelings..
I'm crying more here than
I would at a real graduation!
50 left..Everyone prepare yourselves!
So this is the last
thread for Densha..
Oh, this hurts..it really hurts..
What are we supposed
to do tomorrow?
If you get married, let us know.
We wish you eternal happiness.
Stop writing, guys..that way Densha
will never leave us.
Oh, I know that's not possible..
At least we won't have to listen to
what a great thing you guys have going..
965.  In the end, you were our inspiration..
966.  Densha, I love you!  Don't go!
967.  It's almost over!
968.  So this is it..it's just not right!
969. Why do I cry so much
for someone I've never seen!
970.  The days without Densha
are about to begin..
971.  Your feelings for Densha make me cry too.
Densha is a lucky man.
972.  Densha, you do response #1000.
980.  Is that ok?  What should I write..
982.  Densha, write us a message
with #1000!
984.  It's time to say goodbye.
I can't see what I'm writing through my tears..
985.
I've decided what to write.
It's been on my mind for a long time.
986.  I'm curious.  But I don't want to read it!
987.  That's because after we read it,
we won't see you again!
990.  Farewell, my friends..
991.  It's almost time..
992.  You guys..Densha..
I wish you all the best!
993.  You guys are so kind..
I'm really moved.
994.  My last message..Densha,
let's meet again somewhere.
995.  Please don't forget us!
996.  It's almost over..
997.  If I'd gotten #999, and I had a girl,
I'd confess my love for her.
998.  Here's the whistle
for the departing train!
Congratulations on your graduation.
[Densha Otoko, Congratulations on your Graduation]
[Densha Otoko]
1000.
This thread has some kind of magic.
May the light shine on all of you..
1001. [This thread has reached its limit.
You must start a new one.]
It's thanks to these people that
we were able to get together, right?
Yes.
Good Luck...
Densha Otoko...
Time to go shopping..
- Going Out?
- Yes
I'm going out with Tsuyoshi-san.
- Saori...
- Hmm?
You're glowing.
You too, mom.
Bye!
See ya!
[ Broken Heart Restaurant ]
It's been awhile..
Everything going ok?
We call ourselves a restaurant,
but we only have coffee here.  Idiot.
Then 1 coffee.
I can't believe Misuzu-san left
without a word..
Hey..by Misuzu, do you mean
Jinnkama Misuzu?
You guys too?
Sakurai-san..
- How long have you been there?
- For a while.
But..have you guys been
victimized by her too?
- Victimized?
- You too?
Not just me!
That woman has ruined our lives!
What?
I spent so much money on her!
She and my boss got together..
and destroyed my career plans!
I'm getting divorced now that
my wife found out about us.
I changed flights just to see her!
I bought her a bunch of brand name shoes!
She ruined me!  Me too!  Me too!
Me too!
Ok, let's form a Jinnkama Victim Club!
All right!
Time to find someone else.
Sorry.
Shall we?
Yes.
They were very kind people, weren't they?
[Densha Otoko]
[This story is fiction based on true events]
[ Yess! There will be a special final
episode on October 6!]