Yamada-san?
This is my friend, Sawazaki Kaho.
Pleased to meet you.
Pleased to meet you too.
Haven't we met before?
Hm? Really?
Umm-
I'm just kidding.
You're probably the type who always says yes.  Right?
Oh, you were just joking.
The world isn't that small.
Let's go.
Yamada-san?
Of course.
Hasn't it been a while since we've had to reserve a place to eat?
I thought I'd copy what Yamada-san did last time.
Well, well.  You two seem to be getting along.
It isn't like that.
Yamada-san, I've heard you surf?
Hm?
You don't look the type.
Kaho, that's rude.
Actually-
So where do you surf?
Around here, it'd be Chiba or Shonan...
Then I guess in Chiba.
Then?
No, no.  It's definitely Chiba
Well if it's Chiba, it could be at Onjuku, Katsuura, Ichinomiya...
It's at Utsunomiya.
What, where?
At Uw&*^@#a.
Oh, Ichinomiya.
Uh, right.
If it's Ichinomiya, then I have a friend who surfs there.
You might have met.
Umm- I need use the washroom.
Do you know where it is?
Um, no.
If you leave this store and go straight,
there'll be a set of stairs on your right.
Head downstairs, go left and you'll come an elevator.
Get on that and go to the 6th floor.
Once you get off, there will be a restaurant there.
The washroom is located to your right.
Thank you.
It's awfully far, isn't it?
This is good.
I finally made it.
Really?
Thank you.  Thank you so much.
Not at all.  You're very welcome.
This is good too.
Thank you.
You came back the same way?
Well yes.
You're really an innocent aren't you?
I sometimes might get told that.
What do you want to do now?
I guess one of us can leave now.
Yamada-san, I'm sure it's been uncomfortable for you.
Not at all.
I'm sorry if it seemed that way.
Don't worry about it.
With your permission then...
Saori, let's go then.
Good night.
I'm sorry it couldn't have been a more quiet evening.
No, no.  I enjoyed it.
That was good.
I'll call you then.
I'll be waiting for it.
Well, good night.
Good night.
The Train Man
Original Story
"Densha Otoko"  by Nakano Hitori
Script:
Takefuji Shougo
Openning Theme
"Twilight" by Electric Light Orchestra
Itou Misaki
Itou Atsushi
Shiraishi Miho
Sudou Risa
Satou Eriko
Hayami Mokomichi
Toyohara Kousuke
Openning Anime Production       Character Design
GONZO                               OKAMA
Director
Nishiura Masaki
So then I returned home on my own.
And that's how it went.
I dunno.
I think you did pretty good.
B.
I wonder what her friend really thought about you.
really thought
He's basically just a boring guy.
Even though you were laughing that much?
Out of courtesy.
Is that what it was.
Just to make things clear, I'd say he was medium poor.
She was laughing a fair bit, so I'd say I made a good impression.
I dunno.
What did the friend think about you and Hermes?
Honestly, you two have nothing in common.
I'm telling you, it's not that type of relationship.
And I'm saying that's he's interested in you.
At least understand him that much.
There were captions right here saying, "I want you".
Around where?
I'm saying that's how clearly he was interested in you.
I'm sure she thought I'd make a good friend.
She was saying "you two seem to be getting along."
I dunno.
All that's left is whether she has a boyfriend or someone she likes.
You there, are you living here?
Yes.
You really do need to know if she has a boyfriend or not.
Keep trying to make a good impression on her.
Call her up again and show her you care.
I'm a girl, but why don't you trade e-mail addresses?
You'll be able to communicate with her more readily.
How about...
"Thank you for today-"
"I'll choose the next store, ok?"
"To make it easier to get in touch,
why don't we try e-mailing each other?"
"Let's exchange e-mail addresses."
How about it?
Her e-mail address...
Isn't he just a pet to you?
Pets can't heal a broken heart you know.
Yamada-san is-
Hanging around him isn't going to fix what happened with Sena.
I know you can't date anymore because of Seno.
And I know I'm partially to blame for introducing him to you-
Wait a minute.
It's not your fault.
But it's his fault that your heart's still in pieces.
It's also my fault for not noticing after all this time.
There's nothing to gain by blaming you.
Take care.
You know,
I think there are a lot of people who wouldn't
think much about a lie like that.
I'm probably not strong enough to handle dating.
That's the type of thinking I hate.
Hiding won't fix anything.
You've got to break out of that shell, and look forward.
Kaho.
It's what Friend A might say.
All right, let's go to the next store!
Yamada Tsuyoshi
Hello?
I'm sorry for calling so late.
I'm glad you called.  I was in a mood to talk to someone.
That was good.
Um...
Thank you for today.
No, no.  Thank YOU.
I'll decide on the next store, then.
Ok.
And...
Hiding won't fix anything.
Break out of that shell and look forward.
You have to take me to the ocean some day.
Argh..umm...that would...
I'm looking forward to it.
Ok.
Uh..um.
Talking like this is great but...
if it's not a problem,
the thing is, cell phones can be used for other than talking and...
I got her email address!!
Densha!
New e-mail
Aoyama-san
I decided to e-mail you right away.
An e-mail came!!
Densha!
I'm looking forward to seeing you surf.
Give us the details.
I talked about this before,
but due to a small error in communication,
my hobby is supposed to be surfing.
Are you going to be ok?
Shouldn't you deny this?
Surfing is... impossible.
Is there really no way?  What should I do?
You should do what you want to do.
I'll look up some hints you can learn fast.
It's impossible for an Otaku.
You'll be fine.  Even I'm going to be getting my driving license soon.
With your enthusiasm, there's nothing you can't do.
If it's just getting on a board and standing, I think you can do it.
All you have to do is look like you can surf.
You haven't decided on a date yet, so I'd say go for it.
Let's all find surfing tips for Densha and advise him.
Thanks, all of you.
I'll try it.
I   am   also   looking   forward   to   it.
Here we go!
Keep your weight low.   Master your ups and downs.
Ups  and  Down...
Don't look at your feet.
You should always be facing where you want to go.
Aloha~
You've got the report properly written.
What are you shaking for?
No reason.
We've just recieved a renewal on the Hikari Sangyou contract.
You're also coming to dinner with us ok?
You did good.
The key point at a dinner with a client is "heart to heart".
Equality between "you and me".
I'm here to make a delivery.
... to better yourself.  Synthesize and...
When you're paddling, keep your back arched.
An early take off gives you time to get your balance.
Hand movements are also important in maintaining balance.
All right.
Wilder.  More Wild.
More, more, more!!
What are you practicing?
I'm not.
What, surfing?
You don't look the type.
So what kind of board are you using?
A long.
Yeah, that'll be easier for a beginner.
Oikawa-san, you've surfed before?
Back when I was in Hawaii, I was pretty famous.
Really?
I was good.
If there's an expert around you, study them closely and learn.
What is it?
Study them closely and learn.
What?
Aoyama-kun, I need to see you for a minute.
Hey, how was it yesterday?
You mean that Yamada Tsuyoshi?
I don't know what you were thinking,
but he's totally NG.
I think even Saori will see him anymore.
Really?  What was NG about him?
I dunno...
He's honest, but 120% the type who'll end as a friend.
He's gentle, but-
He lacks presence?
He's faithful-
but a wash out.
Not bad looking,
but totally forgettable?
Forget it.
Meeting's over.
I have to mail Yamada-san.
[Aoyama-san]
[Subject: Confirmation]
[Is next Sunday at the beach ok?]
There's no way that's going to happen.
Do you think?
I think that company's about finished.
It's just too early.
Yeah, I think I may have gone too far.
What are you talking about?
When to take her to see my surfing.
You can surf?
Not really.  Technically,
I'll be able to surf sometime soon.
Reeally?
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm in serious trouble here.
Serious trouble?
Yeah.
I slept with the Vice President
and his wife found out.
I'm wondering what I should do.
Send!
Wh, wh-.. wait.
[Sent Mail]
[Aoyama-san]
[Subject: Of course]
[The beach is a go.]
Jinnkama-san,
don't send stuff like that.
I can't refuse her anymore.
Show her your lousy surfing and go down in flames.
What should I do?
How's it going?
Good thanks.
Thread for single men to rant.
[Surfing... is waay too hard for a beginner.]
Here's your drink.
It was specially made using a mix of vegetables.
It looks great.
You came here for a reason didn't you?
I wouldn't have come if I didn't.
If it's the owner, he's gone to buy supplies.
So Kazuya-san isn't here.
That was why you came?
There was that too.
Then what?
Have you thought about coming home?
If you can't, just visiting is ok too.
What is it all of a sudden?
Nothing really.
But you should show your face every once in a while.
Saori?
It is, isn't it?
It's you!
Kazuya-san?
I'm so surprised.  You look so grown up now.
You haven't changed a bit.
So what is it,
we last saw each other...
7 years ago.
It was.
No wonder you've changed so much.
Thanks for taking my brother in.
No, no, it was me who asked him.
Enough about that, why don't you relax a while inside?
It looks crowded in there, maybe some other time.
Really?
Then how about this Friday?
We're having our openning party, you should come.
I'll be there.
I'll be waiting.
See you then.
Take care.
...starting up.  Strong and proud
you'll need to be, to fly forth darling~
Facing down but-
Why are you singing along?
We're supposed to be savoring the
glory of Takeda Karin's voice here.
Kawamoto-shi,
Mina's name is derived from "everyone".
In other words, it's when everyone is having fun
that Mina has succeeded.
I can't take this anymore.
Yamada-shi,
I'm borrowing your water closet.
It's, it's, it's
on the first floor.
Yamada-shi?
When the kiss scene with Mina comes up,
can I kiss your screen?
I don't think so.
I'm actually less a fan of Mina, and more a fan of Takeda Karin.
I'm really only a fan of voice actresses.
Sorry.
Gross.
Yamada-shi.  I have something I need to ask you.
What is it?
The pretty female on the first floor...
The only females are my mom and little sister.
My Mom only stays over once a month, so...
She was your little sister?
Kawamoto-shi, your face is all red.
Wh- What are you saying?
I'm only interested in voice actresses!
Once you finish up here, you can head home ok?
[Aladdin Channel: Rant thread for Single...]
What was this?
Rant Thread...
Rulz?
I'm heading out to the beach for my first day of actual surfing.
I'm going to take everything I learned during imagery training
and have at it.
[Will]
That's the way to be.
Believe in yourself and give it your best.
Good luck.
It's going to be fun to see how much you've learned.
Maybe you'll be able to stand on the first try.
All right.
I totally failed.
I don't want to do this anymore.
What happened to all the bravado you showed us this morning?
More like, what are you going to do Sunday?
You're giving up already?
If you work at it, it'll happen.
I tried so many times,
but it was totally impossible.
My geekiness has just been proven to the max.
What should I do?
[New E-mail]
[Aoyama-san]
Is next Sunday
still ok for you?
What should I do...
It's important to know your limits sometimes.
It was good you realized this soon.
Tell her the truth right now, and apologize.
You guys are thinking about this too seriously.
Why don't you make it a joke?
You can't help what you can't do.
I wonder if Hermes will be angry.
Doesn't it depend on how you apologize?
What do you think is the best way to apologize?
I tried, but I couldn't do it.
Just give it to her straight.
That's your style.
She won't be angry even if you don't apologize.
She will be too.
All you did was show off a little.
It'll be ok.
I think she'll laugh and forgive you.
Do you think so?
I'll try a cheerful apology first then.
Densha, aren't you forgetting something here?
You ended up lying to Hermes-san.
If you couldn't surf, you should have told her so from the beginning.
What you did was far from honest.
You've betrayed her.
Lie
Is it really?
It's true that your honesty was your greatest appeal.
Lying could be a fatal error.
Densha's in a pinch!
I was deceiving Hermes-san.
That's certainly true.
But I don't want to keep lying to her.
What should I do?
If you don't do anything, it'll all end with this lie.
But if you can surf in 3 days time, it'll all be ok.
Practice like mad.
If you can make it true, it'll no longer be a lie.
Will it go that smoothly?
It'll be a miraculous experience.  Unbelievable.
Densha,
Give it everything you got!
You've openned my eyes.
I'll make this lie a reality.
We'll go Sunday as planned.
I hope the weather will be good.
Please,
Teach me to surf in the next 3 days.
Please.
In 3 days...
what about work?
There's no problem there.
3 days paid vacation?
During a busy time like this?
Yamada.
Whoa, look at his face...
What, you're leaving already?
Sorry, I have things I have to do.
Where did you meet Sakurai-san?
He was living near our host family.
You were there around 5 years right?
He was like an older brother to us.
So that's why Keisuke's working here.
I thought it'd be good for business having a cute guy like him here.
I'm here just for my looks?
That's a skill too.
It must take even more skill to become a manager like you.
I'm Mizuki Yuuko.  I've just turned 23.
30.
And hardly funny.
Why don't we go to the corner?
Thanks for coming out.
Thanks for inviting me.
Everyone's having a great time.
Hm?  I doesn't look like it.
I'm sorry.
I'm not really used to these.
Then do you want to go outside?
That's odd.  Where is it?
Where's what?
I'll tell you when I find one.
How was it when you got back to Japan?
How was it?
A lot of things happened back then.
Really?
What is it?
Did you hear something from Keisuke?
A little about what happened with a guy with a wife and kid.
Saori!
Over there!
Do you remember?
That was your friend back when you still weren't used to LA.
It brings back memories.
The first day I met you,
you were crying in a phonebooth.
You were in junior high.
I was scared and lonely.
You realized there was no one on the other end didn't you?
But you didn't say anything, and waited for me to finish.
Did I?
Hello?
Wait a minute ok?
Here, it's from your no good cheat of a boyfriend.
If you've got something you wanted to tell him, say it now.
You've been hurt.
I won't forgive anyone who lies to you.
You remembered.
Well yeah.
I'm your caring older brother.
I dated him for 2 years.
He even proposed to me.
We talked about our kids,
and all our future dreams.
I was totally lost in him.
I'm stupid aren't I?
Here.
Here!
I don't think anything of you anymore.
I'm going to become so happy, you'll be jealous.
Saori,
that's nothing.
You rotten bastard.
Did you think Saori could ever like you?
You've got a lot of nerve making my cute little sister cry.
One of these days
I'm coming around to beat you to a pulp
and sink you into Tokyo bay.
Tell him.
I hate you, you pig!
I never want to see your face.
You liar!
You big ugly liar!
Yeah, you idiot, you silly liar!
I hate your guts!
You're really amazing.
I don't think anyone would have imagined it.
That you wouldn't even stand once.
I did all I could.
But I'm still not sure I should try it, knowing I'm going to fail.
I think Hermes will understand.
I think it takes courage to admit your mistakes.
If it doesn't work out, you can cry then.
A long time ago, I lied to a girl and hurt her.
In doing so, I lost everything.
It was only afterwards that I realized how much she meant to me.
I'm regret it now.
And that's why I don't want you to make the same mistake.
It doesn't matter if you can't surf.
Just realize that you lied.
What's important
is that you decide what to do while thinking about Hermes-san.
I'm sorry for the long reply.
Good morning.
I made lunch.
I see.
Thank you.
Be careful.
I will.
Don't try anything too dangerous.
Ok.
A lie...
into reality.
You ended up lying to Hermes-san.
It's true that your honesty was your greatest appeal.
Lying could be a fatal error.
If you don't do anything, it'll all end with this lie.
This is an annoucement.
Due to the storm, there's a chance of lightning.
Please seek shelter in a safe area.
Yamada-san.
It's dangerous.
It's no good in this weather.
Please hurry back.
It's unfortunate-
It's not.
It's not...
It's not unfortunate at all.
I'm actually relieved.
What's important
is that you decide what to do while thinking about Hermes-san.
I'm sorry.
I...
can't surf.
lied to you.
Lied?
The first time we had dinner,
I couldn't tell you that net surfing was
another name for using the internet.
I'm so sorry for lying to you.
So you went out of your way and bought a surfboard and a wetsuit?
You've hurt yourself in so many places.
For every bruise on your body I've caused you worry.
I'm also sorry.
If I hadn't misheard you...
That's why...
it's not a lie.
...and that's how it went.
Thank you as always.
Densha~
Are you hungry?
Here.
Thank you.
(-----Yes----)
(-----Yes-----)     (-----Yes-----)
This is our new list of employees.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
This is Tanaka's profile here.
He's relatively new...
When to take her to see my surfing.
[I'm not crying.  It was fant-
[Densha Otoko, you're amaz-
[Your first time surfing, must-
Densha Otoko!
New Message
Aoyama-san
Subject: Wish you the best at work.
Working hard at work.
Let me mail her right back.
Yamada!
Next Week
This peice of fiction is based on a true story.