C, c, comicke?
This time of year has finally come!
This time we'll be putting out a booth of our own!
B, b, booth?  You mean we're putting out a store of our own?
Uh huh.
It'll be the debut for Matsunaga-shi's original series of character designs.
Yamada-shi, you gotta come out and help us.
Of course, it'd be an honor.
This summer's Comic Kingdom is going to be wild.
Aoyama-san
Sorry, but I got a call on the other line.
I'll call you back.
Did you get back already?
Yes.
That's good.
I was worried because you didn't call.
Oh.. I'm so sorry.
Thank you so much for today.
Not at all.
I'm so glad you were there.
I should send you something to thank you.
There's no need for that.
The cups are enough.
Cups?
Oh, the ones I send before.
Yes, I've kept them stored safely.
You shouldn't keep them stored.
I bought them for you to use.
Thank you, but I don't get much chance to use them.
Then...
Huh?
Say Good?
Say Good.  Is this some internet term I don't know?
Ok, I'll be there.
I don't know either.
Is Densha asking for help?
Say Good.  Call the cryptologists!
Ok, I'll talk to you later.
I just got off the phone.
I'll be going to Hermes-san's place to visit her.
Her house?
Say Good => Go to house.  That's what it meant!!
No wayy!!!
Captain! It's a sneak attack!
We're totally unprepared.
Reply not possible.
YES!!!
Give us the details.
When I told her I haven't had a chance to use the cups,
she told me she'd make tea.
And so she asked me,
"So why don't you come over tomorrow?"
Tea with Hermes' cups?
No waay!
The cups.  So you're really going to use them with her.
Densha Otoko, you can trust me on this.
Tell her you like her tomorrow.
I can't do that.
I'll just have tea and come back.
No, you gotta tell her!
Wait a minute! Her house?
Before you tell her how you feel, you have to worry about
her parents!?
Actually, she told me they'd be gone all day.
He parents are gone?
Parents gone 'till the night.
Yes, yes, yes, YES!!!
Densha, this is the best chance you'll get!!!
It's amazing. You're shining!
It's kamikaze!! Kamikaze for Densha!!!
If you got called to her house, you're already home free!!!
So is this what's generally called coming on to someone?*
Coming on?*
Sergeant... my pulse....it...it's fading....
Steady on!!!  Don't make your mommie cry!
If she called you over when no one else was home,
there's only one thing she's thinking about!!!
Arggh!  I'm getting depressed!
Uh, what's this "one thing" you're talking about?
Densha, you're so dense it's criminal!
If you go to her house, a baby's going to be born!!
I just noticed, but got goosebumps all over.
What, isn't there anyone here who's got into a girl's house?!
I've been rejected a lot of times.
Hold on!  We're talking about Hermes here.
It's too early to say "House = green light".  Don't you think?
I'd go forwards one step at a time.
Go to her house -> tell her how you feel -> t, t, tell...
Uh, I can't go any further, it's too depressing.
Guys!  Don't make me so nervous!!
Relax!! We're getting ahead of ourselves.
You have to first tell her how you feel, and get an ok.
All right! We're going to stay up all night
thinking of lines for Densha to use!!
Everyone, man your positions!
It's not like she has to,
but Mom's buying me a new set of furniture.
She's that happy.
For what?
Because you came back.
She needs to get back on her feet,
and quit interfering with you.
D'you have a problem with that?
Saori's having a hard time with relationships
because of her old boyfriend.
That's why I'm trying to find her a suitable guy.
That's not how it happened.
Saori's been timid around men from before that.
I think it started with you and Dad.
Dad lied to you,
and had a girlfriend behind you back.
And you kept moping around aftwards because of it.
And seening all this happening around her,
don't you think it affected Saori too?
So you're saying it's all my fault?
I didn't say that.
But the reason why she can't handle being lied to-
I know.
And that's why I'm suggesting she try an arranged marriage.
[Anti-Stalker Manual]
Important!!
I'll help you with this anytime.
That's why it's not a lie.
Don't be afraid!! I'll protect you!!
Do you want to go on the journey of life together?
I know I'm weak, but I'll support you forever.
Could you be my girl?*
I like you.  Please go out with me.  Keep it simple!
Do you  w, w, w, w, want to g, go on the
j j ourney of l, life t, t, together?
I know I'm weak... but...do you...want to go on..
That's all wrong!
The angle of your wrists is the most important thing.
Hey!  Do you have a bag that'll fit this properly?
You have to pull down like this.  Down, sharply.
[Tablecloth Pulling Contest]
Your back, you have to keep your back low.
Hey, why don't we try it for real.
Yeah, let's try it.
Found one.
Why can't you do it?
You're Lousy.
Your mother does it really well.
What are you guys doing?
Rolling out!
All companies!
Atten
chut!
Inagi, Tsudanuma, Funabashi, Ichikawa, Shinnkoiwa
Kinnshichou, Bakurochou...
[Application Number 60813-980]
[Region: East "K" 206]
[Circle: LOVE MINA'S ANKLE]
What are you making?
Hey, don't sneak up on me like that.
Is someone coming over?
Uh huh, a friend.
Really.
I'm going on a date with Keisuke.
Don't fight anymore, ok.
With who?  When?
See you.
Have fun.
We've got Kichijouji covered.
I wanted to tell you.
I really...  I really like you.
What is it?
Nothing probably.
Ok.
I will...  I'll make you... happy forever.
Got a have courage!
Yes?
Hi, it's Yamada.
I j, jjjjust got here.
I'll be right there.
Ok.
The Train Man
Original Story
"Densha Otoko"  by Nakano Hitori
Script:
Tokunaga Tomokazu
Openning Theme
"Twilight" by Electric Light Orchestra
Itou Misaki
Itou Atsushi
Shiraishi Miho
Sudou Risa
Satou Eriko
Hayami Mokomichi
Kishibe Shirou
Toyohara Kousuke
Akiyoshi Kumiko
Openning Anime Production       Character Design
GONZO                               OKAMA
Director
Takeuchi Hideki
Story 6
W, what's this called?
A patio.
P, patio?
I'll bring tea right away.  Why don't you have a seat?
Ok, thank you.
A recessed floor...
What happened?
It's an awfully cute diggie you have.
That's amazing.
I stopped using it since it broke.
Your hard disk wasn't broken so I was able to fix it.
You should do regular maintenance to keep it working.
I'll check to see if you can connect to the internet properly.
I'm sorry, and you've only just got here.
I'm boiling the water now.
These are Hermes cups.
They're really just the way I sent them.
I'll borrow these then.
Since we..  When we met...
A Channel
I was actually thinking of replacing it.
Really?
I'm at Herman-san's house right now.
What? Y, you're not looking at it with Hermes are you?
No, I'm hiding it.
Live from Hermes-san's house!! Oh no, not again.
Idiot!  What if she catches you?
Th, there's a cute doggie too.
Shut it down now!!  What do you think you're doing?
But I forgot what my lines were.
Is English tea ok?
Y, yes.
Please choose one of these.
She just brought in these cans of tea.
This isn't good, it's too real.
I guess her household drinks really expensive tea.
It says  BE-NO-IST.
Be no ist?
Don't you read it be nwa?
Benoist. Established in the 19th century,
they provide the finest in food and drink.
Intelligence, thanks for the info.
They cater to the British royalty!!!!
Benoist Tea, yay!!!
Have you decided yet?
I'll go with the Benoist.
They're all Benoist.
Huh?
Um, I'll go with this.
Darjeeling?  I like it too.
Right.
Densha!!  Don't worry about what you're going to say!!
Just tell you have you feel!!  Tell her!!!
How about the timing?
Tell her you like her!!
Is everything ok?
Uh.. actually-
How were the muffins?
Oh, they were great.  I can barely stop eating.
I'm glad you liked them.
Hurry up and tell her!
U, u, u, u, uh...
It's such a nice day out.  We should go somewhere.
Once you leave,
you're out!
You won't be able to tell her where there's people around.
Guard the house!
Don't leave the house 'til you tell her!!
Uh.. I brought a dvd with me.  The Matrix?
Oh, the one we were talking about.
Huh?
Doggies?  Why?
Oh, Quill.  I wanted to watch it too.
Really?
Let's watch it then.
Ok.
So...
The button on the far left, that's for the power.
This one?
Yes.
I'm really bad at using these.
I'm sorry.
Hurry up and tell her.
I wonder what he's doing right now.
Benoist tea...
I need a girl too.
Hurry up and tell her!!
Densha!! Densha!! Densha!! Say it!!!
Tell her already!!!
The next stop is lover's lane, lover's lane.
Densha-san...
It's time to lay your own tracks.
You can do it Densha, tell her!!!
Do it I tell ya!!!!
Hurry up and tell her!!
I'm sorry.
Uh... I..
So...you didn't end up telling her?
I'm sorry.
I just couldn't.  I don't have the courage to say "I like you".
You can't keep saying that forever!!
You like her don't you?
You were invited to her house and you didn't do anything?
You loser!!
Don't tell us you weren't able to get a second date?
Actually that's all set up.
A musical?
You don't like them?
No,
I...think I like them.
If you're free, do you want to go this Saturday?
Of course.  I'd love to.
What, she asked you?
Doesn't that mean she likes you too?
Yeah, she's definitely acting differently lately.
You're invited to her house, then asked on a date.
All things I've never experienced, and all in one day!!
You punk!
Well, Densha won't be needing our advice anymore.
That's right.  Densha's last mission is only to
tell her how he feels.
But if I do tell her, and she rejects me,
then we'll no longer be as close.
And you call yourself a man?!!  Tell her!!
It's going to be ok.
Would she invite you over otherwise?
Generally speaking, there should be no problem.
No need for hesitation.
But we still haven't found out if she has a boyfriend.
Think rationally about the situation.
What gives you any hint there's anything to worry about?
So what if she has a boyfriend.
Tell her now, tell her right now.
The timing's important.  Don't pass up this chance.
I'm really scared.  [dispair]
I'm sorry I'm such a coward.
Are you planning on turning away
from a battle you know you can win?
Think about Hermes' feelings too.
You're telling her on the next date!
Work up the courage and go for it!
If you've come this far, you're not going to be rejected.
Densha, we're all with you.
Work up the courage and pass on to the next Stage!
The next stage.
Hey!
There's a wierd call for you.
A wierd call?
Hello?
Your sister's voice is as cute as always.
Did a blue envelope get there?
A blue envelope?
Yeah, I have it here.
Does the address label have a color?
Yes, it's blue.
No way!  Yamada-shi was chosen!
I was chosen?
That envelope is the entry ticket to Comicke.
The white label is NG, the blue means you won.
So the other members of your household don't get too excited,
the envelope was made to look like normal mail.*
So then Yamada-shi,
See you there!
All right.
Just so you know, they need to confirm the bearer's identity
so you have to come in person.
It'll only take a minute,
so you gotta come out.
Got it.
So when is it?
Saturday.
It's going to be great!
Saturday I have to-
Hello?! Hello?!
What am I going to do?
Comike, the highlight of the sumer and the date with Hermes.
Which should I choose?
Hey Densha,
Are you deliberately provoking me?
Of course it's the date!!
Of course I'd normally go to the date,
but this time there's a reason why I have to go.
And it's more imporant than a date with Hermes?
A convention?
Wait. As another Anime otaku,
you have to understand how he feels.
I totally agree.  If you've ever went, you'd know.
One vote for Comike!
As someone uninterrested in fan comics,
I can't figure out what's going in Densha's mind.
The date comes first!!
As a man, there's no other choice!!
You accepted the date first.
Go for the Comike!!  It only comes once a year!!
The way you're going right now,
you can have the date later!!
Comike!!!
Date!!!
Either way,
this is probably going to be your last Comike right?
That's true.
Once you start dating her, you won't be able to go.
On the other hand,
you should go to say goodbye and make it your last Comike.
My vote goes to Comike.
My vote goes to the date.
Comike?
He'd look out of place at a musical anyway,
what's that idiot thinking?
Were you able to get hold of the tickets?
That's great, thank you.
Yes, I'm sure it'll be fun.
Thanks again.
Hello?
I'm sorry for calling so late.
No no, it was actually great timing.
Um... The thing is-
I was able to get the tickets.
And that's the thing.
Is there a problem?
It's about work.
I forgot I had to go that day.
On a Saturday?
Yes.
But actually,
work can wait.
You've already got the tickets and all.
No, you should take care of work first.
It's too bad,
but we can go some other time.
But-
Then meet me on Sunday.
Of course.
My PC seems to have broken again.
I'm thinking of buying a new one,
but do you think you can choose one for me?
Of course.
I'd love to.
Afterwards we can go for something good to eat.
Ok, it sounds great.
Have a good night.
[Sunday, PC, Aoyama-san]
Doesn't that mean you like him?
Like?
You let him into your house right?
Yes, but..  Like isn't-
I haven't felt that lately.
When you like someone so much,
and you get all giddy?
You let them up, and you wonder
What's going to happen now?
Or just seeing him talking to another girl
makes you want to throttle him?
I haven't felt that in so many years...
Doesn't that mean you don't like him?
Pretend I'm Yamada.
We're sitting side by side.
Our hands touch momentarily.
Does it cause a jolt?
It doesn't.
See, it's like that.
You don't like him.
Normally you get excited.
And you want to hold his hand.
Love isn't something you have to think about.
If you're going to sigh, can't you do that elsewhere?
Sorry.
It's like everyone around me is sighing lately.
Oh, Hermes...
What, Hermes?
Densha.
I'm holding on.
Comike.
Why is it I have to wait around for you.
You're the one who called up suddenly.
No complaining!
Here.
What is it?
It's a discount coupon.
See, I'm trying to save you money.
So I'm paying?
Well of course.
Hold it.
There's no other reason why I'd call you here.
Welcome to our store.
Here are your menus.
Please take your time.
It's expensive.
What is it?
I can't believe you're the same species.
What are you doing just standing there?
He's a great looking guy isn't he?
What are you doing?
What, is that girl the one you like?
Of course not.
So it is.  My.
I wonder if those two are going out?
What?
Who is it?
Do you know him?
Uh huh.
That's the guy?
Hmm.. He's got a pretty cute girl with him.
Kind of prim.
I wonder if that's his girl.
It could be that's what they're thinking.
That we're going out.
I doubt it.
It could be we look like a couple.
That we're beauty and the ape.
An ape?
Leave it to me.
I'll ask for you.
Something's suspicious too.
What is?
Let me ask for you.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
Could I get your number?
Tell me your's too.
Can you see it ok?
I was surprised, you were suddenly there.
So was I.
Back there,
I first thought she was your girlfriend.
I was jealous.
What do you mean?
I'm bad with women.
Really?
Well yeah.
At least to me, you're very attractive.
Hm?
I...
Um...
I have something I have to tell you.
I've wanted to tell you for a while.
Today we...
met by coincidence and...
I...I not prepared.
Not for what I want to say.
The next time we meet...
I have something important to say..
at least..
it is for me.
It's very important and...
I need to tell you.
To say how I feel.
W, will you hear what I have to say?
Yes.
Please...
let me know.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I think this feels more natural.
Wait...what did you say!!!
Yay, Benoist!!!
Run!!  We're under barrage!
It'll all be decided when we meet next time.
We both know what the other is thinking.
Or should I say we "found out".
Hermes!!!
It's a movie,
a drama,
a book.
It's been a honour witnessing this miracle.
Densha, you've grown beyond the realm of this forum.
It's almost time for your graduation!
Densha, you've obtained Hermes!!
It's still too early to say.
You've come too far for it to fail.
I'll say it in advance, congratulations!!!
Hermes is awesome!!!
She likes you for sure.
There's no need to wonder what to do.
Yep, all I have to do is tell her how I feel on our next date.
Ahh, everthing's going all white.
Does anyone else want to
pass beyond the light with me?
I guess this is what they call a miracle.
Miracle... It's the result of your hardwork isn't?
It's because you all supported me!!!
If it wasn't for that old drunk,
this miracle wouldn't have happened.
What really made it happen,
was your courage.
If you ignored what happened, we wouldn't be here.
I'm proud that one of the
members on this forum was so brave.  Cheers!
Cheers to our chief!*
Benoir!!
What kinda racket you makin so late?
Hurry yourself ta work!
Dad.
I was planning on leaving right now.
You go on ahead.
Comic Kingdom 14
It's certainly quiet here now.
You're not supposed to stay here overnight.
Hey, where's Yamada-shi?
He should be here on the first train.
It's not here.  It's not here.
Why, why isn't it here?
Why, why, why?
Hello, Healthy Drink Bar, Ryu speaking.
This is Yamada calling.
Aoyama-san's friend?
Um...
What is it?
Was there a blue envelope lying around there?
No, I don't think so.
I see...
Was it something important?
Uh.. well...
It's something I need at work.
Sorry for disturbing you, thanks for your time.
What's this?
Did someone forget it?
Hey, this is-
I'm so in trouble.
Why, why?
He called?
It seemed to be an important document for work.
Ok, then I'll call him from here.
Please let me in.
Please.
You forgot your ticket right?
That one doesn't work.
If you could make an exception for me.
Please.
Yamada-shi, you're late.
Please, let me in.
Please.
I'm begging you.
You can take this in return.
I got it after becoming a regular at this one maid cafe.
Something that precious?
And this too.
This is a limited edition figure of Becky wearing glasses.
I'll give this to you,
so please let us in.
Something so precious?
So you're saying you don't have an entry pass?
Please, we're begging you.
Take 'em!
The interrogation start here.  Now what are your specs?
Hey Saori, what's up?
Where are the documents?
You came here to pick them up yourself?
I couldn't get in touch with him, so I'll deliver them myself.
It's probably this.
Thanks.
I'm off then.
Do you know where he works?
He was saying something about the Tokyo Big Site.
So you.
She so wound up.
She sure must like him.
We can see our goal!
Just a bit more...
Spare us.
Ok, let's all sing Mina's theme song!
1, 2-
Love
Aoyama-san/Yamada Tsuyoshi
It seems they met on the train when
he saved her from a drunk guy.
On a train?
From a drunk?
There's an event of some kind going on.
Then let me off here.
Are you sure?  There's still a ways to go.
That's ok.
And after that he faught off a stalker,
and came to our house.
Faught off a stalker?
And went to your house...
So it's tomorrow then...
when Densha tells her how he feels.
So this is it then.  It really makes you think.
So this is the last day Densha will be single.
Let's all send him off in a big way.
I'm starting to get sad already.
Tomorrow's the day when our comrade heads off his own way.
Try to keep your eyes open till the end everyone!
We're all seeing at the same radiant glow.
Such a soft light.
I'm glad we got him to call her that day.
Why is it that I can't stop shaking?
We're all on the verge of seeing a legend being born!!
I hope I can reach his level someday too...
I like Densha and all of you guys too.  Benoist!!
Rooting for Densha became a daily ritual.
What am I supposed to do now?
Same here.
I was worried about him all the time.
He was our hope all along.
Our hope will be moving on tomorrow.
This is really like a graduation.  I'm crying here.
Everyone's ready right?
Densha doesn't belong here anymore.
I know we're all going to miss him, but...
Huh?  There's salt water in my eyes.
My heart hurts.
I'm crying already.
Benoist!!!
Comic Kingdom's Takeda Karin Live will start shortly.
Those of you with tickets please line up in an orderly fashion.
[Congratulations Densha Otoko]
[You Graduate]
Karin-chan.  It's time.
This way.
What is it?
Mind the store.
What?  I have a date now.
Then, then...close the store.
I'm so sorry.
Extreme circumstances call for extreme measures.
Let's sell them here.
I'll help.
Where should I put this?
Put it where the wind won't knock it down.
I came here to deliver this.
Oh, those stubborn guys.
They went that way.
Hermes was Saori!!
Sorry I was late.
Sorry for asking you so suddenly.
I got these from my Sister.
So these were the tickets?
Nothing, let's go.
Why are there so few people?
Matsunaga-shi
Wow,
There's so much activity in there.
Kawamoto-shi, how did you get in?
Wha!!  This hardly looks like CG at all!!
But the ankles on mine look better.
But the lip over here seem fuller.
Just look at the vivid colors!
Amazing!
Awesome.
They really show sophistication here.
This is great.
What is it Matsunaga-shi?
Yamada-shi, it's bad if someone finds out you're an Otaku right?
I think a greeting is in order here.
That's true.
I'm like, so dead.
And the weather's like, so awesome.
This weather's like bodacious.
Yeah, bodacious.
Like, thank so much for dinner last time.
Meeting you here is like, far out.
Matsunaga-shi, your thing.
Sea Turtles laying eggs!
Like, its so awesome!
Like, they're going to come out.
Like, they're totally flowing out.
Matsunaga-shi.
Matsunaga-shi, we're not needed her anymore.
Oh my gosh, it's like they're spawing!
Um...
Today...
I was sort of...
So you didn't have work?
No.
It's..
I'm sorry.
To be honest, I was surprised.
Yes.
So you..
lied to me.
I thought finally...
I'm so sorry.
I...
At such an important time...
I believed in you.
Next Episode
This peice of fiction was based on a true story.