From Densha Otoko, aired on Thursdays 10pm
(Caption by Hijouguchi Team)
(hijouguchiteam@yahoo.co.jp)
We invited Ito Misaki-san
[Drama "Densha Otoko"]
[Ito Misaki]
Hello
[Drama "Densha Otoko"]
[Ito Misaki]
Hello
Wow...
This is good
He is talking about you two
Ito-kun is all worked up
Not...
At all...
W.W.W.Worked up
Do you two guys talk a lot? During filming?
We do a lot, right?
Yes, we are close to each other
Ito Misaki-san, have you ever thought of Ito-kun as a possible boyfriend?
Different from before
Not yet...
After the drama finishes...
Do you know Ito (Misaki)-san's mail address, Ito-kun?
That is...
Secret
He seems like he knows!!!
Now, Densha Otoko, the drama under the spotlight!
The original story in book form: 1 million copies sold!
Even the movie has been seen by 2.7 million people now!
[Hermes, Aoyama Saori, played by Ito Misaki]
With this much attention, even the Drama
Has more than 20% view rating!
[Densha Otoko, Yamada Tsuyoshi played by Ito Atsushi]
Love story of the year 2005
Let's analyze this drama with the keyword
Numbers!
Maybe an incredible number might appear?!
Here it comes...
Densha Otoko! Working hard! Databank! GO!
200 people
The animation at the opening of the drama
It was created specifically for this drama
And this ending theme by Sambo Master
Actually, this scene...
Was filmed after the trains stopped
At Akihabara Station Overnight!
It was just for 1 min 30 secs... and extras?
Surprisingly, 200 people!
This was the first time ever borrowing Akihabara Station for filming!
48 hours
These people on the Internet, who are so vital to "Densha Otoko"
There are a lot of different faces
There were over 35 people who made appearances
[From the 5th episode]
How much?!!
What a chance, but...
[From the 5th episode]
I also want to walk Hermes-san home!
But walking Hermes-san... you have grown up!
This Internet scene...
For one episode, it took 48 hours of filming!
Why does it take so long?
YES!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
YES!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
Huh?
This is so different from the drama!
Actually this internet scene...
Everyone recorded their voices first
And then based on the voices recorded
They filmed their acting
To add, their rooms were
All side by side like this
From this 48 hours of fliming, only 7 minutes were aired in this episode
Good job!
The things that attracted our attention in this drama
Were things that filled Densha Otoko's or the Internet people's rooms
The Otaku Stuff!
To add, this figure was...
4000 dollars (400,000 yen)!!!
In Densha Otoko's room
There are 132 pieces!!!
The special objects in this drama...
Number of those are!!
3000!!!
A... Amazing!!!
1000 Hours
Now, let's see the two people's work until now!
This time,
Densha Otoko, who did his best for Hermes, Ito Misaki-san
Ito Atsushi-kun
Forgive me please
[From the 4th episode]
First, this scene
It is the scene where he practices surfing for Hermes
Looks so cold~
Falling down many times...
Even if it is just filming, it looks so hard
The time spent to film this scene was 5 hours!
[From the 7th episode]
Why?
And this one
Densha Otoko, waiting for Hermes to give her the present in the rain
Happy Birthday
In this touching scene, both had to film for 6 hours in the rain
They are serious, aren't they?
And there are...
Only two episodes left!
If we add up all the filming time between the two
It amounts up to more than 1000 hours!
They are both really working hard!
And the scene where Densha Otoko really gave his all?
Here it is!!!!!
First, Ito Misaki-san
Ah, everyone is shopping?
Looks good!
[Sudo Risa]        [Sato Eriko]
[Slip]
Oh! Wait, Hermes just fell down?
Did you see that?
Did you just see that?
She just fell down!
You all right?
Ah, but so cute!
[Shiraishi Miho]
And Shiraishi Miho-san
[Hayame Mokomichi]
Full attention to her realistic acting!
Why?
I can't believe we are of the same species
[From here is ad lib]
Ouch, Jinnkama-san!
You, how much do you have on you today?
Today?
I only have $20
What are you doing? You are an adult now!
Sorry, I told you I don't have much...
You got your salary yesterday!
Yes, but... I don't have anything today
Give it all
Wow, so scary~!
What are you thinking!
When you eat with me, you bring shit loads of money!
Shiraishi-san is so into her character!
And Atsushi-kun
Let's get ready for date!
First, wash face
Oh, right right. Shave!
And clean ears
Brush teeth
Do my hair!
Ah, nose hair?
Yes yes this is a little unexpected
Cut it right~
Yes~
Maybe a little too much
You all right?
Atsushi-kun, you are overdoing it!
Atsushi-kun! Overdid his part!
And here
From the OK scene...
Can you smell the Otaku?
Something big happened...
This is the scene where he puts the precious figure inside his jacket
[~Rehearsing~]
During the rehearsal, to the 4000 dollar figure...
Something huge happened!!!
What happened?
Something broke!
Broke?!?
4000? 4000 dollars?
Oh crap...
Ear.. Is broken...
Oh for real! Ear broke off!
[Broke]      [Ear]
It is 4000 dollars...
Oh crap...
Atsushi-kun... You did it...
Until now was Densha Otoko's memorable scenes!
Oh, the figure... 4000 dollars... Were you all right?
No, really,
At that moment, everyone became so quiet
Um...
It was broken...
So what we have now is No.2
The scene with rain... It took 6 hours...
We filmed until 6am
We filmed right until the sunrise
We kept it pouring
You guys filmed together for 1000 hours now?
They were together for 1000 hours!
- Are you jealous?
- So jealous!
When do you wanna stop being a love-love grandpa?!
But it was awesome, right?
It was awesome
Awesome
There are some elements to it where you just can't act, right?
During acting, I learned who Misuzu was...
You learned about another self inside you?
Right
Chiba-san, how is she as a fellow actress?
Wow, amazing!
To identify so much with the character
I was wondering what it was like to have my image changed
Now, you guys are filming the last episode, right?
Are you guys even getting enough sleep?
No, it is quite HARD
Now, it is HARD
For the last episode
We are giving it all
The last episode is 90 minutes...
So is any part different from the original story?
Until you see it...
Please look forward to it!
Tell us~