I have something...
Important to say...
When I was with Misuzu...
Everything was shining..
This confession is...
From Misuzu I have received...
So many precious things...
Hello?
Oh, dad?
What's happening?
Oh, the company is bankrupt?
WHAT? What are you saying?
You are closing my shop too? No way!
WWWait dad
Hello? Dad?
Dad is...
Bankrupt...
He is bankrupt...
You can do it
I...
Like Misuzu!
Hate Sakurai-san!
Why?
Wa, scary!
You are nothing without money
Weren't we destined for each other?
Shut up about destiny and go earn some money
I will take this as a good-bye present
Please, not that!
You are (roar)!
You said you liked it...
Please, at least not the ring!
Ahhhhhhh!!!!
Should we sleep now?
Okay
Separately, right?
Right
Good night
Can you sleep?
No
Can we hold...
Can we hold... hands?
Of... Of course!
Did the forum exist before you started writing there?
Yes
Definitely, even before I started writing...
The issue that was discussed was...
[3 months before]
Today, I met the online girlfriend
I have been reporting to you about
She was so pretty!
[Guitar Otoko]
Yes Yes Yes!!!
Yes yes yes yes yes!!!!
Everyone, part the crowd for him!
It is the return of Guitar Otoko
Everyone, to the shelter!
Here comes Guitar Otoko's bombing!
But why Guitar Otoko?
The girl he met through an online dating service likes musicians
So he practiced guitar through online lessons
They actually met? Amazing!
So many people are waiting to scam people on the online services
The chance of actually meeting is 1 out of 10
Especially, if she is pretty, the chance is like 1000 to 1
Good thing I skipped my work today!
Did you show her your guitar skills?
My heart is beating loudly!
Please explain in detail!
We decided to drink tea before I got to show her my guitar
But I was forced to buy an old guitar for 3 million yen
(*3 million yen = 30,000 dollars)
Is this 3 million?
I asked my friend who knows a lot about guitars
And he said he will sell this especially for you
This is a really awesome guitar!
The world-renowned band Biga Pants used this guitar in their concert, "Tomorrow"
Bi... Biga Pants?
I never heard of Biga Pants...
No I think it is just us who don't know
I will tell you as a music otaku
Such a band does not exist!
Biga Pants... I never heard of them...
How can you say that...
You said you were interested in guitars in the mail you sent
That is because Miyoko-san said you like them...
Then will you buy it?
But there are two strings missing...
What are you talking about...
That makes it even more unique
I thought you were a guitar maniac
So I begged my friend to sell this...
Okay
Really?
Then please stamp here
I have to go somewhere so...
When can we meet later?
I will mail you~
U.. Um...
Got 3 million!
I feel so dirty, so let's get out of here
Shit, you just met him today, right?
People coming to such online services are usually really dumb
Getting money from them requires no skill
Women are scary~
Who got a fortune off of your crappy guitar?
This guitar... Wasn't this used by Biga Pants?
What is Biga Pants?
If you are talking about money, I won't return it
Even on the contract, it says no refund
Did you lie to me...
Was it a lie when you said you liked me...?
Of course it was a lie
Who do you think will like an otaku like you?
Miyoko-san, actually, for you...
You make me sick, turtle!
Let's go
It is your fault that you got tricked
Pain... is not just a dream...
That means, you were tricked?
So this was a scam to rip you off?
3 million...
You didn't give it to her, right?
I bought it
She was crying saying that she begged her friend for me
But after the deal, she...
Went back with some guy in a band
Yes, I was tricked
Single males are
Only gullible to other people
Guitar Otoko...
Bought a pot called guitar... So mean!
Guitar Otoko, what are you going to do?
Now I won't love anyone
And I decided on the Spring of my 30th year
Good job
We won't forget your courage
Now don't be so hard on yourself again
We can't dream of going out with pretty girls
Guitar Otoko, Good job
Now I won't write here
Lastly... Hail, Singles Ranting Thread!
You will get another chance
[Densha Otoko]
The visions dancing in my mind
[Another Final Special]
[Densha Otoko]
The early dawn, the shades of time
Twilight crawling through my windowpane
Am I awake or do I dream?
The strangest pictures I have seen
[The day Hermes and Densha met]
Wow the fireworks were pretty!
Your room is still very well organized
Wow it is Soma Megumi!
Ah, please don't touch it
I organized them by their voice actors
Anyway, what do you mean by something funny?
This is it
Internet
I found this on some forum
[Single Men's Ranting Thread]
Here it is
They call him Guitar Otoko
[Single Men's Ranting Thread]
Gui... Guitar Otoko?
Yes
He was scammed, what a stupid, dumb
Sickening otaku!
And this part is so funny too
I don't want to see it!
Why are you acting this way?
Because you are trying to show me what I don't want to see
I am trying to tell you something funny
Nice to meet you guys
I was always just looking through the thread
But I have something to report today, so I decided to write here
From tomorrow, I graduate from the ranks of Single Men
Tiffany, I love...
No, "I love you"
(*"I love you" is in Korean)
Let's get married
I also like Ushijima-san
Thank you
Is this a newbie?
Today, in the train coming back from Akiba event
A drunk man was harassing other passengers
I could not take it anymore, so I gathered up my courage and told him to stop
"Stop..." I said
For sure, my voice trembled
Because I have never fought before
Don't f**k around with me, you little bastard!
Finally, some salary man came to me and helped me
I didn't look cool... I looked wretched...
Good job, fighting against a drunken man... amazing
Well let's go to sleep for tomorrow
Good night, Tiffany
Ushijima-san
Welcome
Oh, Chanel!
Can you go get Tiffany?
Tiffany? She stopped working here
Handy, is that for real?
What are you talking about
She had a guy
You were tricked
2 million yen!
You lent it to her, right?
Didn't she leave anything for me?
Nothing...
Yeah...
So pitiful~
Pitiful~
Stop it
You were tricked~
I said stop it
You dumbass!
What Tiffany!
I don't know any Tiffany!
How dare you say that wretched name!
Something... something big happened!
I got a present and a letter from the young woman
The present, it came!!!!
The present is... a pair of tea cups,
A cute envelope, a stationery, and some words
Wow~ It smells nice~
No... My face is getting all hot!
Calm down!
Calm down
The smell is probably just an illusion
Can you see if you have any hope from the letter?
She wrote that she was touched by my courage...
Just that sentence? Very ambiguous...
Oh, now that I think of it...
If you got it by delivery, you must have her phone number?
Oh, I can do that!
Where is it...
On, on, on the delivery form, a cell phone number...!
No...
I can't call a girl... OTL
What is he saying in front of me...
I...
Can't even call her
Punch those numbers in!
Think about it after you are connected
I think it is impossible...
People do not change that simply!
You make me mad, geez!
I need bigger courage now than before
My hands are trembling
My face is all hot
My heart is about to explode!
All talk! Do something!
I am only going to say one thing
She is by herself...
But we are all with you
That is how it works
Sending a pair of cups means she wants you!
But do you know what brand of cup it is?
On the cup
H
H E
H E R
H E R M
H E R M E
H E R M E S ... so it says...
Which kitchen ware brand is it?
Hermes!!!!!
YES-------('V')-------!!!!!
Tiffany
You mean the bag brand, Hermes?
It's a brand name item!
I can't stop trembling
There is nothing for you to lose!
Trust her heart!
Help me trust!
[Go!]
[Densha Otoko]
De..de...
Densha Otoko...?
Is he referring to me...
[Densha Otoko]
Densha...
Densha... Otoko....
I will follow what the next post says!
[Go!]
Call her!
Densha Otoko
Please!
At least for us!
Change!
[Call her!]
[Densha Otoko, please, at least for us]
[Densha Otoko, please,
[Call her!]
please, at least
her!]
at least for us
for us, change!]
change!]
I will call her now!
YES!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
YES!!!!!!!!!
YES!!!!!!!
Go, young man!
Go Densha!!!!!!!!!
Tiffany...
The phone number you have dialed...
Of course...
Where did she go off to...
Tiffany...
[July 8th, Friday. Dinner with Hermes]
What is going on? What is all that stuff!
I wanted to cheer on Densha Otoko with Kawamoto-shi
I will be staying here for a while
Can you move the bed over here?
Okay
Wait...
Wa.. Wait
It doesn't fit
Can we make the door a little bigger?
Wawawait!!
Of course not!!
Wait stop stop STOP!
Why did you bring such huge bed?
I can't sleep in a different bedding
Then all you need is your blanket
Oh, that's true
Then, thank you for letting me in
Don't you have a computer in your house?
I need courage to read this thread by myself
What are you talking about?
I can't really tell you what I am talking about...
Oh, a new message from Densha Otoko!
I was so nervous
Walking side by side with a woman
If I just walk normally
I leave her behind
It is okay
I am still holding on...
Wow awesome...
Really awesome...
We are already reading this for the 100th time
And Hermes became Yakushimaru Hiroko in Matsunaga-shi's imagination
But I have so much time...
Densha Otoko is going to go on a meeting...
(*Meeting: Group Blind Date)
Anyway, can you go back to your house now?
Don't say such heartless things
I ordered sushi to celebrate my move-in!
Celebrating your move-in?
Until when are you going to stay here?!
Sushi is here!
I have been waiting~
What is this!
I ordered a on-site sushi service...
My girlfriend likes herring roe
Wasting money again...
Ah, Yamada-shi!
Sorry for calling so suddenly but
You want to go on a meeting now?
A meeting?
You mean with us?
And can you somehow hide your otaku...
That is asking too much...
Can you somehow...
Please
Even if it is Yamada-shi asking, we can't do that
A meeting at the same time...
Maybe Yamada-shi is Densha Otoko...
What... did you say now?
Nono~
No way~
No, nothing
Anyway, I decided not to love anyone now
We will never go
Ah, hello? Hello?
Matsunaga-shi? Kawamoto-shi?
Why?
I don't know
Nice to meet you
Nice meeting you
Why?
Why is this happening?
Senpai, it hurts
Saori just went back with Yamada already
I just wanted to talk at the club
And they bring us here
What is happening?
Senpai, you are killing me!
Wow that was super very good~
It is your turn next~
Where are you going?
Bathroom
If you leave me, I will kill you
I will be back soon
Don't look at the song book
Say something
Um... what should I say...
Anything
Maybe stories about love...
Actually, I got dumped by a girl not too long ago
I met her on a online dating service
I was tricked into buying a guitar for 3 million yen
3 million?
I was tricked
How stupid...
There is no way I can get a girlfriend...
Why are you smiling like a moron?
Why aren't you trying to show her a different side of you? Even after being shamed like that
Make one or two love songs with that guitar
And get a better girl for yourself
Why am I preaching at a meeting
Why are you crying!
It is the first time a woman said things like that to me
No, I didn't mean it that way...
Thank you... For a person like me...
Nono
I will show you something
Sea turtle laying eggs!
Laying eggs!
Yuko-san will never send you a mail
It was going so well then, why?
There must have been a deep reason to have us come out
Anyway, why don't you finish the book to sell at the Comiket
Um...
Densha Otoko posted something...
What are you talking about?
Densha Otoko probably is invited over to Hermes's house by now
But this...
I, I am at Hermes-san's house right now
What? Y, you're not looking at it with Hermes, are you?
No, I'm hiding it
Live from Hermes-san's house!!
Idiot!  What if she catches you?
Shut it down now!!  What do you think you're doing?
But I forgot what my lines were...
Is English tea ok?
Y, yes
Please choose one of these
Okay
She just brought in these cans of English tea
This is dangerous, I am getting excited because it is too real
I guess her household drinks really expensive tea
It says BE-NO-IST
Benoist?
Benoist. Established in the 19th century, they provide the finest in food and drink
Intelligence, thanks for the info
They cater to the British royalty!!!!
Benoist Tea, yes-----!!
Have you decided yet?
Yes
I'll go with the Benoist
They're all Benoist
Um, I'll go with this
Darjeeling?
I like it too
Yes
Hermes
Huh?
Hermes?
Hermes??
Hermes???
Hermes????
[Benoist]
Densha
I am still holding on
Hermes...
Hermes bag and Benoist tea
25 years old, black straight hair
Skinny...
White complexion...
Bright looking...
Is she...
Hermes?
Excuse me but... do you like Benoist tea?
No... that is not the...
You don't have to hide it
And you like Darjeeling?
I said no...
Don't worry, I know it all
Anyway, would you like to have dinner with me?
Please stop it
If not a dinner, then how about a cup of coffee...
I am running Healthy Drinking Bar near the next station
Stop it
What?
I,I... I am telling you... to stop it
What are you saying?
She... she is telling you to st.. stop it...
No this is...
A miraculous...
Ouch!
Ouch ouch!
What are you doing?
Calm down and sit
Sit, geez!
Ouch ouch...
Why are you resisting?
Sit down!
I don't have arthritis...
You look wretched
Act your age
What are you guys!
Give up! Give up!
This man was causing trouble?
Yes
What do you mean, "yes"?
Huh?
Huh? This situation is...
When did you make a copy of the key?
Wow, we couldn't sell any of the "Ankle Princess"
Well that isn't a problem since we predicted it
But I am worried about the scary mood between Yamada-shi and Aoyama-san
Even sea turtle laying eggs didn't work
Matsunaga-shi
I think Densha Otoko got dumped
What?
Densha Otoko also got dumped at the comiket? With Hermes?
Wait a minute...
Maybe... Yamada-shi is Densha Otoko?
Nono no way~
Densha...
Is this the end for him?
What are you talking about?
Nothing, I am talking to myself
Anyway, what did you have to tell me?
Actually, Tiffany called us
Really?
She is working at a shop in Kabukichou
(*Kabukichou is a district in Shinjuku, Tokyo)
And?
But I am sure she has a boyfriend
If not, she wouldn't have stayed in Tokyo
I know that much...
I know...
Long time no see...
Can you even pay back the interest for 2 million yen?
I am sorry...
That is...
Not that...
You have something of worth here
I will take it as this month's interest
Wait there!
Please, not that!
F**k off, bastard!
Are you really giving this to me?
I don't know the details... but it is for your dream, right?
I like Ushijima-san!
Haha, all talks~
It is not because of the money
Whatever~
You say that to other men too
No~
I only say "I like you" to one person
Okay okay
Let's drink tonight!
This world...
No way it is that easy...
I met Hermes-san by accident today,
and it's all clear now
She's was irreplaceable to me
And this is true even now
I can't let it end this way
Densha
Well said, Densha!!
I was waiting for you to say that!
Did you find some handsome new idol??
Ah, yes something like that
[Special on Super Rich People]
[No. 4 Matsunaga Yuusaku (30)]
[Annual Income 30 million yen! Owner of Huge Land in Nagoya!]
Annual Income, 30 million?!
Maybe he is a treasure!
Yes, Densha Otoko!
Showing his otaku-ness to Hermes!
This is Mizuki Yuko, we met at the meeting before
Sorry for the late reply
I couldn't get Matsunaga-san out of my head, so I am sending a mail
Are you okay?
No, nothing
Your eyes are swiveling around
What are you hiding?
No just...
What is this
No, don't!
It is my hobby
[20 days since fixing computer]
Work work work!
It is done!
I fixed it!
Densha, I am back!
I got completely dumped by Hermes-san
This time, it is the end for real
What happened while I was gone?
If I hide that I'm an otaku, I'll be lying to her
You're taking it too seriously, everyone has things they have to hide
An Otaku is what makes you Densha
What's important is trying to be sincere to Hermes
100% getting dumped
Even if it is Hermes, she will hate you
Show her the true spirit of an otaku
I know it's a crazy gamble
But I can't lie to her anymore!
I'm going to come out to Hermes about my otaku
I got to go to Akiba with Hermes-san
What?!
You mean the fortress of otakus,'Akihabara'?
- You mean the fortress of otakus,'Akihabara'?
- Moreover, aren't you showing her too much?
Moreover, aren't you showing her too much?
What is up with this sudden happy-mode
I am excited!
Hermes-san might find out about this forum someday
Hey Densha, this is a quite serious problem
If you get caught, you will for sure be hated
This forum
Is my pride
So
Now
I will tell her
About this forum
My precious heart for her
Your precious concerns
By the time I got there, she already found out
I think her brother told her
I think Hermes-san was shocked
At finding stories concerning her here
I couldn't explain anything, just got dumped
After she said to never see her again
I finally realized...
Now
There is no way
To meet her
What are you talking about!
You still have a chance! Unlike me!
That's enough
You did good
Singles saying things about what you decided
Would not have any meaning anymore
- Would not have any meaning anymore
- I know it is hard for you
But don't stop now. You can find other girls!
No!
I can't accept things ending this way!
- I can't accept things ending this way!
- Densha...
Let's go back to the origin of all single males!
Densha Otoko!
The End!
The three months I spent with Densha are my treasures!
Now
I won't write here anymore
But I won't forget you guys
Thank you
Densha Otoko is done with now
So why don't you go back to Nagoya now?
No, I still have something to do
Wait, what are you doing?
Who are you talking to over the mail?
Brush your teeth before going to sleep
Yuko-san
Moreover, the mail says...
"Brush your teeth before going to sleep"??
You guys are sending mails like a couple!
Stop it
Did you already meet her several times?
No, not once since the meeting
Why
Meeting up with her is better than mailing
I don't want to be scammed again!
I really will be wretched if I get tricked again
"Again"? Did something happen before?
No...
I feel some mysterious power from the forum
Yes, as if it is saying it's not over yet
Why did you guys let Densha go with unfinished business?
This way, he won't have changed at all
I am also not sure that things will work out
But
I don't want any regrets
He never told Hermes-san how he actually feels
He can give up after he tells her
But it is too late now
Densha will never come back to this forum
We are only connected through the net
That is why we are called singles
Unless we change, we can't hope to change Densha's mind!
Is there anyone that will get him to come here
And tell him to confess!! Anyone!!!
Tomorrow is Sunday!
High probability that dejected Densha will go to Akiba!
How about Undercover Akiba project?
Densha told me he lives on the Chuo Line
I will wait at the station!
I will be the announcer at the station!
I will do a live street performance in Akiba
I will shout Densha in the middle of Akiba
I will call him 3000 feet above the ground!
I will write his story and publish it!
I will also call for people at Akiba
I will buy the whole Akiba to find him
Then I will call him on the TV
All right!
Let's make Densha come back to this forum!
Densha
Everyone is...
Right beside you
Inage
Tsutanuma
[JR Akihabara Staion]
Hunabashi
Ichikawa
[JR Akihabara Staion]
Shinkoiwa
Kinshichou
Bakurochou
Dad!
[Densha! Look at the forum!]
Who is Densha Otoko?
Well I don't know either
[Densha! Look at the forum!]
Caption by: Hijouguchi Team
(hijouguchiteam@yahoo.co.jp)
Ouch
What are you doing?
[Densha-san! Look at the forum!]
We already have something here, so over there...
Look here, look here!
[Densha Otoko! Come back to the forum!]
It is free to look at it
Pachinko store, this on the front
Next, Banzai
This on the left of the cow
Okay
Next, Ishimaru Electrics
Can you put this up in huge letters?
Everyone understand?
Please finish all the work in 2 hours
Let's get to work!
Densha
Come back!
Hermes...
[Densha Otoko!! Come back to the forum!!]
Hey Densha! Are you watching?
Densha! Come back to the forum!
You won't understand anything that way!
I will be right back
Good luck
Please look at the forum
Densha Otoko? You mean that Densha Otoko?
[Densha! Confess!]
Densha... Confess...
[Densha Otoko! Come back to the forum!]
Everyone...
For me...
Change yourself so that you won't regret it later!
[Densha Otoko! Come back to the forum!]
Densha, this love is not over yet
[Look at the forum! Densha Otoko! -All Densha Supporters-]
I am a girl, and I think this is not the goal yet
Densha, come back to the forum!
I won't push you anymore
Because plenty of singles have pushed you until now
But now, get your own courage and go!
[Densha! Confess!]
I think Hermes needs you!
[Densha Otoko]
[Densha Otoko! Come back to the forum!]
[Densha Otoko! Come back!]
Single man, A-boy! Go get her!
I think I've shared not only his happiness but also his sadness
So, you are not alone when you feel depressed!
[Densha Otoko! Look at the forum!]
We are always with you!!!
Sincerely, thank you everyone
Every single word is written on my heart
It is a good thing that I met this thread
It is a good thing that I spent time with you guys
I...
Will try once more
Yes!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
Densha
If it is you...
It is possible!
I can't understnad
You are getting so much courage from Densha
But you can't come to a date by yourself
It is because I don't have any courage that I am rejecting a relationship
I have been tricked by women before
Matsunaga-shi, you have experience with women?
Actually, with the girl I met on the online dating service
We exchanged mail 123 times
And the first day we met, I was tricked into buying a guitar for 3 million yen
That story is...
Guitar Otoko's...?
Yes
I am the one
Who was scammed!
Stupid, dumb,
Sickening otaku, Guitar Otoko
Who said that...
I am scared
Of being tricked again
Matsunaga-shi...
I can't be like Densha Otoko
Long time no see~
Oh you brought your friend
Anyway, this is a pretty weird store
Um...
Yes?
I can't go out with Yuko-san
Oh, I don't mind your hobby
No it's not that
Please give me up!
Wait a second
Let's talk outside
No violence!
You can't go out with me? What do you mean!
No... I mean...
Tell me to my face, if you are a man
Um... your ankle is not moe~ enough...
Your ankle is not my type
Are you trying to say that my leg is fat?
Yes... if you are talking about the ankle...
I usually reject people like you
Why was I ever going for you?
I am ashamed of myself
That kick almost matches that of Mina
Don't be so sad
I was also hurt hearing that Yamada-shi's sister had a boyfriend
What is this pain in my heart!
It even permeated into his heart!
How strong!
Why did I lie about her ankle being fat?
Ma..Ma..Matsunga-shi!!!
Why are you all worked up...
I think Densha Otoko's confession is over
What?
Let's scroll up to see
I just came back
There it is
She and I decided to go to our secret place
Hermes-san didn't say anything while we were going there
Of course, neither did I...
And then, the silence was broken
I read the forum
Yes...
I was happy
Don't read it out loud!
I am imagining her as Takeda Karin
Can Kawamoto-shi play the part of Densha Otoko?
No thank you...
Densha-san...
Thinking about me in such ways...
I was so happy!
All the people at the forum are all so nice
Yes
So...
I came...
To formally listen to what is in your heart...
Can you...
Can you... tell me?
Yes...
I.I.I..I have something important to say
Yes
Everything was shining when I was with Hermes-san
But...
I... didn't have anything...
Couldn't do anything for you...
But...
But...!
My heart caring for Hermes-san!
Compared to anyone's...
There can be no less!
I.....
I......
You can do it
I....
I.....!
He.He.. Hermes-san...
L.L..Like Hermes-san!
I also...
Like...
Densha-san!
So
Even from now on...
Will you always be with me?
Yes!!
I started crying with you...
What are you doing?!
After saying I like you...
I like you even more
Is everyone still alive?
It was a huge bombing...
I didn't know the the final weapon was this... strong
F..F... Finally, love has been fulfilled!
Let him continue ranting
B..But
So nice that it all worked out
Otaku single man becoming a couple...
Now Densha is way ahead of us
So let's graduate him from this thread!
Because he is not a single man anymore, right?
So our part is over
I will be alone again
Hey... Can't Densha stay here?
Right
Couples are taking part in this too
Wouldn't Densha also want to stay?
No way
This way, if anything happens to Densha
He will come looking for our help
It doesn't help him grow
Densha gave us all something
Shouldn't we give his new start tons of blessings?
Sorry, I am a little late
Hermes-san said "I wish everyday were Sunday"
In the mail that she just sent
I am so happy~
Sorry but please say that kind of stuff in the Couple Zone
Now ranting is over
We are not that free to listen to your ranting forever
Go away before this thread becomes a "1000 reply thread"
Huh? Things seem a little cold here... Is it just me?
Densha, listen to me
You are not a single man anymore
Which means, it is time for you to graduate
Now we will not look over you anymore
I want you to stay, but I think it is time to say goodbye
Why?
Finally, we became companions
That makes me feel lonely again
We are saying this because we are your companions
You must take a new step now
You are not alone anymore
Be strong!
Who will protect Hermes-san if you don't protect her?
All right
I...
Will leave
Well said, Densha
Everyone! Tell him your feelings!
This is the single man's graduation!
Densha...
I understood through you
That I can't always stay as a supporter
So I will find my love on the field
You guys are really... Benoist!!
I always shouted "Hermes, moe~!"
But for today, Densha moe~!
I can't stop here either
No more loose socks! Now panty hose!
Last train!
Happiness for Densha and Hermes-san!
Densha, you write the 1000th reply
Soon...
It is good-bye...
I thought of... the message...
I...
Something I have been thinking all along...
Don't forget us!
Finally, this is the end...
It was fun
Thanks
Bell for train leaving~!
Graduation
Congratulations~!
999 Name:
[Densha Otoko, Congratulations on your graduation!]
[Densha Otoko]
This thread is full of magical power...
May the light be with you guys too!
Light be with you guys...
[1001 Name: 1001 Over 1000 Thread
This thread has more than 1000 replies
You can't write anymore, so please make a new thread]
Awesome companions, right?
I also want to confess to Yuko-san
What are you talking about Matsunaga-shi?
I was running away because I was afraid of getting hurt
What happened to you suddenly?
Her kick was for me
Now you are going into trans-mode?
Let the light be with me!
Long time no see everyone
This is Guitar Otoko
Guitar Otoko!
You are alive!
Actually, I have been following Densha Otoko silently
Because of him, I think I can stand up on my feet once more
Tomorrow at 7PM, in front of Tokyo Dome
I will confess tomorrow through the big screen
I will write what I intend to say here
Isn't it too much telling where to confess?
If I don't do this much, I don't think I will be able to do it
Confession through the big screen!
This is even bigger than Densha Otoko's graduation!
And he even disclosed the time, what is he thinking?
I think she is just a scam
I know I am taking a risk
But my intuition tells me she is the right person
I don't deserve her because she is such an awesome person
So to make my intention stronger, I wanted to tell everyone about it
I will send her a mail now
Guitar Otoko, why are you being so hard on yourself?
What is your source of energy?
I learned from Densha
The strong attitude of never giving up
And the unwavering trust for love
[Unwavering trust]
Please be in front of the big screen on Tokyo Dome tomorrow at 7pm
What is that?
Isn't this just a joke?
But you seem so occupied about it
Wasn't money your purpose?
But for some reason...
Even if it just sending mails for over 100 times
You get familiar with him...
Maybe it is just a maternal feeling
I can't just leave him like that
Well, it is all over anyway, okay?
Okay okay
Frendy
Ushijima-san
You are really early today!
What is going on?
Sorry
Which store in Kabukichou is Tiffany at?
Ushijima-san, even if you go...
Even if she has a boyfriend, it doesn't matter
I trust Tiffany
So at least I want to tell her my feelings
You are so stubborn
She is in Rick Dome
Rick Dome
Okay
Sorry
If I read this forum
I feel like everything will go okay
So I could gather up my courage
Because of your advice
And your support
I...
I think I grew up a little bit
Whenever I think of her, I feel more unsecure...
But you guys gave me courage even though I didn't know your names or faces
If I didn't write on this forum
I couldn't have liked myself as I do now
And moreover
I couldn't have met
Such precious friends
Because always you guys were beside me
I could
Try my best
It is a good thing that I met this thread
It is a good thing that I spent time with you guys
Tiffany
May the light
Be with you guys
My dream was becoming a singer
At the shop, some guy calling himself a manager of an office
Told me to pay him 2 million for signing a contract
But...
He never called me back
So I followed him to Tokyo
But there was no office
Sorry
For lying to you...
I felt so sorry for Ushijima-san
I wanted to work to pay you back
That is enough
I...
Don't have any money
I look wretched
And all I want is for the Hanshin Tigers to win
(*Hanshin Tigers: a baseball team in Japan)
I don't know that much about Tiffany
Not my style...
I like slightly bigger breasts
30 years old...
Shit, what am I talking about
I can't think of anything good to say
It has to be you
I will make you happy
So so...
Be with me
Yes!
Also I...
Really really like Ushijima-san!
Really...
Are you okay even with me?
I told you before
I only say "I like you" to one person
Ushijima-san
Laugh
Being this happy
Who would be able to laugh?
Shit
I have to buy the ring again!
Sorry but I have to go somewhere
Where?
It is where another guy who received courage from Densha is
I am going to go back
Senpai, be considerate
It is already 7 o'clock
Yuko-san
I will now tell you my feelings
Is that Guitar Otoko?
What an otaku!
He is super Akiba-type
Guitar Otoko's specifics?
Looks low
I came to cheer Guitar Otoko on
But looks like there is almost no chance
I am not late
Finished!
I first met you
On some meeting
I was on fire just from your first impression
The fall will end soon
The season of abundance will end soon
So before it all ends
I will tell you
I like you~
I really like you~
That is so creepy
The single man was full of single-ness
Why did I even skip my class
Guitar Otoko, not on fire
Even I can sing better
Let's just go back home
No hope whatsoever
Give me my money back!
Well, I didn't pay...
I can't take this anymore
I hope she didn't come
So I will tell you before it all ends
This is too much
Let's go back
Is there someone called Yuko-san?
Please listen to me!
There was someone called Guitar Otoko, a typical otaku
He never went out with any girls
So to a girl he met at the online-dating service
He was tricked into buying a guitar for 3 million yen
So he decided to never love anyone
But
He stood up on his feet only because he met you
He stood up to tell you his feelings
So...
It might be a horrible performance
But will you please listen to it until the end?
He made that for you, senpai...
Love song...
I...
Don't deserve this
Money was the primary purpose at first
But it was "at first"
I only communicated with him through mail
But over 100 times
You are my everything
Just you being with me...
But still, he is really bad
I can't even think that he actually practiced
Not late yet?
Not late yet, right?
Yes!
Yes, this is Matsunaga-shi's cellphone
Tell the pitch-deaf beside you
To buy me dinner this Sunday
Matsunaga-shi
Matsunaga-shi!
We did it!
She called!
The phone!
Yuko-san called you!
To tell you to buy dinner this Sunday!
YES!!!!!!!!!
I am for ankles
Hey everybody
I am for ankles!
On your ankle
Want to go drink?
Yes!
The dinner was delicious
Yes, I didn't know it was going to be such a feast!
I have prepared your beds
Um... She is staying next door...
Oh~ I thought you two were sharing a room~
Just got married?
N.No...
No
But this is fine
It is cold these days
So I will place them together
Thank you
The bath tub will close soon so please hurry
Then I will go take a bath
Yes
W.W.W.What do I do?
Everyone, long time no see
This is emergency!
I came to a hot springs with Hermes-san
But things went weird and now we are sharing one room
What do I do?
Densha, he came-------('V')-------!!!!!!!!!!!!
------------------------------
If the light hidden in your tears is turned on
Geez, he is helpless
------------------------------
If the light hidden in your tears is turned on
Just ranting on like that!
------------------------------
If the light hidden in your tears is turned on
Just ranting on like that!
------------------------------
...
I told him not to come back
------------------------------
I will talk about warm things in front of your eyes
There is only one thing you can do!
------------------------------
I will talk about warm things in front of your eyes
There is only one thing you can do!
------------------------------
Even then if our voices
What was that sudden bombing?
------------------------------
Even then if our voices
What was that sudden bombing?
------------------------------
Go dry
I can't forgive him!
------------------------------
...
I can't forgive him!
------------------------------
At least until the morning comes
Even I haven't experienced it!
------------------------------
At least until the morning comes
Densha is becoming an adult!
------------------------------
At least until the morning comes
Densha is becoming an adult!
------------------------------
I want to sing with someone!
I like Densha who asks us about even things like these~~!
------------------------------
I want to sing with someone!
I like Densha who asks us about even things like these~~!
------------------------------
If you say you were fake yesterday
Ask your parents!
------------------------------
If you say you were fake yesterday
Can I explain step by step?
------------------------------
If you say you were fake yesterday
Live coverage please!
------------------------------
If you say you were fake yesterday
I don't think I am the only one imagining
------------------------------
I will only lose yesterday's scene
Is Hermes watching this too?
------------------------------
I will only lose yesterday's scene
The things connecting the new days
Um...
------------------------------
The things connecting the new days
There is only  mixed-gender tub... Do you want to come too?
------------------------------
Are new days and myself!
There is only a mixed-gender tub... Do you want to come too?
------------------------------
I check it for some reason
The world calls that love!
Hermes-san just asked me
------------------------------
The thing that connects our heart's voices
"Do you want to take the bath together?"drftgy
------------------------------
The thing that connects our heart's voices
Bombing, it came!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
------------------------------
I didn't know that would be this scary!
Bombing, it came!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
------------------------------
Together in one voice
As if the past until now never existed
------------------------------
I sing!
Love and peace!
------------------------------
Will the flower blossom through sadness
Us in the new days
My pleasure~
------------------------------
Us in the new days
Will be known, so I feel~
------------------------------
For our dreams, the world is
Waiting for us to shout
------------------------------
Singing for you
I didn't know it would be that fearful
This drama is based on a true story
------------------------------
But us checking each other
This drama is just a bit based on a true story
------------------------------
But us checking each other