1
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:08,321
Caption by Hijouguchi Team
hijouguchiteam@yahoo.co.jp

2
00:00:08,321 --> 00:00:10,544
P.P.P...Please look at the forum

3
00:00:10,544 --> 00:00:13,667
E.E.E...Everything about me is in there

4
00:00:13,667 --> 00:00:15,409
P.P.Please

5
00:00:15,409 --> 00:00:17,774
R.R.R.R.Read until the last post

6
00:00:17,774 --> 00:00:20,661
A.A.At the last post, a message for Aoyama-san....

7
00:00:33,045 --> 00:00:38,147
[A-channel]

8
00:00:38,147 --> 00:00:39,523
[Single Men's Ranting Thread]

9
00:00:44,791 --> 00:00:47,879
Today, in the train coming back from Akiba event

10
00:00:47,879 --> 00:00:51,375
A drunk man was harassing other passengers

11
00:00:52,202 --> 00:00:56,609
I could not take it anymore, so I gathered up my courage and told him to stop

12
00:00:56,609 --> 00:00:59,186
Stop...

13
00:01:03,038 --> 00:01:06,504
I... I... am telling... you..... to ...... stop......

14
00:01:06,504 --> 00:01:08,602
For sure, my voice trembled

15
00:01:08,602 --> 00:01:11,425
Because I have never fought before

16
00:01:15,602 --> 00:01:16,522
Are you okay?

17
00:01:17,408 --> 00:01:19,818
I look so... wretched OTL

18
00:01:26,332 --> 00:01:28,676
Something... something big happened!

19
00:01:28,676 --> 00:01:34,465
I got a present and a letter from the young woman

20
00:01:34,465 --> 00:01:38,652
Can you see if you have any hope from the letter?

21
00:01:38,652 --> 00:01:42,111
She wrote that she was touched by my courage...

22
00:01:42,111 --> 00:01:43,722
Aren't things going too well?

23
00:01:43,722 --> 00:01:46,081
Now this is just becoming someone's imagination!

24
00:01:46,081 --> 00:01:47,477
Everyone, don't take this too seriously

25
00:01:47,477 --> 00:01:49,825
On, on, on the delivery form, there is a cell phone number!

26
00:01:49,825 --> 00:01:50,436
C

27
00:01:50,436 --> 00:01:50,873
Ca

28
00:01:50,873 --> 00:01:51,785
Call

29
00:01:51,785 --> 00:01:53,258
Impossible, impossible, impossible

30
00:01:53,258 --> 00:01:55,716
First, pick up the phone

31
00:01:55,716 --> 00:01:58,736
I have the phone in my hand, but I can't call her

32
00:01:58,736 --> 00:02:01,478
I need bigger courage now than before

33
00:02:01,478 --> 00:02:02,649
My hands are trembling

34
00:02:02,649 --> 00:02:03,480
My face is all hot

35
00:02:03,480 --> 00:02:05,257
My heart is about to explode!

36
00:02:05,257 --> 00:02:07,293
Shit, even I am all nervous

37
00:02:07,293 --> 00:02:09,226
Don't be fooled! He is baiting you

38
00:02:09,226 --> 00:02:10,688
I am only gonna say one thing

39
00:02:10,688 --> 00:02:12,715
She is by herself...

40
00:02:12,715 --> 00:02:15,482
But we are all with you

41
00:02:15,482 --> 00:02:18,109
Thank you everyone!

42
00:02:18,109 --> 00:02:20,039
I am shedding tears

43
00:02:20,039 --> 00:02:21,676
Because of your kindness

44
00:02:21,676 --> 00:02:24,353
And my own wretchedness

45
00:02:24,353 --> 00:02:27,023
I want to change!

46
00:02:28,951 --> 00:02:31,416
But do you know what brand of cup it is?

47
00:02:31,416 --> 00:02:32,027
On the cup

48
00:02:32,027 --> 00:02:32,626
H

49
00:02:32,626 --> 00:02:33,094
H E

50
00:02:33,094 --> 00:02:33,636
H E R

51
00:02:33,636 --> 00:02:34,148
H E R M

52
00:02:34,148 --> 00:02:34,533
H E R M E

53
00:02:34,533 --> 00:02:36,471
H E R M E S ... so it says...

54
00:02:36,471 --> 00:02:37,482
Hermes!!!

55
00:02:37,482 --> 00:02:38,982
Hermes?!

56
00:02:38,982 --> 00:02:39,707
Yes!

57
00:02:39,707 --> 00:02:41,389
You read it E-ru-me-su

58
00:02:41,389 --> 00:02:43,641
E.ru.me.su!

59
00:02:43,641 --> 00:02:45,694
You mean the bag brand, Hermes?

60
00:02:45,694 --> 00:02:49,826
It she just wanted to say thanks, she wouldn't have sent Hermes cups

61
00:02:49,826 --> 00:02:51,327
How about talking to us while calling her?

62
00:02:51,327 --> 00:02:52,267
We will be ready

63
00:02:52,267 --> 00:02:57,636
There is nothing to lose for you!

64
00:02:58,936 --> 00:03:04,591
[Densha Otoko]
[Try your best!]

65
00:03:15,398 --> 00:03:18,339
I will call her now!

66
00:03:20,584 --> 00:03:26,713
Yes!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!

67
00:03:26,993 --> 00:03:28,187
[So awesome!! ( '_ ' .) so awesome!]
[Yes yes yes yes~~~~!]

68
00:03:28,187 --> 00:03:29,166
[So awesome!! ( '_ ' .) so awesome!]
[Yes yes yes yes~~~~!]
[Go Densha!! Go Densha!!]

69
00:03:29,166 --> 00:03:30,545
[Yes yes yes yes~~~~!]
[Go Densha!! Go Densha!!]
[You are a man among men!]

70
00:03:30,545 --> 00:03:31,167
[Go Densha!! Go Densha!!]
[You are a man among men!]
[I can't hold it anymore! So Amazing! 731!!]

71
00:03:31,167 --> 00:03:31,838
[You are a man among men!]
[I can't hold it anymore! So Amazing! 731!!]
[Awesome! Go Densha!]

72
00:03:35,959 --> 00:03:38,339
I realized somthing huge!

73
00:03:38,339 --> 00:03:41,149
I somehow got to meet Hermes-san again

74
00:03:41,149 --> 00:03:44,803
But if she meets an otaku like me, she will look down on me!

75
00:03:44,803 --> 00:03:45,637
What do I do now?

76
00:03:45,637 --> 00:03:48,332
Relax. Your appearance is the problem

77
00:03:48,332 --> 00:03:50,701
If you change your appearance, you will be able to hide your otakuness

78
00:03:50,701 --> 00:03:52,734
If you change how you look, it will change how you feel

79
00:03:52,734 --> 00:03:55,728
There is hope if we give him a lecture on clothing and conversation skills!

80
00:03:55,728 --> 00:03:58,452
All right! For now, we will change Densha's appearance!

81
00:03:58,452 --> 00:03:59,578
Densha Otoko

82
00:03:59,578 --> 00:04:00,540
Densha Otoko
Renewal

83
00:04:00,540 --> 00:04:02,254
Densha Otoko
Renewal Project

84
00:04:03,382 --> 00:04:05,638
First, hairstyle

85
00:04:05,638 --> 00:04:07,869
Not blonde, but do dye your hair

86
00:04:07,869 --> 00:04:09,892
Just let the people at the hair salon decide for you

87
00:04:09,892 --> 00:04:12,357
If you want impact, you must go for corn rows or dreads

88
00:04:12,357 --> 00:04:14,880
No, short hair gives the best impression

89
00:04:14,880 --> 00:04:17,965
Isn't he going to panic when the worker talks to him?

90
00:04:17,965 --> 00:04:22,564
You can do anything for Hermes-san!

91
00:04:28,296 --> 00:04:30,020
Um...

92
00:04:30,020 --> 00:04:32,812
How am... I?

93
00:04:34,560 --> 00:04:39,051
Actually, I am not even thinking about...

94
00:04:39,051 --> 00:04:43,569
Going out with Hermes-san...

95
00:04:43,569 --> 00:04:45,904
But my heart...

96
00:04:45,904 --> 00:04:48,477
Is definitely leaning towards her

97
00:04:48,477 --> 00:04:52,238
If I meet, then I will definitely start liking her

98
00:04:52,238 --> 00:04:55,349
Of course, she might have a boyfriend

99
00:04:55,349 --> 00:05:00,693
And if I still like her, that might give me a hard time...

100
00:05:00,693 --> 00:05:03,068
I am already having a hard time...

101
00:05:04,775 --> 00:05:08,043
But just a single like me...

102
00:05:08,043 --> 00:05:11,770
Thinking about things like this in itself is extraordinary

103
00:05:11,770 --> 00:05:12,862
It is all because of you

104
00:05:12,862 --> 00:05:14,212
It is all because of you
[Densha! Confess!]

105
00:05:14,212 --> 00:05:15,584
[Densha! Confess!]

106
00:05:15,584 --> 00:05:17,461
Everyone...
[Densha! Confess!]

107
00:05:17,461 --> 00:05:19,049
Thanks so much!
[Densha! Confess!]

108
00:05:20,407 --> 00:05:22,409
For all of your precious hearts

109
00:05:22,409 --> 00:05:23,976
Thank you

110
00:05:26,438 --> 00:05:27,894
I...

111
00:05:27,894 --> 00:05:29,478
Will do my best!

112
00:05:37,721 --> 00:05:40,445
I was so nervous

113
00:05:40,445 --> 00:05:43,917
Walking side by side with a woman

114
00:05:43,917 --> 00:05:47,270
If i just walk normally, I leave her behind

115
00:05:47,270 --> 00:05:51,466
And she was... even prettier than the last time I met her!

116
00:05:51,466 --> 00:05:52,321
Sorry

117
00:05:52,321 --> 00:05:56,294
A man like me walking with a woman like Hermes-san

118
00:05:56,294 --> 00:05:57,991
It was so awkward...

119
00:05:57,991 --> 00:05:59,833
It made me so uneasy

120
00:05:59,833 --> 00:06:02,485
She is even taller than I am!

121
00:06:02,485 --> 00:06:06,495
It felt like as if everyone was looking at me

122
00:06:15,624 --> 00:06:17,638
It is okay

123
00:06:17,638 --> 00:06:20,141
I am still holding it...

124
00:06:26,613 --> 00:06:29,443
I was so surprised that my body stiffened

125
00:06:30,534 --> 00:06:32,709
Why did you let go?

126
00:06:32,709 --> 00:06:34,917
Hold hands!

127
00:06:34,917 --> 00:06:36,426
I am still holding it...

128
00:06:36,426 --> 00:06:38,129
I am still holding it...

129
00:06:38,129 --> 00:06:40,384
I am still holding it...

130
00:06:40,384 --> 00:06:43,866
No, I wanted to hold her hand

131
00:06:43,866 --> 00:06:48,231
I wanted to tell her that I wanted to hold her hand

132
00:07:02,175 --> 00:07:02,741
Yes

133
00:07:02,741 --> 00:07:03,196
Yamada-shi

134
00:07:03,196 --> 00:07:07,939
Did you forget that Mina's limited edition first episode DVD is coming out tomorrow?

135
00:07:07,939 --> 00:07:12,945
On that edition, there are sketches and cut-scenes for the legendary episode seven!

136
00:07:12,945 --> 00:07:15,976
At this rate, it will be sold out!

137
00:07:18,694 --> 00:07:19,780
Sorry

138
00:07:19,780 --> 00:07:22,843
But there are more important things than that

139
00:07:22,843 --> 00:07:24,629
Please excuse me

140
00:07:29,708 --> 00:07:32,161
Actually, I told you before but...

141
00:07:32,161 --> 00:07:36,467
Through a little misunderstanding, surfing became my hobby

142
00:07:36,467 --> 00:07:37,878
Are you all right?

143
00:07:37,878 --> 00:07:40,104
I will tell you how to become an expert quickly!

144
00:07:40,104 --> 00:07:42,224
If it is just balancing on the board, then I might be able to do it...

145
00:07:42,224 --> 00:07:46,381
Let's all find information and help Densha!

146
00:07:46,381 --> 00:07:48,109
Thanks guys!

147
00:07:48,109 --> 00:07:50,259
I will try my best!

148
00:07:58,716 --> 00:08:00,216
It is ok if you can't really surf

149
00:08:00,921 --> 00:08:04,363
But just don't forget that you lied

150
00:08:05,298 --> 00:08:06,743
The really important thing is...

151
00:08:06,743 --> 00:08:10,894
To give Hermes-san an explanation, for her sake

152
00:08:12,037 --> 00:08:13,578
Sorry...

153
00:08:13,578 --> 00:08:15,101
I...

154
00:08:15,101 --> 00:08:17,554
Can't surf...

155
00:08:17,554 --> 00:08:19,253
I...

156
00:08:19,253 --> 00:08:23,756
Lied to you...

157
00:08:23,756 --> 00:08:25,120
Lie?

158
00:08:25,120 --> 00:08:29,435
I am so sorry for lying to you

159
00:08:33,824 --> 00:08:37,052
I can't run away from otakuness

160
00:08:37,052 --> 00:08:40,554
If I try to hide my otakuness, I will be lying to her

161
00:08:40,554 --> 00:08:43,860
You are being too sensitive, everyone has some secrets

162
00:08:43,860 --> 00:08:45,271
You don't have to hide it!

163
00:08:45,271 --> 00:08:47,423
There can be no Densha without otakuness

164
00:08:47,423 --> 00:08:51,129
No, I think it is considerate to tell Hermes-san that you are an otaku

165
00:08:51,129 --> 00:08:53,726
Thank you everyone, for your sincere replies

166
00:08:53,726 --> 00:08:56,905
I know I am taking a big risk

167
00:08:56,905 --> 00:09:01,791
But I really can't lie to Hermes-san

168
00:09:03,191 --> 00:09:10,035
I will tell Hermes-san that I am an otaku

169
00:09:10,035 --> 00:09:12,481
I am...

170
00:09:14,116 --> 00:09:15,433
An otaku...

171
00:09:17,370 --> 00:09:19,489
"Backwards!"...

172
00:09:19,489 --> 00:09:21,305
Or "Disgusting!"...

173
00:09:21,305 --> 00:09:25,277
If you feel like this, then it is okay...

174
00:09:28,714 --> 00:09:32,093
But...

175
00:09:32,093 --> 00:09:34,435
To me...

176
00:09:34,435 --> 00:09:37,481
I can only live this way

177
00:09:42,745 --> 00:09:46,991
I didn't want to lie to Aoyama-san

178
00:09:48,718 --> 00:09:50,925
So...

179
00:09:50,925 --> 00:09:56,473
Please look at me as I am

180
00:10:15,369 --> 00:10:16,420
Hello?

181
00:10:16,420 --> 00:10:17,448
Hey, where are you now!

182
00:10:17,448 --> 00:10:21,065
I am working overtime! And you are not even showing up!

183
00:10:21,065 --> 00:10:23,356
It is not too late to come now! Come here now!

184
00:10:23,356 --> 00:10:26,578
Sorry, I made a very important promise for today

185
00:10:26,578 --> 00:10:29,322
What? Are you talking back to me?

186
00:10:29,322 --> 00:10:32,401
There is no way that takes priority before me

187
00:10:32,401 --> 00:10:34,382
Please, not today!

188
00:10:34,382 --> 00:10:38,412
I have the most important promise of my life

189
00:10:38,412 --> 00:10:40,345
What?

190
00:10:40,345 --> 00:10:41,346
Sorry!

191
00:10:46,965 --> 00:10:48,757
For the first time, I got rejected

192
00:10:54,653 --> 00:10:59,966
On this board, I wrote all the conversations I had with Hermes-san

193
00:11:00,454 --> 00:11:01,703
Maybe...

194
00:11:01,703 --> 00:11:06,410
It was too unbearable for Hermes-san

195
00:11:06,410 --> 00:11:07,786
But...

196
00:11:07,786 --> 00:11:10,198
If I didn't post on this forum

197
00:11:10,198 --> 00:11:11,769
I couldn't have...

198
00:11:11,769 --> 00:11:15,575
Met her...

199
00:11:15,575 --> 00:11:18,461
If I didn't post on this forum

200
00:11:18,461 --> 00:11:19,634
I wouldn't have...

201
00:11:19,634 --> 00:11:24,003
Liked myself as I do now...

202
00:11:24,508 --> 00:11:26,115
And moreover...

203
00:11:26,115 --> 00:11:31,472
I couldn't have met such precious friends

204
00:11:32,767 --> 00:11:35,913
Because you guys were always beside me

205
00:11:36,925 --> 00:11:38,449
I...

206
00:11:38,449 --> 00:11:42,422
Could do my best

207
00:11:42,422 --> 00:11:44,558
This forum is...

208
00:11:44,558 --> 00:11:46,186
My pride

209
00:11:47,181 --> 00:11:48,992
So...

210
00:11:48,992 --> 00:11:50,376
Now...

211
00:11:50,376 --> 00:11:52,029
I will tell her...

212
00:11:52,029 --> 00:11:55,511
About this forum

213
00:11:55,511 --> 00:11:58,456
My heart...

214
00:11:58,456 --> 00:12:02,221
All of your precious concerns...

215
00:12:03,156 --> 00:12:06,372
I want her to know them

216
00:12:25,892 --> 00:12:27,805
To Hermes-san

217
00:12:27,805 --> 00:12:34,208
I am sure you were shocked in many ways when you saw this forum

218
00:12:34,208 --> 00:12:40,238
I feel embarassed... and a little nostalgic...

219
00:12:40,238 --> 00:12:43,502
I get such weird feelings

220
00:12:43,502 --> 00:12:45,010
But...

221
00:12:45,010 --> 00:12:51,098
Everything I wrote here is perfectly true

222
00:12:51,098 --> 00:12:55,488
I can tell that to everyone here

223
00:12:55,488 --> 00:12:58,666
Even though I don't know their faces or their names

224
00:12:58,666 --> 00:13:05,055
They are my true friends

225
00:13:06,289 --> 00:13:07,488
To me...

226
00:13:07,488 --> 00:13:11,408
If there is anything that I can be proud of

227
00:13:11,408 --> 00:13:16,634
It is the fact that I met them

228
00:13:17,911 --> 00:13:19,713
Because they were there

229
00:13:19,713 --> 00:13:22,762
I didn't give up on you

230
00:13:27,748 --> 00:13:29,678
Because they were there

231
00:13:29,678 --> 00:13:34,702
I could decide to tell you all my feelings

232
00:13:37,819 --> 00:13:40,048
Tomorrow

233
00:13:40,048 --> 00:13:44,399
I will wait at our secret place

234
00:13:46,089 --> 00:13:47,334
I will wait until you come

235
00:13:49,924 --> 00:13:53,389
Lastly,

236
00:13:53,389 --> 00:14:01,022
I apologize for hurting you by writing on the forum without your consent

237
00:14:10,011 --> 00:14:16,589
[Densha Otoko]

238
00:14:29,898 --> 00:14:35,391
[Last Episode]

239
00:14:38,004 --> 00:14:39,084
Densha

240
00:14:39,084 --> 00:14:41,022
You have grown up this much!

241
00:14:41,022 --> 00:14:43,004
You are my enemy, but I am surprised

242
00:14:43,004 --> 00:14:48,837
But I will tell you that there exists an insurmountable obstacle

243
00:14:48,837 --> 00:14:52,978
This is the final round!

244
00:14:57,628 --> 00:14:58,313
Yes

245
00:14:58,313 --> 00:14:59,109
Oh, no!

246
00:14:59,109 --> 00:15:00,708
Saori lost conciousness

247
00:15:01,333 --> 00:15:03,651
She is being moved to a hospital near here

248
00:15:03,651 --> 00:15:06,409
She is calling your name unconsciously

249
00:15:06,409 --> 00:15:07,988
Please go there now!

250
00:15:07,988 --> 00:15:09,738
Okay! I will be right there!

251
00:15:10,700 --> 00:15:14,507
Huh? Who was there now!

252
00:15:15,321 --> 00:15:17,045
Yes yes

253
00:15:17,045 --> 00:15:19,043
Ouch! Ouch!

254
00:15:22,728 --> 00:15:24,428
Sakurai! Dispatch!

255
00:15:27,954 --> 00:15:29,386
Saori?

256
00:15:29,386 --> 00:15:29,932
Kazuya-san?

257
00:15:29,932 --> 00:15:31,018
Is it something urgent?

258
00:15:31,018 --> 00:15:32,671
Then hop on!

259
00:15:32,671 --> 00:15:33,759
Thank you

260
00:15:54,452 --> 00:15:56,214
Hey, today as a special event at Live House

261
00:15:56,214 --> 00:15:59,179
Sanbo Master is releasing their new song!

262
00:15:59,179 --> 00:16:01,087
It is the song to cheer on

263
00:16:01,087 --> 00:16:04,615
Densha Otoko on A-channel!

264
00:16:04,615 --> 00:16:07,205
Then Sanbo Master's "To the invisible Densha Otoko"

265
00:16:07,205 --> 00:16:09,565
Shout love and give courage!

266
00:16:09,565 --> 00:16:13,217
I don't know your name!

267
00:16:13,217 --> 00:16:14,810
I don't know your face!

268
00:16:16,932 --> 00:16:19,443
I might even be your friend!

269
00:16:19,443 --> 00:16:21,514
I will sing to you

270
00:16:21,514 --> 00:16:25,978
The world calls that love!

271
00:16:31,384 --> 00:16:38,240
涙のかすなかあかともったら
If the light hidden in your tears is turned on

272
00:16:38,240 --> 00:16:45,289
君の目の前であたためてた事話すのさ
I will talk about warm things in front of your eyes

273
00:16:45,289 --> 00:16:48,307
それでも僕等声が
Even then if our voices

274
00:16:48,307 --> 00:16:49,853
乾いてゆくだけなら
Go dry

275
00:16:49,853 --> 00:16:52,064
[Densha Confess!]
乾いてゆくだけなら
Go dry

276
00:16:52,064 --> 00:16:53,107
[Densha Confess!]
朝が来るまでせめて
At least until the morning comes

277
00:16:53,107 --> 00:16:56,008
朝が来るまでせめて
At least until the morning comes

278
00:16:56,008 --> 00:16:59,381
誰かと歌いたいんだ
I want to sing with someone!

279
00:16:59,381 --> 00:17:06,241
昨日のあなたがうそだと言うなら
If you say you were fake yesterday

280
00:17:06,241 --> 00:17:12,255
昨日の景色を捨てちまうだけだ
I will only forget about yesterday's scene

281
00:17:12,255 --> 00:17:15,800
新しい日々をつなぐのは
The things connecting the new days

282
00:17:15,800 --> 00:17:18,585
新しい日々と僕なのさ
Are new days and myself!

283
00:17:18,585 --> 00:17:22,666
僕はなぜか確かめ合う
I check it for some reason

284
00:17:22,666 --> 00:17:26,080
世界じゃそれを愛と呼ぶんだぜ！
The world calls that love!

285
00:17:26,080 --> 00:17:28,391
心の声をつなぐのは
The thing that connects our heart's voices

286
00:17:28,391 --> 00:17:29,498
Hey, listen to the Japanese Broadcast
心の声をつなぐのは
The thing that connects our heart's voices

287
00:17:29,498 --> 00:17:30,133
Hey, listen to the Japanese Broadcast
これほど怖いものだとは
I didn't know that would be this scary!

288
00:17:30,133 --> 00:17:32,318
The song for Densha Otoko is on!
これほど怖いものだとは
I didn't know that would be this scary!

289
00:17:32,318 --> 00:17:33,500
The song for Densha Otoko is on!
君と僕が声を合わす
Together in one voice

290
00:17:33,500 --> 00:17:36,159
君と僕が声を合わす
Together in one voice

291
00:17:36,159 --> 00:17:41,890
今までの過去なんてなかったかのように
As if the past until now never existed

292
00:17:41,890 --> 00:17:44,323
歌いだすんだ！
I sing!

293
00:17:44,323 --> 00:17:45,778
It is a good song

294
00:17:45,778 --> 00:17:46,531
I cry too much these days



295
00:17:46,531 --> 00:17:47,150
I cry too much these days
僕等はいずれ誰かを疑っちまうから
Because we start doubting each other

296
00:17:47,150 --> 00:17:49,056
I hope Densha and Hermes-san are listening to this
僕等はいずれ誰かを疑っちまうから
Because we start doubting each other

297
00:17:49,056 --> 00:17:51,651
I feel like even we are getting encouragement
僕等はいずれ誰かを疑っちまうから
Because we start doubting each other

298
00:17:51,651 --> 00:17:54,432
Our role is to wait for Densha until he comes back
せめて今まだけ美しい歌を歌うのさ
At least, for now, I will sing a beautiful song!

299
00:17:54,432 --> 00:17:56,893
There is a high chance that Hermes-san still hasn't read this forum
せめて今まだけ美しい歌を歌うのさ
At least, for now, I will sing a beautiful song!

300
00:17:56,893 --> 00:17:57,697
Very high!
せめて今まだけ美しい歌を歌うのさ
At least, for now, I will sing a beautiful song!

301
00:17:57,697 --> 00:17:58,415
They usually don't read
せめて今まだけ美しい歌を歌うのさ
At least, for now, I will sing a beautiful song!

302
00:17:58,415 --> 00:18:00,899
Please, if you read!
せめて今まだけ美しい歌を歌うのさ
At least, for now, I will sing a beautiful song!

303
00:18:00,899 --> 00:18:03,717
Hermes-san! Please go to the secret place!
悲しい言葉では
Through sad words

304
00:18:05,105 --> 00:18:06,053
Please stop here

305
00:18:06,053 --> 00:18:09,159
何も変わらないんだぜ
Nothing changes

306
00:18:09,159 --> 00:18:10,163
Thank you

307
00:18:10,163 --> 00:18:13,800
奴らが何をしたって言うんだ
What did they do!

308
00:18:13,800 --> 00:18:13,951
奴らが何をしたって言うんだ
What did they do!

309
00:18:13,951 --> 00:18:17,538
Then now, it is the climax!
昨日の貴方が裏切りの人なら
If you were a traitor yesterday

310
00:18:17,538 --> 00:18:21,040
昨日の貴方が裏切りの人なら
If you were a traitor yesterday

311
00:18:21,040 --> 00:18:23,804
昨日の景色を
The scene from yesterday

312
00:18:32,177 --> 00:18:33,701
This is Yamada-san's

313
00:18:51,756 --> 00:18:53,537
Aoyama-san's house

314
00:18:57,996 --> 00:18:59,852
Um... This is Yamada

315
00:18:59,852 --> 00:19:04,213
I am at the hospital where Saori was moved to, but she is not here

316
00:19:04,213 --> 00:19:07,402
Huh? Are you confusing something?

317
00:19:07,402 --> 00:19:09,533
My sister just went out

318
00:19:09,533 --> 00:19:12,724
Oh really?

319
00:19:12,724 --> 00:19:15,005
Her expression suddenly changed and she hurriedly left the house

320
00:19:15,005 --> 00:19:17,125
Hurriedly?

321
00:19:17,125 --> 00:19:19,034
Ah, okay

322
00:19:19,034 --> 00:19:20,648
Um...

323
00:19:20,648 --> 00:19:21,979
Yes

324
00:19:21,979 --> 00:19:25,293
I read the forum

325
00:19:27,615 --> 00:19:28,841
Yes

326
00:19:28,841 --> 00:19:31,157
About sister...

327
00:19:31,157 --> 00:19:33,193
I realized...

328
00:19:33,193 --> 00:19:35,056
That you were sincere

329
00:19:35,911 --> 00:19:36,810
Yes

330
00:19:37,732 --> 00:19:40,347
Sorry for hitting you

331
00:19:40,347 --> 00:19:43,888
She will understand you

332
00:19:43,888 --> 00:19:45,272
My sister...

333
00:19:45,967 --> 00:19:47,920
Thank you

334
00:19:47,920 --> 00:19:48,853
Excuse me

335
00:19:57,989 --> 00:19:59,982
This is the secret place

336
00:20:04,078 --> 00:20:09,461
I think Yamada ran away thinking he doesn't deserve her

337
00:20:11,363 --> 00:20:12,705
Ah, Saori

338
00:20:14,456 --> 00:20:16,184
All right!

339
00:20:16,184 --> 00:20:18,488
All is going according my plan

340
00:20:28,377 --> 00:20:30,104
[Densha Otoko! Come back to the forum!]

341
00:20:34,322 --> 00:20:38,445
長いキスの途中で
During the long kiss

342
00:20:38,445 --> 00:20:41,228
Fu-Fu さりげなく
Fu-Fu As if it were nothing

343
00:20:41,228 --> 00:20:45,001
首飾りを外した
You undid her necklace

344
00:20:45,001 --> 00:20:48,375
Fu-Fu 指さきで
Fu-Fu With your fingers

345
00:20:48,375 --> 00:20:55,192
友達の領城から
From the zone of friendship

346
00:20:55,192 --> 00:21:04,054
はみだした君の青いハイヒール
The blue high heel that came out of

347
00:21:04,054 --> 00:21:10,709
誰か Romantic 止めて Romantic
Someone Romantic Stop Romantic

348
00:21:10,709 --> 00:21:17,232
胸が胸が苦しくなる
My heart, my heart is becoming unbearable

349
00:21:17,232 --> 00:21:23,974
惑う瞳甘く溺れて
I am fallen into your wavering eyes

350
00:21:23,974 --> 00:21:28,726
Hold me tight せつなさは止まらない
Hold me tight sadness doesn't stop

351
00:21:28,726 --> 00:21:29,472
Yes

352
00:21:29,472 --> 00:21:31,741
Saori, I found Yamada

353
00:21:32,116 --> 00:21:33,375
He is on the station platform

354
00:21:33,375 --> 00:21:34,694
Come right now!

355
00:21:34,694 --> 00:21:35,665
Ok

356
00:21:48,753 --> 00:21:49,798
Where is Yamada-san?

357
00:21:49,798 --> 00:21:51,893
Yamada said...

358
00:21:51,893 --> 00:21:56,339
He doesn't deserve you... and left

359
00:21:59,090 --> 00:21:59,970
Saori

360
00:22:01,330 --> 00:22:02,836
Let's get married

361
00:22:17,829 --> 00:22:20,592
He told me before he left

362
00:22:21,453 --> 00:22:22,471
"Take good care of her"

363
00:22:23,272 --> 00:22:25,282
To make Saori happy

364
00:22:26,944 --> 00:22:27,795
Kazuya-san

365
00:22:28,240 --> 00:22:29,494
Saori

366
00:22:34,715 --> 00:22:36,593
Why am I hugging him!?

367
00:22:42,403 --> 00:22:43,458
Saori!

368
00:22:55,565 --> 00:22:56,461
Yamada said...

369
00:22:58,363 --> 00:23:02,445
He doesn't deserve you... and left

370
00:23:10,398 --> 00:23:12,175
Saori

371
00:23:12,175 --> 00:23:13,683
Let's get married

372
00:23:24,307 --> 00:23:26,446
Aoyama-san...

373
00:23:29,828 --> 00:23:30,969
Kazuya-san...

374
00:23:33,664 --> 00:23:34,205
Thank you

375
00:23:34,205 --> 00:23:36,123
No

376
00:23:36,536 --> 00:23:38,178
Yamada

377
00:23:38,178 --> 00:23:39,395
Take good care of her

378
00:23:39,826 --> 00:23:42,848
Make Saori happy

379
00:23:43,747 --> 00:23:45,902
If I knew this would happen, I should have forced her to come with me

380
00:23:45,902 --> 00:23:47,096
Wow look at this!

381
00:23:47,096 --> 00:23:47,758
Wow, what is happening?

382
00:23:47,758 --> 00:23:50,503
Super lucky!

383
00:23:50,503 --> 00:23:52,765
Wait

384
00:23:52,765 --> 00:23:54,870
You guys are!

385
00:23:54,870 --> 00:23:55,813
Uh oh!

386
00:23:55,813 --> 00:23:57,198
The diamond!

387
00:23:59,516 --> 00:23:59,912
Sorry

388
00:23:59,912 --> 00:24:01,054
What are you doing, bastard?

389
00:24:01,054 --> 00:24:02,432
This is an emergency

390
00:24:03,857 --> 00:24:06,470
Stop right there!

391
00:24:06,470 --> 00:24:08,542
That is my Lanebo

392
00:24:08,542 --> 00:24:09,829
Stop!

393
00:24:09,829 --> 00:24:11,915
Shit

394
00:24:11,915 --> 00:24:13,929
I will follow you with my Lanebo II

395
00:24:21,330 --> 00:24:22,868
What are you doing!

396
00:24:22,868 --> 00:24:24,421
Where are you taking it!

397
00:24:24,990 --> 00:24:26,339
Ring!

398
00:24:26,339 --> 00:24:28,105
Lanebos!

399
00:24:28,105 --> 00:24:30,493
Hermes!

400
00:24:30,493 --> 00:24:32,701
Come back!

401
00:24:43,854 --> 00:24:45,412
Um...

402
00:24:45,412 --> 00:24:47,089
Finally...

403
00:24:47,089 --> 00:24:48,620
We meet

404
00:24:50,306 --> 00:24:51,678
Densha Otoko-san

405
00:24:58,751 --> 00:25:00,082
Densha...

406
00:25:00,082 --> 00:25:01,512
Still not returned...?

407
00:25:05,563 --> 00:25:11,329
I stayed up overnight on this forum

408
00:25:11,329 --> 00:25:13,601
Is everyone awake?

409
00:25:15,923 --> 00:25:18,570
I am not fully conscious, but for Densha...

410
00:25:18,570 --> 00:25:19,175
I will wait

411
00:25:19,175 --> 00:25:22,676
Sleepy sleepy sleesleesleepy....

412
00:25:22,676 --> 00:25:25,934
This is too much... I am gonna sleep for a bit

413
00:25:25,934 --> 00:25:28,667
Our warriors are dropping one by one!

414
00:25:28,667 --> 00:25:31,698
And one single man carrying the burden!

415
00:25:31,698 --> 00:25:32,224
Sleep...

416
00:25:32,224 --> 00:25:34,720
Whatever happens I want to say "Welcome"

417
00:25:34,720 --> 00:25:36,004
So I am awake...

418
00:25:36,004 --> 00:25:37,667
But so sleepy...

419
00:25:37,667 --> 00:25:39,695
Ah, it is over now

420
00:25:40,398 --> 00:25:42,179
I just came back

421
00:25:44,820 --> 00:25:46,126
Is it Densha?

422
00:25:46,126 --> 00:25:47,591
Really, is it Densha?

423
00:25:48,545 --> 00:25:54,624
He's back!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!

424
00:25:55,232 --> 00:25:58,621
How long it will take to write what happened today...

425
00:26:00,025 --> 00:26:00,630
Sleepy...

426
00:26:00,630 --> 00:26:03,892
I know you are sleepy, but do your best to write

427
00:26:03,892 --> 00:26:04,427
Right!

428
00:26:04,427 --> 00:26:06,879
We stayed up all night waiting for you!

429
00:26:06,879 --> 00:26:09,912
I win for waiting for 15 hours!

430
00:26:09,912 --> 00:26:11,496
You guys did wait for a long time

431
00:26:11,496 --> 00:26:12,893
Can I start with the result?

432
00:26:12,893 --> 00:26:13,581
No no

433
00:26:13,581 --> 00:26:14,619
The main theme comes at the end!

434
00:26:14,619 --> 00:26:15,188
Please

435
00:26:15,188 --> 00:26:18,117
Kill us slow~ly and painfully!

436
00:26:18,117 --> 00:26:19,902
Result at the last station, please~!

437
00:26:19,902 --> 00:26:21,540
Let's go!

438
00:26:21,540 --> 00:26:23,739
My heart rate is really dangerous now!

439
00:26:23,739 --> 00:26:26,011
I am trembling with my computer desk

440
00:26:26,011 --> 00:26:27,663
Finally, this thread's strongest and biggest...

441
00:26:27,663 --> 00:26:30,300
And the legendary final attack is...

442
00:26:30,300 --> 00:26:31,591
Starting

443
00:26:32,415 --> 00:26:33,851
Then I will start writing

444
00:26:34,577 --> 00:26:39,192
As promised, I was waiting for her at the place

445
00:26:39,192 --> 00:26:41,751
Practicing confessing to her

446
00:26:41,751 --> 00:26:42,585
Then

447
00:26:42,585 --> 00:26:45,506
Someone told me that Hermes-san lost consciousness

448
00:26:46,910 --> 00:26:48,469
It was false information

449
00:26:48,469 --> 00:26:50,840
And I hurried back to the place

450
00:26:52,367 --> 00:26:57,260
And coincidentally, I met Hermes-san at the station

451
00:26:57,260 --> 00:26:58,801
It is so dramatic~

452
00:26:58,801 --> 00:27:01,766
It looks like it was to let them meet there!

453
00:27:01,766 --> 00:27:02,617
Nice directing!

454
00:27:02,617 --> 00:27:05,036
Good job for the false informer!

455
00:27:05,490 --> 00:27:06,621
You're welcome

456
00:27:06,906 --> 00:27:10,398
She and I decided to go to our secret place

457
00:27:11,396 --> 00:27:15,420
Hermes-san didn't say anything while we were going there

458
00:27:15,838 --> 00:27:17,429
Of course, neither did I...

459
00:27:18,719 --> 00:27:22,490
And then, the silence was broken

460
00:27:23,711 --> 00:27:28,088
I read the forum

461
00:27:28,088 --> 00:27:29,115
Yes...

462
00:27:31,080 --> 00:27:33,418
After reading the forum...

463
00:27:35,096 --> 00:27:40,999
I understood your need to lean on people on the forum

464
00:27:42,730 --> 00:27:44,579
And

465
00:27:45,675 --> 00:27:49,627
I understood your perceptions of me

466
00:28:02,810 --> 00:28:04,579
I was happy

467
00:28:06,006 --> 00:28:07,330
Yes?!

468
00:28:07,330 --> 00:28:09,188
Yamada-san...

469
00:28:09,464 --> 00:28:11,993
Thinking about me in such ways...

470
00:28:12,607 --> 00:28:14,297
I was so happy!

471
00:28:18,986 --> 00:28:23,042
All the people at the forum are all so nice

472
00:28:25,376 --> 00:28:26,311
Yes

473
00:28:38,461 --> 00:28:40,068
So...

474
00:28:43,161 --> 00:28:45,517
I came to...

475
00:28:45,517 --> 00:28:48,526
Formally listen to what is in your heart...

476
00:29:03,353 --> 00:29:05,976
Can you...

477
00:29:05,976 --> 00:29:07,379
Can you... tell me?

478
00:29:15,971 --> 00:29:17,093
Yes...

479
00:29:18,374 --> 00:29:20,679
Yes yes yes

480
00:29:20,679 --> 00:29:21,468
Hermes-san moe~!

481
00:29:21,468 --> 00:29:24,667
Telling Densha-san's heart starts now?

482
00:29:24,667 --> 00:29:25,785
This is confessing time!

483
00:29:25,785 --> 00:29:28,128
Ahhhhhhh now all the Densha cheering at once!

484
00:29:28,128 --> 00:29:32,264
The attack that will make shelters useless is impending

485
00:29:32,264 --> 00:29:34,473
The feelings from finishing an RPG game for the first time

486
00:29:34,473 --> 00:29:36,176
Have been revived!

487
00:29:36,176 --> 00:29:38,946
Everyone, I will be obliterated by this attack

488
00:29:38,946 --> 00:29:40,535
So let me say this now

489
00:29:40,535 --> 00:29:42,277
I like you all so much!

490
00:29:42,277 --> 00:29:42,682
Uooooo!!!

491
00:29:42,682 --> 00:29:44,641
I am going to run in the streets naked!

492
00:29:44,641 --> 00:29:47,482
I am so excited I can't speak... !@#!@#$!@##@!$$#@!

493
00:29:47,482 --> 00:29:51,280
Bring it on!!!!

494
00:29:53,017 --> 00:29:56,489
The silence continued for a while

495
00:29:57,266 --> 00:30:01,747
I couldn't say a word because I was so nervous

496
00:30:13,644 --> 00:30:17,494
I.I.I..I have something important to say

497
00:30:18,146 --> 00:30:19,063
Yes

498
00:30:30,101 --> 00:30:36,973
Everything was shining when I was with you

499
00:30:38,306 --> 00:30:41,058
Until now...

500
00:30:41,058 --> 00:30:42,556
My...

501
00:30:42,556 --> 00:30:45,114
Good times...

502
00:30:45,114 --> 00:30:47,825
The scene of the town that never changed...

503
00:30:49,280 --> 00:30:53,498
And being so wretched myself...

504
00:30:54,606 --> 00:30:56,332
Everything...

505
00:30:56,332 --> 00:30:57,719
Magically...

506
00:30:58,449 --> 00:31:01,459
All started to shine

507
00:31:03,695 --> 00:31:06,034
Because Aoyama-san was...

508
00:31:06,579 --> 00:31:07,440
To me...

509
00:31:09,157 --> 00:31:11,370
The light in my life

510
00:31:16,111 --> 00:31:18,669
From Aoyama-san...

511
00:31:19,084 --> 00:31:20,343
I have received...

512
00:31:21,763 --> 00:31:23,007
So many precious things...

513
00:31:29,962 --> 00:31:31,474
But...

514
00:31:33,377 --> 00:31:34,579
I.....

515
00:31:35,809 --> 00:31:37,479
Didn't have anything...

516
00:31:39,562 --> 00:31:41,706
Couldn't do anything for you...

517
00:31:46,650 --> 00:31:47,945
But...

518
00:31:50,312 --> 00:31:51,426
But...!

519
00:31:55,641 --> 00:32:00,751
My heart cares for Aoyama-san!

520
00:32:03,871 --> 00:32:08,165
Compared to anyone's...

521
00:32:08,165 --> 00:32:10,788
Compared to anyone's... there can be no less!

522
00:32:24,208 --> 00:32:25,704
I.....

523
00:32:27,751 --> 00:32:29,121
I......

524
00:32:44,854 --> 00:32:46,138
You can do it

525
00:33:02,842 --> 00:33:04,701
I....

526
00:33:07,707 --> 00:33:09,588
I.....!

527
00:33:13,104 --> 00:33:16,473
A.A.. Aoyama-san...

528
00:33:24,576 --> 00:33:26,041
L.L..Like Aoyama-san!

529
00:33:37,489 --> 00:33:40,112
I also...

530
00:33:40,112 --> 00:33:42,993
Like...

531
00:33:42,993 --> 00:33:44,568
Yamada-san!

532
00:33:53,416 --> 00:33:55,795
So

533
00:33:55,795 --> 00:33:58,357
Even from now on...

534
00:33:58,357 --> 00:34:00,899
Will you always be with me?

535
00:34:04,699 --> 00:34:05,755
Yes!!

536
00:34:08,106 --> 00:34:15,658
Yes!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!

537
00:34:16,203 --> 00:34:18,357
Thank you...

538
00:34:20,627 --> 00:34:22,885
Always...

539
00:34:22,885 --> 00:34:25,283
Always...

540
00:34:25,283 --> 00:34:29,130
Be with me...

541
00:34:29,130 --> 00:34:33,173
Yes

542
00:34:34,294 --> 00:34:36,678
Sorry

543
00:34:36,678 --> 00:34:39,012
I...

544
00:34:39,012 --> 00:34:41,422
Really...

545
00:34:41,422 --> 00:34:43,877
Like... Aoyama-san...

546
00:34:55,588 --> 00:34:56,770
Sorry

547
00:34:57,595 --> 00:34:59,244
Women were

548
00:34:59,244 --> 00:35:02,520
Never nice

549
00:35:02,520 --> 00:35:04,619
To me...

550
00:35:16,788 --> 00:35:20,483
I started crying with you...

551
00:35:41,636 --> 00:35:47,381
Is this the kiss!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!

552
00:35:55,465 --> 00:35:58,724
After saying I like you...

553
00:35:58,724 --> 00:36:00,764
I like you even more

554
00:36:13,490 --> 00:36:14,707
This is enough!

555
00:36:14,707 --> 00:36:16,872
I don't have any regrets in my life now!

556
00:36:16,872 --> 00:36:18,851
I think I will cry with him

557
00:36:18,851 --> 00:36:21,447
I am already crying!

558
00:36:22,150 --> 00:36:23,897
My tears are

559
00:36:23,897 --> 00:36:25,671
Glowing like holy water!

560
00:36:25,671 --> 00:36:26,355
Through tears

561
00:36:26,355 --> 00:36:28,799
I am dehydrating

562
00:36:28,799 --> 00:36:32,700
I can't cry when my dad comes, so I am gonna cry out now

563
00:36:32,700 --> 00:36:34,523
Spring has come~

564
00:36:34,523 --> 00:36:36,181
Spring has come~

565
00:36:36,181 --> 00:36:38,777
Where has it come?

566
00:36:38,777 --> 00:36:40,292
To Densha~

567
00:36:40,292 --> 00:36:42,185
To Hermes-san~

568
00:36:42,185 --> 00:36:45,450
To single men! Benoist!

569
00:36:45,450 --> 00:36:46,981
Densha, congratulations

570
00:36:46,981 --> 00:36:50,218
And everyone at this thread, good job

571
00:36:50,218 --> 00:36:51,471
You guys are the best!

572
00:36:51,471 --> 00:36:54,023
Are you together? Are you together now?

573
00:36:54,023 --> 00:36:55,846
You are this year's MVP

574
00:36:55,846 --> 00:36:57,942
Now hobbies don't matter

575
00:36:57,942 --> 00:37:01,251
It is real now, going out with each other

576
00:37:01,251 --> 00:37:01,909
Good girl!

577
00:37:01,909 --> 00:37:02,794
Hermes-san

578
00:37:02,794 --> 00:37:05,128
Otaku or single men...

579
00:37:05,128 --> 00:37:07,418
Be happy all you want!

580
00:37:07,418 --> 00:37:08,475
I am crying even more

581
00:37:08,475 --> 00:37:10,253
I am also crying

582
00:37:10,253 --> 00:37:11,569
All of Densha's insecure feelings...

583
00:37:11,569 --> 00:37:13,427
And the life from now...

584
00:37:13,427 --> 00:37:17,325
They were all for the happiness with Hermes-san!

585
00:37:18,698 --> 00:37:21,444
Thinking about it made me cry too

586
00:37:21,444 --> 00:37:22,029
Relax

587
00:37:22,029 --> 00:37:24,141
I am also crying

588
00:37:24,141 --> 00:37:26,327
I never cried this much for other people

589
00:37:26,327 --> 00:37:27,521
Some liquid came out of my eyes!

590
00:37:27,521 --> 00:37:29,067
But no one is wiping them for me!

591
00:37:29,067 --> 00:37:31,778
Are there girls like this in Tokyo?

592
00:37:31,778 --> 00:37:33,217
Is this the Japanese Dream!?

593
00:37:33,217 --> 00:37:36,242
A kiss with a cute and naive sister?

594
00:37:36,242 --> 00:37:37,740
Is it there? Is it still there?

595
00:37:37,740 --> 00:37:40,362
Is there still something I can cry for?

596
00:37:40,362 --> 00:37:42,411
Hermes-san is not the end, right?

597
00:37:43,030 --> 00:37:44,752
Finally, it came! The final weapon!

598
00:37:44,752 --> 00:37:46,155
And then I look back to find nothing

599
00:37:46,155 --> 00:37:49,533
Am I still... alive?

600
00:37:49,533 --> 00:37:50,904
Medic!!

601
00:37:50,904 --> 00:37:52,374
You are so awesome!

602
00:37:52,374 --> 00:37:52,989
Congratulations

603
00:37:52,989 --> 00:37:54,353
Please tell me when you guys get married

604
00:37:54,353 --> 00:37:57,786
Is there anything left to report? Sergeant Densha!

605
00:38:02,067 --> 00:38:03,276
There is still more...

606
00:38:03,276 --> 00:38:05,108
But it is time for Mina

607
00:38:05,108 --> 00:38:06,398
So I will continue later

608
00:38:06,937 --> 00:38:08,430
You are going to go watch Ani!

609
00:38:08,430 --> 00:38:11,277
Ending here! So perfect!

610
00:38:11,277 --> 00:38:12,300
That's you, Densha!

611
00:38:12,300 --> 00:38:13,962
You are Ani-otaku of Ani-otakus

612
00:38:13,962 --> 00:38:15,379
Hey, what is Mina?

613
00:38:15,379 --> 00:38:17,069
Lunar Rabbit Weapon Mina

614
00:38:17,069 --> 00:38:17,887
Look it up for yourself from there

615
00:38:17,887 --> 00:38:22,675
I like you!

616
00:38:22,675 --> 00:38:25,936
うつむいた笑顔が
The face full of shininess

617
00:38:25,936 --> 00:38:28,613
空に舞う
Is dancing in the sky

618
00:38:29,785 --> 00:38:33,472
You met her thanks to me... Damn it, Densha!

619
00:38:33,472 --> 00:38:35,205
Stopping for Anime! Right here!

620
00:38:35,205 --> 00:38:37,683
Think about it from my point of view!

621
00:38:37,683 --> 00:38:40,284
Got me all excited...

622
00:38:40,284 --> 00:38:43,016
I will beat you up next time I see you!

623
00:38:43,016 --> 00:38:45,835
Ah... I wanna do it too!

624
00:38:45,835 --> 00:38:47,783
Destined love

625
00:38:49,750 --> 00:38:51,093
You!

626
00:38:51,093 --> 00:38:53,122
Why are you using the cell phone!

627
00:38:53,122 --> 00:38:55,749
You wanna touch there too?

628
00:38:55,749 --> 00:38:58,777
Come on! Touch it!

629
00:39:03,802 --> 00:39:06,618
Trying to do it with me? You are 10 years too old!

630
00:39:06,618 --> 00:39:07,887
Stop it!

631
00:39:07,887 --> 00:39:09,271
She wants you to stop!

632
00:39:11,294 --> 00:39:13,099
So scared~!

633
00:39:14,685 --> 00:39:17,338
What! I was getting beat up by that woman...

634
00:39:23,546 --> 00:39:24,323
Are you all right?

635
00:39:24,323 --> 00:39:25,774
Thank you

636
00:39:25,774 --> 00:39:26,798
Did we meet somewhere before?

637
00:39:26,798 --> 00:39:28,156
I was thinking the same thing

638
00:39:28,156 --> 00:39:29,511
Is this...

639
00:39:29,511 --> 00:39:30,834
Destiny?

640
00:39:31,431 --> 00:39:33,042
Please look forward to it!

641
00:39:35,629 --> 00:39:37,716
Nothing came into my head

642
00:39:51,340 --> 00:39:56,050
We left there just strolling around

643
00:39:57,120 --> 00:40:00,171
And we arrived at a park

644
00:40:01,106 --> 00:40:04,700
And we sat at an empty bench...

645
00:40:05,171 --> 00:40:09,420
But were we ever this close?

646
00:40:10,202 --> 00:40:12,779
No way...

647
00:40:12,779 --> 00:40:15,880
Suddenly he comes back!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!

648
00:40:15,880 --> 00:40:18,105
Suddenly he continues!!!!!!!!!!!

649
00:40:18,105 --> 00:40:21,323
An attack, shooting on the enemy territory during a ceasefire!

650
00:40:21,323 --> 00:40:25,089
I like Densha who continues as if nothing happened in between!

651
00:40:29,082 --> 00:40:30,288
This...

652
00:40:30,288 --> 00:40:32,504
I bought this for you from Italy

653
00:40:33,380 --> 00:40:34,185
Yes?

654
00:40:36,442 --> 00:40:38,428
Open it

655
00:40:38,982 --> 00:40:39,850
Okay

656
00:40:49,549 --> 00:40:52,833
Isn't this very expensive?

657
00:40:52,833 --> 00:40:54,991
Not really

658
00:40:55,895 --> 00:40:57,443
I am happy

659
00:40:57,443 --> 00:40:58,664
Wow, awesome

660
00:41:00,914 --> 00:41:02,236
Thank you

661
00:41:02,973 --> 00:41:04,207
Really

662
00:41:04,207 --> 00:41:05,832
Thank you

663
00:41:05,832 --> 00:41:07,315
No no...

664
00:41:07,315 --> 00:41:08,813
Try it on

665
00:41:10,444 --> 00:41:11,938
Okay

666
00:41:18,209 --> 00:41:19,715
Huh?

667
00:41:29,543 --> 00:41:31,331
Thank you

668
00:41:31,331 --> 00:41:32,740
It fits on you

669
00:41:33,792 --> 00:41:35,246
Thank you

670
00:41:37,027 --> 00:41:38,687
This is a paired necklace

671
00:41:54,473 --> 00:41:56,087
Huh?

672
00:41:56,087 --> 00:41:56,776
"A pair!! Yes!!!!!!"

673
00:41:56,776 --> 00:41:57,787
Or

674
00:41:57,787 --> 00:41:58,539
"Present!! Yes!!!!"

675
00:41:58,539 --> 00:42:01,886
Why aren't you guys saying those things?

676
00:42:01,886 --> 00:42:05,300
No, honestly I didn't think it would go this far

677
00:42:05,300 --> 00:42:08,020
My thought process really didn't follow it all

678
00:42:08,020 --> 00:42:10,872
I would say the enemy is too strong

679
00:42:10,872 --> 00:42:12,206
I am slowly getting mad!

680
00:42:12,206 --> 00:42:14,209
Can this really happen in real life?

681
00:42:14,209 --> 00:42:17,911
At least not in my life

682
00:42:20,381 --> 00:42:25,097
Now that I am finally all calm, I will tell you what I couldn't say until now

683
00:42:26,367 --> 00:42:28,400
Why we started liking each other

684
00:42:29,715 --> 00:42:31,638
And our thoughts then

685
00:42:33,462 --> 00:42:35,203
We were talking and talking about them

686
00:42:35,203 --> 00:42:37,798
But things to talk about never ran out

687
00:42:40,877 --> 00:42:42,691
And I realized something extraordinary

688
00:42:44,887 --> 00:42:47,984
I am missing one of my contact lenses

689
00:42:48,442 --> 00:42:52,436
Something felt weird since a while ago

690
00:42:52,436 --> 00:42:54,178
Probably that's it

691
00:42:54,178 --> 00:42:56,041
Then we should go looking for it

692
00:42:59,704 --> 00:43:02,662
It is okay, I was going to throw it away after using it

693
00:43:02,662 --> 00:43:04,329
Really?

694
00:43:04,329 --> 00:43:05,532
Yes

695
00:43:16,786 --> 00:43:19,042
I can't see anything now

696
00:43:22,395 --> 00:43:25,254
You can't see my face either?

697
00:43:25,254 --> 00:43:26,465
I...

698
00:43:26,465 --> 00:43:28,329
Could actually see her face...

699
00:43:29,781 --> 00:43:31,439
I... can't see...

700
00:43:35,154 --> 00:43:37,308
Now can you see?

701
00:43:42,060 --> 00:43:44,952
You sneaky bastard~~!!!!!!

702
00:43:44,952 --> 00:43:48,223
Hermes-san! This guy is bullshitting!

703
00:43:48,223 --> 00:43:51,531
He is attacking without declaring war! You bastard! Are you trying to kill me?!

704
00:43:51,531 --> 00:43:53,851
Wait, you guys...

705
00:43:53,851 --> 00:43:55,950
Is it just me getting this weird feeling?

706
00:43:55,950 --> 00:43:57,952
I... can't defend by myself!

707
00:43:57,952 --> 00:43:59,740
A bombing is impending

708
00:43:59,740 --> 00:44:01,387
The last blow is coming!

709
00:44:01,387 --> 00:44:03,668
Run away! Run away!

710
00:44:05,472 --> 00:44:08,386
It is Densha-san's turn

711
00:44:09,768 --> 00:44:11,288
Okay...

712
00:44:20,142 --> 00:44:21,909
Not there...

713
00:44:26,900 --> 00:44:29,215
Here...

714
00:44:38,521 --> 00:44:41,149
Was it for two or three seconds?

715
00:44:42,211 --> 00:44:48,160
I didn't know such soft things existed in this world

716
00:44:49,705 --> 00:44:54,968
For the first time, I saw her face with confidence

717
00:44:54,968 --> 00:45:00,425
I could even recognize my reflection in her eyes

718
00:45:00,425 --> 00:45:10,150
The bombing has come!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!

719
00:45:10,150 --> 00:45:13,739
These love-love things...

720
00:45:13,739 --> 00:45:15,945
Good bye

721
00:45:17,258 --> 00:45:19,068
It is all over

722
00:45:19,068 --> 00:45:20,128
After that...

723
00:45:20,128 --> 00:45:22,187
She whispered...

724
00:45:22,187 --> 00:45:25,410
"You are so attractive, Densha-san"

725
00:45:26,184 --> 00:45:29,142
In a low voice

726
00:45:29,142 --> 00:45:31,045
And kissed again

727
00:45:31,045 --> 00:45:34,918
My Hermes Castle is falling down!

728
00:45:34,918 --> 00:45:37,392
When you hear you are attractive...

729
00:45:41,121 --> 00:45:43,392
And then our lips touched each other some more times...

730
00:45:44,944 --> 00:45:48,116
And we did the adult's kiss too!

731
00:45:52,267 --> 00:45:53,335
Wait!

732
00:45:53,335 --> 00:45:57,506
What do you mean by "adult's kiss"!

733
00:45:59,137 --> 00:46:00,890
Everyone is getting a blow from behind!

734
00:46:01,744 --> 00:46:03,967
This is all for the report

735
00:46:03,967 --> 00:46:06,036
Everyone, thank you

736
00:46:06,036 --> 00:46:07,353
I will sleep for now

737
00:46:07,353 --> 00:46:09,268
I will write again later

738
00:46:35,565 --> 00:46:36,364
No violence!

739
00:46:36,364 --> 00:46:37,742
You can't go out with me? What do you mean!

740
00:46:37,742 --> 00:46:39,515
No... I mean...

741
00:46:39,515 --> 00:46:41,122
Tell me to my face, if you are a man

742
00:46:41,122 --> 00:46:45,363
Um... your ankle is not moe~ enough...

743
00:46:45,363 --> 00:46:47,964
Your ankle is not my type

744
00:46:47,964 --> 00:46:50,318
Are you trying to say that my leg is fat?

745
00:46:50,318 --> 00:46:52,597
Yes... if you are talking about the ankle...

746
00:46:52,597 --> 00:46:55,891
I usually reject people like you

747
00:46:55,891 --> 00:46:57,191
Why was I ever going for you?

748
00:46:57,191 --> 00:46:58,746
I am ashamed of myself

749
00:47:02,586 --> 00:47:04,886
Sorry for calling you to come out

750
00:47:04,886 --> 00:47:05,846
Actually

751
00:47:05,846 --> 00:47:09,833
I wanted to say something before listening to Saori

752
00:47:09,833 --> 00:47:11,164
Sorry

753
00:47:12,214 --> 00:47:12,888
I...

754
00:47:12,888 --> 00:47:16,172
So many times forced my opinion on you without thinking about your feelings

755
00:47:16,660 --> 00:47:20,955
I thought I just wanted to protect you

756
00:47:20,955 --> 00:47:23,068
But... it wasn't

757
00:47:23,068 --> 00:47:28,275
Because I was afraid of you falling in love, I forgot about something important

758
00:47:29,558 --> 00:47:31,421
No, that's not true

759
00:47:31,421 --> 00:47:34,911
Because Kaho was really caring for me

760
00:47:34,911 --> 00:47:37,876
Now I can go out with Yamada-san

761
00:47:38,538 --> 00:47:39,382
Saori

762
00:47:39,382 --> 00:47:41,813
I wanted to talk about Yamada-san

763
00:47:41,813 --> 00:47:43,772
But I guess you already know

764
00:47:45,681 --> 00:47:47,133
Congratulations

765
00:47:47,897 --> 00:47:49,518
Hermes-san

766
00:47:52,698 --> 00:47:53,980
Ah, brother!

767
00:47:53,980 --> 00:47:56,379
Don't put figures here

768
00:47:58,688 --> 00:47:59,754
Hey Tsuyoshi!

769
00:47:59,754 --> 00:48:01,553
Sit down!

770
00:48:01,553 --> 00:48:02,714
Matilda-san!

771
00:48:03,684 --> 00:48:06,269
Huh? What the hell are you talking about?

772
00:48:06,269 --> 00:48:08,482
What? It was you, mom. The voice was so similar...

773
00:48:08,482 --> 00:48:10,377
I have something to say, so sit down

774
00:48:13,340 --> 00:48:14,611
Actually

775
00:48:14,611 --> 00:48:18,044
There is something you should congratulate your mommy about

776
00:48:18,044 --> 00:48:18,775
I got it~

777
00:48:18,775 --> 00:48:21,215
Eh? Congratulations!

778
00:48:21,215 --> 00:48:21,722
When...?

779
00:48:21,722 --> 00:48:25,017
When I stayed here last month for one night~

780
00:48:25,017 --> 00:48:25,694
Yes yes

781
00:48:25,694 --> 00:48:28,338
Dad also worked a little hard for it

782
00:48:28,338 --> 00:48:30,415
So full of energy~!

783
00:48:30,415 --> 00:48:31,272
What are you saying!

784
00:48:31,272 --> 00:48:33,650
Hey, what do you want to name the baby?

785
00:48:33,650 --> 00:48:36,097
Honey, it is too early for that

786
00:48:36,097 --> 00:48:39,675
I was thinking about it just now, but if it is a girl

787
00:48:39,675 --> 00:48:40,984
Let's name her Matilda

788
00:48:40,984 --> 00:48:41,638
Agree!

789
00:48:41,638 --> 00:48:42,606
Agree!

790
00:48:42,606 --> 00:48:43,750
Matilda, sounds good

791
00:48:43,750 --> 00:48:47,244
Matilda?!? How do you write that in Kanji?

792
00:48:53,480 --> 00:48:56,579
Sorry, I am a little late

793
00:48:56,579 --> 00:49:00,288
Hermes-san said "I wish everyday were Sunday"

794
00:49:00,288 --> 00:49:02,102
In the mail that she just sent

795
00:49:02,102 --> 00:49:03,808
I am so happy~

796
00:49:03,808 --> 00:49:05,676
Sorry but please say that kind of stuff in the Couple Zone

797
00:49:05,676 --> 00:49:07,447
Now ranting is over

798
00:49:07,447 --> 00:49:10,798
We are not that free to listen to your ranting forever

799
00:49:10,798 --> 00:49:14,528
Go away before this thread becomes a "1000 reply thread"

800
00:49:14,528 --> 00:49:18,121
Huh? Things seem a little cold here... Is it because of me?

801
00:49:18,121 --> 00:49:20,185
Densha, listen to me

802
00:49:20,185 --> 00:49:22,049
You are not a single man anymore

803
00:49:22,049 --> 00:49:24,154
Which means, it is time for you to graduate

804
00:49:24,154 --> 00:49:27,024
Now we will not look over you anymore

805
00:49:27,024 --> 00:49:29,814
I want you to stay, but I think it is time to say goodbye

806
00:49:29,814 --> 00:49:32,305
I... don't want to depart with you guys

807
00:49:32,995 --> 00:49:35,580
I will still show up

808
00:49:35,580 --> 00:49:38,676
So don't say such cold things

809
00:49:38,676 --> 00:49:40,186
I don't want to listen to you being weak

810
00:49:40,186 --> 00:49:42,244
Staying here only makes things uneasy

811
00:49:42,244 --> 00:49:44,881
This thread is only for single men

812
00:49:44,881 --> 00:49:47,918
There is no place for you here

813
00:49:49,943 --> 00:49:51,865
Why?

814
00:49:51,865 --> 00:49:54,106
Finally, we became companions

815
00:49:56,177 --> 00:49:59,062
That makes me feel lonely again

816
00:49:59,062 --> 00:50:01,803
We are saying this because we are your companions

817
00:50:01,803 --> 00:50:03,669
You must take a new step now

818
00:50:03,669 --> 00:50:05,144
You are not alone anymore

819
00:50:05,144 --> 00:50:06,012
Be strong!

820
00:50:06,012 --> 00:50:09,283
Who will protect Hermes-san if you don't protect her?

821
00:50:27,453 --> 00:50:34,386
[Densha Otoko! Come back to the forum!]

822
00:50:34,386 --> 00:50:38,996
[Densha Otoko-san! Come back to the forum!]

823
00:50:47,071 --> 00:50:50,054
All right

824
00:50:50,054 --> 00:50:51,948
I...

825
00:50:51,948 --> 00:50:53,220
Will leave

826
00:51:02,947 --> 00:51:04,092
Well said, Densha

827
00:51:04,092 --> 00:51:06,163
You won't have a problem even without us now

828
00:51:06,163 --> 00:51:08,710
Let's send him away with the last 300 replies!

829
00:51:08,710 --> 00:51:12,126
Everyone! Tell him your feelings!

830
00:51:12,126 --> 00:51:14,590
This is the single man's graduation!

831
00:51:16,528 --> 00:51:17,058
Densha...

832
00:51:17,058 --> 00:51:18,286
I understood through you

833
00:51:18,286 --> 00:51:20,635
That I can't always stay as a supporter

834
00:51:20,635 --> 00:51:24,433
So I will find my love on the field

835
00:51:24,433 --> 00:51:26,834
You guys are really... Benoist!!

836
00:51:26,834 --> 00:51:28,994
I always shouted "Hermes, moe~!"

837
00:51:28,994 --> 00:51:31,759
But for today, Densha moe~!

838
00:51:31,759 --> 00:51:33,639
I can't stop here either

839
00:51:33,639 --> 00:51:36,878
No more loose socks! Now panty hose!

840
00:51:36,878 --> 00:51:38,094
Last train!

841
00:51:38,094 --> 00:51:38,993
Last train!

842
00:51:38,993 --> 00:51:40,987
Happiness for Densha and Hermes-san!

843
00:51:40,987 --> 00:51:43,581
I will also do my best and go to Densha-world

844
00:51:43,581 --> 00:51:45,278
Second platform, turn around!

845
00:51:45,278 --> 00:51:49,751
Train for Happiness-station, leaving soon!

846
00:51:49,751 --> 00:51:52,610
Hey, only 200 replies left!

847
00:51:56,130 --> 00:51:59,651
Densha, who told us that a man is not all about appearance

848
00:51:59,651 --> 00:52:03,053
Is real... and so I test

849
00:52:03,720 --> 00:52:04,577
Thank you

850
00:52:04,577 --> 00:52:08,245
The 747 with Densha and Hermes-san on successful take off

851
00:52:08,245 --> 00:52:11,372
Is due to your fuel and service

852
00:52:11,372 --> 00:52:14,645
Good thing I met this thread!

853
00:52:14,645 --> 00:52:19,182
I was attracted by your sincere and honest heart, and I cheered you on

854
00:52:19,182 --> 00:52:20,385
Young man!

855
00:52:20,385 --> 00:52:22,242
Enjoy the life!

856
00:52:22,242 --> 00:52:25,409
I could also protect Hermes-san from a drunken man

857
00:52:25,409 --> 00:52:26,163
But...

858
00:52:26,163 --> 00:52:28,413
Only you are fit for Hermes-san

859
00:52:29,118 --> 00:52:30,486
This is nothing like a miracle

860
00:52:30,486 --> 00:52:34,137
You moved her heart with your effort

861
00:52:34,137 --> 00:52:38,180
Go away to the Couple Zone

862
00:52:38,180 --> 00:52:43,268
You not coming back here is the biggest consolation for me

863
00:52:43,268 --> 00:52:45,966
So I say an old line...

864
00:52:45,966 --> 00:52:47,722
I hate Densha!

865
00:52:47,722 --> 00:52:49,767
What I hate even more is seeing myself

866
00:52:49,767 --> 00:52:53,224
Giving more blessings to you than anyone else

867
00:52:53,224 --> 00:52:53,707
Uh oh!

868
00:52:53,707 --> 00:52:54,393
Only 100 replies to go!

869
00:52:54,393 --> 00:52:55,432
Too fast!

870
00:52:55,432 --> 00:52:58,816
Everyone just wants to say thanks to Densha

871
00:52:58,816 --> 00:53:01,534
Go without turning back!

872
00:53:01,534 --> 00:53:02,498
Densha, good job!

873
00:53:02,498 --> 00:53:04,497
I put aside my test to cheer you on

874
00:53:04,497 --> 00:53:07,156
So thinking about what to do now makes me depressed

875
00:53:07,156 --> 00:53:11,646
But through these three months, I think I received something so precious

876
00:53:11,646 --> 00:53:15,033
I want to get accepted at a college and enjoy the campus life!

877
00:53:15,033 --> 00:53:17,769
I really like Densha and you guys

878
00:53:18,709 --> 00:53:23,727
I also like all of you guys!

879
00:53:24,384 --> 00:53:27,834
I have been called *"Meat" or "Pooh" until now
*From Kinnikuman in 1979 and Winnie-the-Pooh

880
00:53:27,834 --> 00:53:30,845
I became passionate for the first time in my life

881
00:53:30,845 --> 00:53:35,103
It is Densha's history and my history

882
00:53:35,103 --> 00:53:39,793
Well, it might not make sense, but leave it that way

883
00:53:39,793 --> 00:53:42,484
The three months spent with you guys

884
00:53:42,484 --> 00:53:44,335
Were fun

885
00:53:44,335 --> 00:53:45,821
Everyone, unarm yourselves!

886
00:53:45,821 --> 00:53:49,817
Yamada's signal man from the 8th division in the front line, returning to HQ

887
00:53:49,817 --> 00:53:54,496
I want to share this happiness of staying alive

888
00:53:54,496 --> 00:53:56,772
All, salute to Densha!

889
00:53:59,658 --> 00:54:00,241
Densha!

890
00:54:00,241 --> 00:54:01,619
We will meet again someday

891
00:54:01,619 --> 00:54:02,784
On this thread...

892
00:54:02,784 --> 00:54:08,189
I just wanted to give a little advice to wavering people like you

893
00:54:08,189 --> 00:54:09,804
I won't say goodbye

894
00:54:09,804 --> 00:54:11,534
See you again, Densha

895
00:54:11,534 --> 00:54:12,748
And brother in arms

896
00:54:12,748 --> 00:54:16,766
I like who you are

897
00:54:16,766 --> 00:54:19,123
I like your sincerity

898
00:54:19,123 --> 00:54:25,063
And more than anything else, I like your caring heart for Hermes-san

899
00:54:25,063 --> 00:54:27,344
As long as I have my girlfriend

900
00:54:27,344 --> 00:54:30,704
I will care for her

901
00:54:33,545 --> 00:54:35,084
After getting to know Densha-san

902
00:54:35,084 --> 00:54:38,960
I realized a man is not all about appearance, and now I have confidence

903
00:54:38,960 --> 00:54:43,451
My boyfriend is backwards too, but actually through cheering for your love

904
00:54:43,451 --> 00:54:47,343
I realized that he is a warm person

905
00:54:47,343 --> 00:54:48,621
Thank you

906
00:54:50,670 --> 00:54:54,712
No, thank you!

907
00:54:54,712 --> 00:54:56,504
Really, a insignificant opportunity

908
00:54:56,504 --> 00:55:00,533
A lot of courage, and a little bit of advice

909
00:55:00,533 --> 00:55:03,427
And your effort and growth

910
00:55:03,427 --> 00:55:05,984
Resulted in a miracle like this

911
00:55:05,984 --> 00:55:08,167
Always, treasure it in your heart!

912
00:55:10,963 --> 00:55:14,831
I also fulfilled the love that I once gave up on

913
00:55:16,076 --> 00:55:17,607
Thanks in many ways

914
00:55:17,607 --> 00:55:20,985
It is time to say goodbye to Densha

915
00:55:20,985 --> 00:55:24,855
Maybe I got to like you a little from cheering you on

916
00:55:25,984 --> 00:55:30,076
I even think it would have been okay to have "helped" you escape from self-pity

917
00:55:31,354 --> 00:55:34,934
Please explain the details of Densha and Hermes-san's future

918
00:55:34,934 --> 00:55:38,019
So sad saying goodbye to you!

919
00:55:38,019 --> 00:55:40,517
I hope I meet you somewhere

920
00:55:40,517 --> 00:55:43,709
Go for tomorrow!

921
00:55:44,256 --> 00:55:48,273
While following your love story, a lot has happened to me as well

922
00:55:48,273 --> 00:55:50,999
The biggest thing that happened was marriage

923
00:55:51,608 --> 00:55:52,351
And I...

924
00:55:52,351 --> 00:55:55,827
Came to appreciate her even more now because of you

925
00:55:56,427 --> 00:55:58,023
Thank you so much

926
00:55:58,023 --> 00:56:00,541
Meeting you is my pride

927
00:56:01,708 --> 00:56:04,983
All of you...

928
00:56:04,983 --> 00:56:08,090
Are my pride

929
00:56:08,090 --> 00:56:12,371
When I read your report, I was glad that I made this thread

930
00:56:13,611 --> 00:56:17,071
Not just because love has been fulfilled for the first time

931
00:56:17,071 --> 00:56:22,232
But because a lot of people became happy because of you

932
00:56:22,232 --> 00:56:23,908
Densha...

933
00:56:23,908 --> 00:56:25,374
You guys...

934
00:56:27,027 --> 00:56:28,632
Good job

935
00:56:29,224 --> 00:56:31,736
These past three months have been very fun

936
00:56:32,299 --> 00:56:36,158
The time spent with you felt more real than Michiho

937
00:56:36,930 --> 00:56:37,751
Definitely...

938
00:56:37,751 --> 00:56:40,826
Throughout life, I will start forgetting things

939
00:56:40,826 --> 00:56:44,151
And someday, this thread will be gone too

940
00:56:44,151 --> 00:56:47,721
But I don't want to forget what happened here

941
00:56:47,721 --> 00:56:51,196
It seems that real life is full of troublesome things

942
00:56:51,196 --> 00:56:53,240
But maybe, there might also be some pleasant things after all

943
00:56:53,240 --> 00:56:55,960
That is what I learned from this

944
00:56:55,960 --> 00:56:57,120
Someday...

945
00:56:57,120 --> 00:56:59,031
To see what you are seeing right now

946
00:56:59,031 --> 00:57:02,769
I will pace myself

947
00:57:02,769 --> 00:57:06,940
Until then, let your heart out at the Couple Zone

948
00:57:15,682 --> 00:57:17,496
I was away for a while

949
00:57:17,496 --> 00:57:21,089
But I did get to see your growth until the end

950
00:57:21,089 --> 00:57:23,067
You first didn't know what to do

951
00:57:23,067 --> 00:57:24,934
But you grew up with the help of a lot of people

952
00:57:24,934 --> 00:57:28,626
And now you graduate as an awesome man

953
00:57:28,626 --> 00:57:32,142
Densha, don't ever let go of her hand

954
00:57:32,142 --> 00:57:34,134
Whatever happens

955
00:57:34,134 --> 00:57:37,895
From now on, you will go through many different things

956
00:57:37,895 --> 00:57:41,525
When you feel frustrated, remember this place

957
00:57:41,525 --> 00:57:44,892
What you have done here, what you have heard here

958
00:57:44,892 --> 00:57:49,530
And how much you thought of Hermes-san here

959
00:57:50,147 --> 00:57:52,647
Be happy!

960
00:57:52,647 --> 00:57:55,569
And to everyone here

961
00:57:55,569 --> 00:57:58,815
Thanks for giving up your precious time

962
00:57:59,537 --> 00:58:00,764
I can't hold it

963
00:58:00,764 --> 00:58:03,145
Damn it

964
00:58:03,145 --> 00:58:06,043
Tears are not stopping

965
00:58:16,399 --> 00:58:20,247
You guys... thanks so much

966
00:58:22,457 --> 00:58:23,592
I am so happy

967
00:58:23,592 --> 00:58:24,844
I got courage from you guys

968
00:58:24,844 --> 00:58:27,386
I feel grateful

969
00:58:27,386 --> 00:58:31,761
A lot of emotions are being expressed through my tears

970
00:58:33,662 --> 00:58:35,904
I...

971
00:58:35,904 --> 00:58:38,622
Won't forget all of you guys

972
00:58:41,381 --> 00:58:43,638
You guys!

973
00:58:44,740 --> 00:58:45,948
I really like you guys!

974
00:58:45,948 --> 00:58:47,844
I really like you guys too!!!

975
00:58:50,778 --> 00:58:54,299
Now, rise up without turning back!

976
00:58:54,299 --> 00:58:56,766
It seems this is more sad than the real graduation

977
00:58:56,766 --> 00:58:58,255
Now only 50 replies left

978
00:58:58,255 --> 00:58:59,286
Everyone get ready

979
00:58:59,286 --> 00:59:02,202
Now no more Densha's thread?

980
00:59:02,202 --> 00:59:03,466
So sad...

981
00:59:03,466 --> 00:59:04,695
My heart is aching!

982
00:59:04,695 --> 00:59:07,984
What can I look forward to now!

983
00:59:07,984 --> 00:59:09,834
If you get married, tell us!

984
00:59:09,834 --> 00:59:11,953
Be happy forever!

985
00:59:11,953 --> 00:59:13,592
Everyone! Let's stop writing!

986
00:59:13,592 --> 00:59:17,270
Then Densha will stay here!

987
00:59:17,270 --> 00:59:18,737
I know...

988
00:59:18,737 --> 00:59:20,397
But that is impossible...

989
00:59:20,397 --> 00:59:23,055
No more ranting!

990
00:59:23,055 --> 00:59:24,390
965

991
00:59:24,390 --> 00:59:26,872
Densha was our hope

992
00:59:26,872 --> 00:59:28,497
966

993
00:59:28,497 --> 00:59:33,673
Densha! I really like you! Don't go!

994
00:59:33,673 --> 00:59:34,944
967

995
00:59:34,944 --> 00:59:37,301
Now this thread will be gone soon!

996
00:59:37,301 --> 00:59:39,454
968

997
00:59:39,454 --> 00:59:42,654
No more Densha now! No, I don't like this!

998
00:59:42,654 --> 00:59:46,221
969 sniff sniff

999
00:59:46,221 --> 00:59:50,240
Why is it so sad when only a stranger is leaving?

1000
00:59:50,240 --> 00:59:51,942
970

1001
00:59:51,942 --> 00:59:55,265
In a while, days without Densha will begin!

1002
00:59:55,265 --> 00:59:57,986
971

1003
00:59:57,986 --> 01:00:02,420
I am crying for all of your caring feelings! Densha is a lucky guy!

1004
01:00:02,420 --> 01:00:04,072
972

1005
01:00:04,072 --> 01:00:08,361
Densha, you write the 1000th reply

1006
01:00:10,222 --> 01:00:13,042
980

1007
01:00:13,042 --> 01:00:15,477
1000th reply... Are you giving it to me?

1008
01:00:17,421 --> 01:00:18,572
What should I write?

1009
01:00:18,572 --> 01:00:20,695
982

1010
01:00:20,695 --> 01:00:24,921
Densha, at the final moment, give us the final message!

1011
01:00:24,921 --> 01:00:26,947
984

1012
01:00:26,947 --> 01:00:31,693
It is time to say goodbye! I don't even know what I am writing because of the tears

1013
01:00:32,214 --> 01:00:35,569
985

1014
01:00:35,569 --> 01:00:37,831
I thought of... the message...

1015
01:00:40,474 --> 01:00:42,503
I...

1016
01:00:42,503 --> 01:00:44,095
Something I have been thinking all along...

1017
01:00:44,095 --> 01:00:45,649
986

1018
01:00:45,649 --> 01:00:47,806
I want to know! But I don't want to see it now!

1019
01:00:48,325 --> 01:00:50,395
987

1020
01:00:50,395 --> 01:00:54,137
If I see that, that means goodbye to Densha!

1021
01:00:54,137 --> 01:00:56,269
990

1022
01:00:56,269 --> 01:00:58,211
Goodbye! Friend!

1023
01:00:58,211 --> 01:01:01,063
991

1024
01:01:01,063 --> 01:01:03,187
Now.. it is time...

1025
01:01:03,187 --> 01:01:04,898
992

1026
01:01:04,898 --> 01:01:07,514
You guys, Densha! Good bye!

1027
01:01:07,514 --> 01:01:09,198
993

1028
01:01:09,198 --> 01:01:11,351
You guys are all so sincere! I am touched

1029
01:01:11,351 --> 01:01:13,567
994

1030
01:01:13,567 --> 01:01:17,729
Last reply. See you again somewhere, someday! Densha!

1031
01:01:17,729 --> 01:01:19,475
995

1032
01:01:19,475 --> 01:01:21,441
Don't forget us!

1033
01:01:21,441 --> 01:01:23,971
996

1034
01:01:23,971 --> 01:01:26,598
Finally, this is the end!

1035
01:01:26,598 --> 01:01:28,220
997

1036
01:01:28,220 --> 01:01:33,386
If I were to get 999 replies, then I would confess too! But I don't have a girl...

1037
01:01:33,386 --> 01:01:36,028
998

1038
01:01:36,028 --> 01:01:39,621
Bell for train leaving~!

1039
01:01:45,831 --> 01:01:48,112
Graduation

1040
01:01:48,112 --> 01:01:51,143
Congratulations~!

1041
01:01:59,878 --> 01:02:03,508
[Densha Otoko, Congratulations on your graduation!]

1042
01:02:05,519 --> 01:02:08,048
999 Name:

1043
01:02:08,048 --> 01:02:12,949
[Densha Otoko, Congratulations on your graduation!]

1044
01:02:12,949 --> 01:02:17,172
[Densha Otoko]

1045
01:02:19,238 --> 01:02:21,731
1000

1046
01:02:21,731 --> 01:02:26,015
This thread is full of magical power...

1047
01:02:28,867 --> 01:02:31,815
May the light be with you guys too!

1048
01:02:58,007 --> 01:02:58,008

1049
01:02:59,000 --> 01:03:07,052
[1001 Name: 1001 Over 1000 Thread
This thread has more than 1000 replies
You can't write anymore, so please make a new thread]

1050
01:04:00,407 --> 01:04:05,628
Through all these people, we can stay together now

1051
01:04:06,775 --> 01:04:08,179
Yes

1052
01:06:04,492 --> 01:06:06,525
You can do it!

1053
01:06:06,525 --> 01:06:07,836
Densha Otoko

1054
01:06:41,828 --> 01:06:44,052
Let's go, then

1055
01:06:54,312 --> 01:06:54,838
Are you going out?

1056
01:06:54,838 --> 01:06:57,883
Yes, I am going to go out with Tsuyoshi-san

1057
01:07:00,091 --> 01:07:01,012
Saori

1058
01:07:02,534 --> 01:07:04,641
You face looks bright

1059
01:07:04,641 --> 01:07:06,735
You too, mother

1060
01:07:07,528 --> 01:07:08,614
See you later!

1061
01:07:09,128 --> 01:07:09,866
See you later!

1062
01:07:09,866 --> 01:07:11,342
See you later!

1063
01:07:11,342 --> 01:07:12,552
See you later~!

1064
01:07:15,647 --> 01:07:17,951
[Unrequited Love]
[Restaurant]

1065
01:07:24,389 --> 01:07:25,840
Long time no see

1066
01:07:25,840 --> 01:07:27,656
How's work?

1067
01:07:27,656 --> 01:07:31,151
Our name is "restaurant" but we only serve coffee, you bonehead!

1068
01:07:31,151 --> 01:07:32,832
Give me a cup

1069
01:07:34,088 --> 01:07:35,914
Misuzu-san

1070
01:07:35,914 --> 01:07:37,968
Leaving without telling me...

1071
01:07:38,412 --> 01:07:40,333
Hey you, Misuzu?

1072
01:07:40,333 --> 01:07:41,997
You mean Jinnkama Misuzu?

1073
01:07:47,811 --> 01:07:48,765
You too?

1074
01:07:50,393 --> 01:07:52,962
Sa...Sakurai-san

1075
01:07:52,962 --> 01:07:53,595
When did you get here...

1076
01:07:53,595 --> 01:07:55,405
A while ago

1077
01:07:55,405 --> 01:07:58,772
But are you also victims of Jinnkama Misuzu?

1078
01:07:58,772 --> 01:07:59,465
Victim?

1079
01:07:59,465 --> 01:08:01,055
Then you are also...?

1080
01:08:02,558 --> 01:08:03,814
Not just me!

1081
01:08:08,645 --> 01:08:12,503
All of us... ruined our lives because of her!

1082
01:08:13,963 --> 01:08:16,093
I used up so much money

1083
01:08:16,093 --> 01:08:18,423
Because I had a relationship with a girl

1084
01:08:18,423 --> 01:08:20,998
I turned away from a successful life to a ruined life

1085
01:08:20,998 --> 01:08:22,589
My wife found out, so she filed for divorce

1086
01:08:22,589 --> 01:08:24,668
I even changed my flight schedule to go meet her!

1087
01:08:24,668 --> 01:08:26,993
I bought her a lot of expensive dress shoes

1088
01:08:26,993 --> 01:08:27,671
I!

1089
01:08:27,671 --> 01:08:30,879
I!

1090
01:08:30,879 --> 01:08:32,016
I!

1091
01:08:32,016 --> 01:08:36,085
All right, let's form a club of Jinnkama Misuzu's victims

1092
01:08:39,349 --> 01:08:40,919
Let's go find a new love

1093
01:08:42,016 --> 01:08:45,506
[I am going on a trip! Thank you for everything! - Misuzu]

1094
01:08:47,975 --> 01:08:50,008
[JR Tokyo Station]

1095
01:08:53,287 --> 01:08:56,556
The visions dancing in my mind

1096
01:08:56,556 --> 01:08:56,756
Sorry
The early dawn, the shades of time

1097
01:08:56,756 --> 01:08:58,080
Sorry
The early dawn, the shades of time

1098
01:08:58,080 --> 01:08:59,768
Shall we go?
The early dawn, the shades of time

1099
01:08:59,769 --> 01:09:04,800
Yes
Twilight crawling through my windowpane

1100
01:09:06,678 --> 01:09:10,223
Am I awake or do I dream?

1101
01:09:10,223 --> 01:09:13,866
The strangest pictures I have seen

1102
01:09:13,866 --> 01:09:17,394
Night is day and twilight's gone away

1103
01:09:17,394 --> 01:09:19,419
They were good people

1104
01:09:19,419 --> 01:09:20,634
With your head held high and your scarlet lies

1105
01:09:20,634 --> 01:09:21,869
Yes
With your head held high and your scarlet lies

1106
01:09:21,869 --> 01:09:22,593
With your head held high and your scarlet lies

1107
01:09:22,593 --> 01:09:26,285
You came down to me from the open skies

1108
01:09:26,285 --> 01:09:26,680
[Densha Otoko]

1109
01:09:26,680 --> 01:09:28,584
[Densha Otoko]
It's either real or it's a dream

1110
01:09:28,584 --> 01:09:29,416
[Densha Otoko]
There's nothing that is in between...

1111
01:09:29,416 --> 01:09:30,254
There's nothing that is in between...

1112
01:09:30,254 --> 01:09:33,640
Shit
Twilight, I only meant to stay awhile

1113
01:09:33,640 --> 01:09:37,000
Why don't the old doors allow this?
Twilight, I only meant to stay awhile

1114
01:09:37,000 --> 01:09:38,100
Why don't the old doors allow this?
Twilight, I gave you time to steal my mind

1115
01:09:38,100 --> 01:09:43,000
Twilight, I gave you time to steal my mind

1116
01:09:43,000 --> 01:09:47,000
Away from me

1117
01:09:54,063 --> 01:09:59,190
This drama is a fiction based on a true story

1118
01:09:59,190 --> 01:10:00,023
Decided! Yes----('V')----!!!!!

1119
01:10:00,023 --> 01:10:05,000
Decided! Yes----('V')----!!!!!
Densha Otoko, Encore Last Episode
October 6, Thurday 10PM
30 minute special extension!!!

