"Gimme" is back!
I'm going to Akiba with Hermes!
(Akiba is slang for Akihabara)
What??
Akiba?  You mean, the otaku fortress, Akihabara?
Filled with guys like this, guys like that, guys like these...
And guys like those and guys like these...
and guys like this...
THAT Akihabara??
Like, that's going a bit overboard on the 'coming out,' isn't it?
Please give me the details  In Japan!
Okay, well let me quickly explain what Hermes and I talked about
No!  Take your time!
For us, everything about dealing with women is completely new!
C'mon, kill us slowly and toy with us!
Okay...  I'll explain everything...  From start to finish.
Um  Do you remember your promise?
P  Promise?
I guess you forgot...
Uh, no  I mean
The Com -pu-ter!
I guess you did forget.
I'm so sorry!
Then, as your punishment
next time...
you have to help me find one.
Yes!
What the heck  He's in Happy Mode all the sudden
Oh man, a pouty Hermes...  Moe...
(see notes regarding 'Moe')
Until now, I was backing up Densha, but I  I
The medic!  GET THE MEDIC!!
No...  There's no pulse...
What are you going to use your PC for?
As long as I can surf the net and check my e-mail, it's okay
Okay, so a more user-friendly machine
Yamada-san, where do you usually buy them?
Usually I go to Akiba...
Uh...  I mean, Akihabara.
Okay, let's go there
Um, but, if you don't care too much...
any electronics store will do...
Yamada-san, I want to go where you usually go to.
I want to get to know you better.
It's an air raid!
Quick, to the bomb shelter!
It's too late for me.
See you on the other side...
The conversations I dream of when I'm in bed...
You're having them in real life!
So it's a date at Akihabara...
Akiba is the best!!
(note - for Ameircan internet junkies, it's closer to "Akiba rox0rz!")
Hermes is wearing a maid outfit in my head...
A maid outfit...
Welcome home...
...master.
No...  No!
You can't have a Hermes that cute!
Want me to take you to a good hospital?
I bet she'll match Densha's otaku style...
wearing a flower-pattern dress with a mid-length skirt...
...and two ponytails.  I'm sure of it!
How do I look?
Twin ponytails  Oh man...
I gotta Google a good PC for Aoyama-san.
Please!
Yeeessss...
Translation by Masakun
Time stamping by whoever worked on the Korean subs - (chandlerkim @ gmail.com) (thank you!)
Editing by Masakun
Thanks to those who spend time distributing this TV show,
and to Greyhorse for subbing episodes 1 through 8
[Akihabara]
Um...
Yes?
Shall we hold hands?
You don't want to?
With pleasure!
P...Please.
I never really asked you what kind of PC you wanted...
...it might not be of much help to you...
You researched all of this?
Well...
...there isn't much more I could've done for you.
That's so nice of you -
thank you so much!
Don't mention it!
There are lots of people here wearing backpacks.
Does everyone spend the night somewhere?
No, it's usually a day trip to Akihabara.
It's good that you found one that you liked.
Thanks to you.
No, you're too kind.
Do you want to go to the 'Purikura' machines?
('Purikura' = those sticker picture machines, short for 'Print Club')
Over there.
A...a...photo w...with the two of us?
Would you rather not?
No, I'd love t
These came out a bit funny...
...but they make nice souvenirs.
Th...thank you!
(I'll bet he was going for a shoryuken...)
Yamada-san, you're pretty good!
(Not a DDR song!)
Mr. Yamada!
(it's grammatically incorrect to directly address someone with a -shi suffix for reasons similar to why Americans don't address their
Hello.
(peers by putting a title before their friends' last names, but...)
Mr. Matsunaga, since Aoyama-san is here...
(the writers for this program must've felt that it made good Otaku-talk)
we should go Shibuya mode.
(Certain areas of Tokyo have their own youth cultures...)
Right.  Uhhh  Coincidence  it's so dangerous!
(but in most cases, it's a girl thing, like the typical Valley Girl...)
No appointment  It's nothing! (bad Japanese pun)
(...and I'm almost certain that they aren't using real 'Shibuya-esque' language)
Guys, it's okay.
Like, ohmigosh, I sooo don't know what you're talking about!
That's like, so hilarious!
No...  You don't have to talk like that.
Huh?
Ohh I see, Mr. Yamada.
You spilled the beans on your otaku-ness!
That's a giant leap forward for you, no?
B...but, Aoyama-san...
are you okay hanging out...
with a race like ourselves?
Am I okay?  No, I'm having fun!
She's such a good person!
She's about 23 levels higher than
the high school girls and office ladies who destroy us!
Maybe about 15,000 exp?
Level?
Exp?
Do all of you go to Akihabara a lot?
About 4 times a week.
We look at girl games...
(Girl games = PC games, often for adults only, that get the player involved in virtual relationships with girls that are in such games)
...or anime girl figures.  We also go to events...
(Girl games = PC games, often for adults only, that get the player involved in virtual relationships with girls that are in the different games)
Girl games?
They're love simulation games.
They're so...  Moeeee...
Moe?
Um, one more time, please!
Moe-?
This place
...is my own special spot.
Really?
Yes.
You're the first person I've told this to.
I guess that means from now on, it's our special spot.
Yes!
Wh...when I come up here, I feel a little more courageous.
So I only come here...
...for special occasions.
So...  Is today a special day?
Oh... No...
I didn't mean it like...
Hey!  This is your chance to tell her!
If you don't tell her now, when will you??
I'll bet Hermes is just waiting for you to tell her.
Uh...uhm...
Yes?
Uh...
Oh...  I...
I...  It's nothing.
I see.
Densha!  Are you really trying to become a 'couple' with her?
(this is another Gundam pun - 'Couple' typed as 'Capule' from Gundam ZZ)
You've failed as a human being!
I did realize it was a chance.
But, it hasn't been too long since we made up...
and if we were to start dating, how would I be?
I worry about these things.
Don't be a chicken!
And you call yourself a Japanese guy!?
Have you forgotten your Japanese Spirit!?
Well, Japanese Spirit has nothing to do with this, but just in case...
If you're seeing her often and you guys are clicking...
What's the rush?
Eventually, you won't be able to NOT confess your feelings for her.
Hey let's stop saying stuff that'll rush him, yeah?
I have a feeling that Densha's own decisions will be more useful...
than ideas from a bunch of single guys.
Densha, you tell her when YOU feel it's right.
Don't worry - no matter what happens...
Densha, I got your back.
-pant pant-
W...what the...?
Densha!  What happened!?
The Lord Densha has lost his bloody mind!
Whose post is he panting about?
See?  You guys bugged him about confessing so much...
He's gone mad!
Densha!  Snap out of it!
On my cell...  Hermes sent me a picture of her...  In her sleepwear!
You were all worked up over her picture!?
What kind of bombing is that?
How could you attack us like that when we're so defenseless?
Her sleepwear  Are you talking about pajamas?  A negligee?
Pajamas.
I feel so stupid for seriously worrying about you!
Oh c'mon you idiot - confess to her!
She's rolling around the bed...
She's so cute!
Shit, I've never wanted to see Hermes's face more than I do right now
So who are you guys thinking about?
Miki Nakatani for me!
(Miki Nakatani was Hermes in the movie version of Densha Otoko)
It has to be Mitsuko Baisho from a while back!
No way, it's Kumiko Ohba
Yuko Ogura, aka Yuko-rin
I'll bet she's like Ryoko Kuninaka
Oh c'mon, you think a hot chick like that is gonna have Densha within striking zone?
This is why Otakus' imaginations are so dumb
But, more than any girl on TV...
I like Hermes.
This...is...ticking...me...off...
Densha  I don't know what you're thinking...
...but Hermes still isn't yours.
Well said.
So hurry up and make her yours!
Don't forget that she still owes you for helping her out
Yep.  Maybe she's cornered in a spot where she can't say no to you even if she wanted to.
And he's hit while he's on the ground!
...yeah...
You're right.  Sorry for acting all high and mighty.
I really should know my place.
Next time, I'm going to help her set up her computer...
so I thought I'd tell her then, but...
...I guess not.
Okay I'm out.  Good night everyone.
Wait!
Wait!  What's this with her room!?
You have to mention juicy details like that first!
Don't throw away your plans to tell her!
Hey, we're sorry about bullying on you like that!
We were only kidding!  Tell us when you're going!
Densha, don't go to sleep!
A response - give us a response! A response - give us a response! A response - give us a response!
The Densha is currently unable to depart.
(if you haven't guessed, Densha means 'train' in Japanese)
Over here please.
Hello.
('Ojama shimasu' is what you say when you enter someone's house or apartment)
Mom
This is Yamada-san
Come on in!
Saori...
Where's Yamada-san?
What are you talking about?
This is Yamada-san.
Nninice to meet you  I...I'm Yamada.
Saori...
You have your contacts on, right?
Yeah
Okay...so is that a joke or something?
He just seems like a weirdo to me.
Mom, that's rude.
But!
What a disappointment.
N-nice mmeeting you.
Let's go up to my room.
Hello?
Aoyama speaking.
Come on in.
This -
This is your room, Aoyama-san?
Yes.
Why don't you relax while I get some tea for us?
Sure.
Hey...
Yamada-san...
...seems like a nice person.
Huh?  Mom?
His height is kind of adorable...
And if you squint at him, he doesn't look like he's not well-groomed.
Well that's a change.
Really?
Hey, this Sunday -
Llet's go out on a family dinner with Yamada-san.
What's wrong?  You're suddenly
It smells so nice
Is something wrong?
Uh - no, it's nothing
You've got a nice computer.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Do you need any help?
No it's okay, it won't take long.
Please sit down.
I see.
It'sit's been so hot lately.
Yes.  I'm not too fond of summer, actually.
Oh I see.
If I'm not wearing layers, I can't hide my physique so I don't like it.
But, Aoyama-san, you're pretty skinny, so I don't think that's a problem.
You...  You're saying I'm skinny...
My friends and my mom tell me that I don't look good because I'm so skinny.
I see...
I guess the reason -
I don't have a boyfriend is that my body is like this
So... you don't have a boyfriend?
No
A fiancee?
She's available for sure!
Free!
Is everything all right?
Uhyes.
But...
Even if you're skinny or fat
I think that's fine.
It's just that other guys are blind.
Please...
Please don't lead me on like that.
Confess!
Uhm...
No, please go ahead.
Do you want to have dinner with my family this coming Sunday?
Dinner?
(shokuji means 'meal' if it's literally translated, but dinner is often implied with the use of this word)
Sure
Okay
I'll let you know when and where later on.
All right.
W...with the family?
What am I gonna do?
It's dinner with Hermes's family!
She told me that her dad won't be there, but...
...why did I agree to go?
This is what you get for leaving us for ourselves.
Ah, the rite of passage before you can confess to her
But if the dad's not there, you can set your sights just on Hermes's mom.
Keep in mind that the most important objective of this mission is to be liked by Hermes's mother.
Rich ladies will definitely be on the lookout for your appearance!
She's not rich, but my mom doesn't like sloppy guys either.
No thanks for the useless info!
But you should definitely look nice - abesh!
(Fist of the North Star reference)
Can't just dress up casually like usual?
A dinner with the family means you gotta suit up!
Go with a tux.
Ask me anything about suits!
I can give you a 3 hour lecture.
What else do you have to worry about...
You're fine on table manners right?
Table manners?
Brrr...  Shiver shiver shiver shiver shiver
I guess you didn't know after all...
I'll bestow upon you my skills in
eating a banana gracefully
It's also important to be a good talker at the dinner table.
Go to a self-improvement seminar!
Read a paper and be up on current events.
So there's a new suit, table manners,
and dialogue on the list...
The way this conversation is headed,
it's about time we gave 'it' a try again.
Densha Otoko
(Evangelion?  What's that?)
Modification Plan
part 2
(Evangelion?  What's that?)
Um...  Where'd you buy that suit?
With a suit, rather than getting what's trendy,
you have to be able to impress.
It's better to look at people around you
rather than fashion magazines.
Oikawa-san
Where did you buy that suit?
Paris...  Milano...  New York...
Oh, this is a custom tailored suit I got in Milano.
I can't compete with Oikawa-kun
but I have an Italian suit too.
But I can't compete against Oikawa-kun.
There are lots of well-dressed people
among your superiors at work.
That's really true!
Amazing!
Of course.
Japanese suits...  I can't get myself to wear them.
Yeah, I'd say so too.
And the logo...
Huh?
But this...
This is made in Japan.
['Made in Italy' written in Japanese]
Yeah, well...  Um...
What?
Communication with Hermes's mother is key.
But it's almost impossible for Densha to
get good at conversations.
Maybe you can try praising her?
Nobody dislikes being praised, you know.
Be humble about it.
(Literal meaning = keep your back low)
Hey what are you doing?
You're grossing me out!
Jinkama-san,
you really have the sharpest tongue in Japan
You trying to pick a fight with me?
Don't let that smile disappear from your face!
That was a good one!
Your thick makeup makes you look young today!
Shut the f_ck up!
That was a good one!
That aloof look on your face is beautiful!
death
I'm sure the other person will be smiling.
That felt great!
Last item: table manners
Don't hold your knife upside down
And drink your soup silently lol
It's only manners
BUT they're important!
Hey...  Are you sure about this?
Yeah.
This is the only way I can get it on short notice.
Here goes.
Start with the knife and fork on the outside.
Yes ma'am!
Whoa, what're you doing?
Hey, could you take over?
Can you push this button as soon as
he makes a mistake?
Okay leave it up to me.
Get ready for some quality judging!
After eating...
wipe your mouth with the napkin, and then...
take a sip of your drink.
Too long...
Too long!!
What did I do wrong?
No, no, your face.
Yamada eating with Saori's family?
Yeah, but it's tough trying to find a good place...
Saori - you bought a computer recently, right?
Then you should look up a place on the 'net.
I didn't know you were into web surfing.
Hey, you ever hear of "Aladdin Channel?"
"Aladdin Channel?"
It's an anonymous BBS that's been talked about lately.
Apparently they'll listen to any kind of problems you might have.
Really?
I thought Aladdin Channel was...
a gathering place for Otakus,
where they talk smack on others
and do lots of shady stuff.
For real?
And I was going to ask some questions about guys...
Saori
My dad's acquaintance has a good restaurant
Really?
Really.
Kengo Aoyama
[Divorce Form]
Th...th...
Thank you for inviting me today.
Relax, you can take it easy.
Can I go home?
No
I need you to be here.
But I have nothing to do with this dinner.
Thank you for visiting our restaurant today.
I have tonight's dinner listed under Kazuya Sakurai.
As Kazuya Sakurai asked...
the entire restaurant is for you guys tonight.
That's so nice
To have this restaurant all to ourselves.
With pleasure
Kazuya Sakurai
is always very kind to us.
Please enjoy your meal
You
Did you say my name 3 times or more?
Yes
Your full name - I used it thrice.
Okay everyone listen!
Today I reserved this restaurant all to myself.
You are to listen to my every command!
Understand??
Yes!
Densha...
For you, today is the end.
It...it's spicy...
Mmm, this is delicious.
I didn't think it would be so light.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Y...yes, it is.
[For Yamada]
(I wonder where they sell this...)
Thanks.
Drink.  Drink.  Drink!
It's hot!
Drink!  Drink!
Drink.  Drink.  Drink.  Drink.  Drink.  Drink.
-Drink more water!
Unless you go to the bathroom...
we can't bring out the main dish!
I can't...
I'm gonna pee...
I'm so sorry.
Please excuse me!
Drink.  Drink.  Drink.  Drink.
Yes!
Now it's time...
For the secret weapon!
(I HAVE to learn that trick!)
Fake Tsuyoshi
(reminder - Densha's first name)
You have to play his part.
You sure I'm fit for this role?
Eh?
You're fine.
You totally look like him.
Don't worry.
Go, Fake Tsuyoshi.
Pops...
Pops?
Hey wait!
Don't go out!
What's going on?
Mom, can you tell me what's going on here?
Mother?
There's nothing to talk about if it's just me and him.
That's why I had you all join me.
This is bullshit!
Why didn't you say anything?
If I told you, you wouldn't have come!
Of course not!
Yuki
Did you bring it?
Let's not talk about this over dinner.
So you planning on running away like that again?
Then I'll have to ask you to sign it here.
Please, not here.
Um...
Who are you?
Huh?  Oh...  oh, oh, I'm, uh, I'm...
Tsuyoshi Yamada.
My friend.
I see.
I'm Saori's father.
Huh?
Sorry, but...
we have to have a talk as a family
could you please leave?
Okay, I'll go home.
I'm sorry.
No, please.
Thank you for everything today.
Um...
I have to go to my next gig...
Good night.
You said
...you wouldn't divorce...
until after Keisuke graduated from college.
That's why I waited.
Let's get this over with.
I have to run some errands after this
can you please just hurry up?
Is she waiting for you or something?
This has nothing to do with you.
Mom just hurry up!
Keisuke can you please stay out of this?
If you don't end it here you'll just get
all of us into deeper trouble.
Look at sis.
Thanks to you and dad...
she can't trust guys anymore.
Keisuke.
Can't you keep us out of this?
is that true, Saori?
What are you saying?
You keep your mouth shut.
Keisuke, stop!
Uhh...
I forgot something...
I'm outta here.
Take whatever it is that you left here.
I'm sorry.
Is there something else?
Oh, um, no.
I think that marriage...
is an amazing thing.
Just going out with someone
is such a big deal for me...
but then
you propose
meet each others' parents
buy rings
have a wedding
it probably...
probably requires a lot more courage
than you can imagine.
What are you trying to say?
Let him talk!
Well...  I...
I...
I'm not sure what exactly I'm trying to say.
But
I don't want to see Aoyama-san so sad.
I too have a dad and a mom.
Unlike the two of you,
My dad is no help at all
and my mom is never home.
But
They're always smiling.
Even for such little things
they laugh so much.
And that's why
I feel so safe, and I laugh with them too.
Children...
want their parents to be smiling.
I'm sure
More than anyone
she wants her parents to be happy
That's why
she always wants you to be smiling.
I'm sorry
Here you are.
The divorce papers.
I signed everything.
Yuki
See you.
Mom
I think I'm starting to understand...
...why you chose that person.
Can we go?
Saori.
I'm sorry.
Dad
See you later.
You won...
Densha Otoko.
Um...
Shall we
hold hands?
Sure.
...so that's all for today.
Great!  Densha, you're making me cry...
Is the Densha Mobile Suit a monster?
(yet another Gundam 0079 reference...  too good!)
Our Modification Plan - useless!
Anything is okay if the ending is good!
Looks like Hermes's mom likes you too
Okay, we cleared this mission.
No more weak spots left!
Next time, the confession!!
Everyone's so excited now!
분위기 탔다고 하니,
Speaking of which,
looks like this BBS has gotten lots of attention too!
Now that you mention it,
we have a lot more members these days.
People are designed to flock to interesting places.
Oh yeah, there were some high school girls
talking about this thread in the train.
I was suprised that my friends knew about it.
We're all on our way to fame for sure!
Wait a minute,
if the party's gotten this big
Hermes will find out about this sooner or later.
There's a chance that Hermes's friends will find out
>
What does Densha think?
I don't see it as a problem...
"as if you had a right to say that," he interjected.
왜 그렇게 낙관적으로 생각할수있는거야?
How can you think so lightly?
This board is packed with your thoughts and feelings!
"It's started to smell good"
"Age = length of time withou a girlfriend"
Your peculiar mannerisms are all shown to the public
"Where should I eat?"
She'll know about all your questions like that too.
She'll find out about my Hermes obsession...
Who cares about us anonymous members?
Densha, she'll find out about all your panting too!
Don't scare me like that.
Hey Densha,
this is a pretty serious problem!
If this leaks out,
Hermes will be pretty upset!
Even if it's Hermes,
I don't think she'll forgive you
for spilling the beans on her so much.
I'm a girl,
but if someone was talking about me
and I didn't know about it, I wouldn't like it.
That's an honest opinion.
Holding hands or a first date...
I think a girl would want to keep that between the two of you
Having my words written down like this...
WOULD FREAK ME OUT
Llike the stalker!
She thought that was between the two of you...
she'll start crying if she knew you were telling us!
Your mistakes or misunderstandings, like the surfing,
would be pretty sad to have exposed.
Depending on your point of view...
you've shared with everyone details of her private life.
I thought about it after reading everyone's replies...
but maybe this is a betrayal against Hermes.
[Betrayal]
Betrayal...
I didn't even think about that.
I was betraying Hermes...
Well it's only a 'what if' scenario.
Don't dwell on it too much.
But can we leave it at that?
No, we cant.
It's better to tell her on your own before she finds out.
If you feel bad about it,
you should pour out your guts to her!
But if you tell her she'll get really pissed...
There's less than a 1% chance that Hermes will find out!
It's not betrayal as long as she doesn't find out.
If you talk to her,
I'm sure she'll understand.
If I were Hermes, I would, sex you, I mean, shun you!
('seikou' is most likely used to mean sex in this phrase)
Hermes will get electrocuted from all the shock!
If you expose this BBS,
your chances of making it to the World Cup
go down the drain!
This is the single-guys' association.
Densha...
Respond immediately!
Hey Densha!  You listening!?
I tried everything...
but I don't think I can go back there.
Good bye...
Densha.
Ow!  Ouch!!
Wait a minute...
This part...  Was this the problem all along?
기다려라 전차
Wait for me...
Densha!
Okay, gotta put this part here...
Hey what do you think you're doing?
This is...
No!
What's going on?
I really don't know what you're talking about
Why is stuff about sis written on there??
Did you do that?
How could you say such a thing?
...it must be him.
Yamada wrote all that, right?
I'll bet you hooked up with me because...
you wanted to snoop around on sis!
No, that's not true!
So you were in this together...
I can't believe this shit.
Hey!
Look, we're not trying to threaten you here.
You'll only self-destruct if you tell her about this BBS.
Densha, we're saying these things for your sake.
I don't want to see you get hurt!
if you tell her it'll be over for sure!
Are you okay with flushing all your efforts down the toilet?
I don't care if we're single forever.
I don't care if we're made fun of.
But for you...
we want things to go well.
We're putting all our hopes on to you
so just keep mum about this!
It's up to you to decide
if you've betrayed her or not.
But...
you need to think about what this board meant to you
and I want you to come up
with your own answer.
after giving this board a lot of thought, too.
Your thoughts and feelings
made me really happy.
Thank you
for worrying so much for me.
However...
I can't let things be.
Through this message board
I've explained everything
that happened between us.
and that...
what I did...
for her, may be something terrible.
but!
if I hadn't posted here
I never would have made it
with Hermes.
If I hadn't posted here
I never...
would have understood what it is...
to be able to like myself.
And more than anything,
I never would have...
met so many wonderful friends.
You guys...
because you guys were always there for me
I...
was able to make it this far.
This board...
is something I'm proud of.
So...
right now...
I'm going to...
tell her about this board.
My feelings...
everybody's feelings...
I want her to understand them...
In conclusion...
I'd like to say...
with feelings much stronger than words...
Guys...
I'm sorry.
...and
thanks.
What's wrong?
What's with the scary look on your face?
Sis, you were being tricked by that guy Yamada all along.
What?
That guy...
he was talking about you on the internet!
His encounter with you...
Your emotional problems...
He jokingly posted about everything to
everyone in Japan, and he was
making a fool out of you!
You're kidding...
I can't...
[-pant pant-]
What a scumbag
[Stalker]
[Surfing]
He betrayed you, sis.
Special thanks to:
d-addicts.com
Greyhorse
xiaryx
tianj
Binkley
T.Y.
Anonymous Korean subtitler (I'm sorry - I don't know your name)
Translation: Masakun
Scripting: Masakun
Editing: Masakun
Grammar check: Masakun
Timing: Anonymous Korean Subtitler
Yes, there are 11 episodes of Densha Otoko!
Why was Jinkama surfing the web in a hotel room, anyway?
Special thanks to:
d-addicts.com
Greyhorse
xiaryx
Binkley
T.Y.
Anonymous Korean subtitler (I'm sorry - I don't know your name)
Translation: Masakun
Scripting: Masakun
Editing: Masakun
Grammar check: Masakun
Timing: Anonymous Korean Subtitler
Yes, there are 11 episodes of Densha Otoko!
Why was Jinkama surfing the web in a hotel room?
Why has her role been reduced so much?
핍한 생활이 부족해서.. 과외도 구하고 있는데
여러분들의 도움이 필요합니다!
기부전화 060-700-덜덜덜덜 로! -_-;;
그럼, 즐거운 감상이 되셨길 바랍니다!
자막 제작 : 모리시타 (chandlerkim@gmail.com)
(blog.naver.com/mo_ri)
다음회 '전차남' 은
9월 15일(목)방송
기적의 최종장에 돌입!!!
키타--------
최종장에 돌입!!!