It's ringing.
Hi, this is Aoyama speaking,
Um, um, this is Y y yamada-
but I'm unable to take your call at this moment.
If you'd like to leave a message,
please do so after the beep.
Um, um this is Yamada calling,
but thank you for the c c cups-
Ow. It just had to be the edge...
Ah-  Just now, th, that wasn't meant for you and-
It was just her voice mail...
Maybe?
It's from the Train Man...how gross.
Please!  Let me answer it!
Who was it?
I don't know, probably a stranger.
731 - Alias Densha Otoko
I called her, but I only got her voice mail.
It still took guts; you've definitely leveled up.
I'd like to say "look at the time!",
but you did good.
Hope you try again tomorrow.
I'd never called a girl before,
but more than anything, I wanted to thank her.
So I'll definitely call her again tomorrow.
I'm all choked up watching you grow.
Who would have thought this whole incident
with Densha Otoko would get this far.
You should take it easy for tonight.  You get a B.
Phone Book
No: 125
Name: Aoyama-san
Group 0
Remaining Memory: 484/500
Options Remaining: 100/100
We'll be making stops at : Shinnkoiwa,
Kinnshicho, Bakurocho, Shinn-Nihonbashi, and Tokyo Stations.
Right clear, left clear.  Hey, you're late again!
I don't know where I'm supposed to go from here.
See here,
if you ask the fortune teller,
he'll tell you a story about the Demon Lord.
You're right.  Thanks.
Hey, does Master Yamada have a girl friend?
Uh, a girlfriend?
There's no way he would.
Yeah, I know.
If we hurt him too much, he might not help us with the game.
We'll be making stops at, Inagi, Tsudanuma, Funabashi, Ichikawa...
A girlfriend...I like the ring of that.
Hello.  Mother?
If you're calling about that, I'll talk to you about it later.
Ok?  Later then.
Another arranged marriage?
Right from the morning too.
Thursday 7th, 23:06
Voice Messaging Center
Um, um this is Yamada calling,
but thank you for the c c cups-
Yamada, you're free tonight aren't you?
Yes.
Then we're going to have dinner with one of our clients.
Dinner?
Yeah, dinner.
It's at 7:00 with the president of Hikari Sangyou.
But isn't that Oikawa-san's account?
Oh, sorry about this.  I have things I have to do.
You don't have to worry about anything, Oikawa.
It doesn't matter whose account it is, you little lackey.
I'll leave it to you then.
I'm off to see some companies.
Take care, Oikawa.
See you at 7:00...oops.
See you at 7:00, you little runt.
Ok.
Call History
7/10      9:35
Aoyama-san
Call History
7/8       9:32
Aoyama-san
Call From
Jinkama-san
Yes, this is Yamada speaking, but is there anything wrong?
Why else do you think I'd be calling?
Of course there's a problem.
How am I supposed to talk to you
about the trouble I'm having with my boss?
You're already having problems with your boss?
It's still the first day!
Well they say you should make a strong first impression.
I don't think that's what they mean.
Aoyama-san.
Isn't that oil paper a little big?  It's fine.
Are you listening?
Yes.
I was thinking...
Maybe it'd be easier if I just slept with the manager.
Um..Jinkama-san,
I've got a call on the other line.
Do you think I'm letting you off that easy?
No, I've really got another call!
Then why don't you just ignore it?
I really can't.
You know, from what I hear,
the manager seems to like it really wild!
Look, I really help you with things lik-
What is it, a guy?
Sort of.
Something going on.
I really don't know anything about the merry-go-round move.
Are you sure we're not liable if
anything happens while you're doing it?
Jinkama-san?
She just does what she wants...
Hey, are you done yet?  Hurry up!
So it's you...
I'm so sorry.  Sorry everyone.
Man, that was long...
Aoyama-san
Please recharge your batteries.
Why, why, why?
Oh yeah...
How do I call her now?
The Train Man
Original Story
"Densha Otoko"  by Nakano Hitori
Script:
Takefuji Shougo
Openning Theme
"Twilight" by Electric Light Orchestra
Ito Misaki
Ito Atsushi
Shiraishi Miho
Sudou Risa
Satou Eriko
Hayami Mokomichi
Kishibe Shirou
Akiyoshi Kumiko
Openning Anime Production       Character Design
GONZO                               OKAMA
Acting Director
Takefuji Hideki
Story 2
I should have wrote down her number.
I'm sorry.
Of course it wouldn't fit.
A charger, a charger.
Cell Phone Chargers
Found them.
What is it?
Nothing.
I see...
A convenience store, a convenience store.
I found one.
SAT: Special Assault Team
Umm.
I want to buy a battery charger.
It's an emergency.
Palace of Value
Don Quixote
I'm saved.
I couldn't reach your cell.
So this was where you were dawdling.
I wasn't.
What are you crying for?
We're off to dinner.
Until a car comes.
Mr. President, that joke was pure genious.
Really?
Do you have any other ones?
What did the slayer say to the vampire?
You have a stake at stake.
Ah, ha hA!  Oh help me, that was so funny!
So how old is your grandson now?
Oh, he turned 5 just last month.
He really likes this anime called Mina.
What?  Have you heard of it?
Yes, a little.
That's great then.
My daughter tried to explanation it to me
but I just can't seem to get through to him.
I haven't received any more voice mails either.
The person who helped you on the train?
Was he good looking?
I couldn't see him well because I wasn't
wearing my contacts, but
he looked...
designed for hard core anime fans.
It's done by Gonzo, who's famous for his high quality CG work.
He did it in an 80's style,
which is actually refreshing now.
The story's also a classic.
Trapped in the nether world, Mina's saved
only because he's interested in you.
It's gotta be it.
No way.  Anyway you look at it, he was your brave hero.
Like The Last Samurai, like Tom Cruise.
Well he was Japanese.
A Ken Watanabe huh?
This conversation's getting weird,
so leave your delusions to yourself.
What did you say to me?
I thought he really seemed like an earnest person.
exactly, there's no faulting his regard for her.
Her presence alone, as they travel through the nether world,
is enough to restore his soul.
If it wasn't for that
I don't think he would have called just to thank me.
And that's all a ploy just to lure you.
You really shouldn't take him seriously.
Isn't it you with the over-active imagination?
Get a boyfriend, and then I'll listen to you.
You've got a lot of nerve.  Let's take this outside.
But Mina decides to stay in the nether world
to vanquish the forces of evil!
She's-
I just got back home from work.
Finally, after all this time.
After all the times she called me.
He's back!!
You don't know how long I've been waiting for this.
First relax and have a cup of tea.
Tea can come later!
Call her up!
I'm going to call her now.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
You did it yesterday, you can do it today.
Don't cry if it goes badly.
Give us a full report when you're done.
Aoyama-san
Hello?
I guess he'll be calling her right now.
We have nothing to do but wait.
I don't think I've felt this way
since my days in the debate club.
This makes me think of watching my
son at school during open house.
I wonder what they're talking about now.
Densha's probably having a hard time.
I can see that happening.
Doesn't anyone else have problems?
There's nothing to do here.
After I got layed off at work, I filed for divorce,
and left our house.
I thought my wife would be angry with me,
but she's waiting for me to come back.
I just don't know what I should tell her.
Someone really responded.
I have no sympathy for guys this fortunate.
Mr. Layed Off, think about how your wife feels first.
I'm actually replying seriously.
How do you feel about your wife?
That's the important thing.
Haven't you learned anything from Densha?
I just got off the phone.
My hands are still shaking.
Yes!
You did good, you're a real man.
How'd it go?
She actually had to go take a bath.
Hermes-san says she'll call back later.
It was no good, I was too nervous...
Come on, tell us more.
You got KOed in the first round huh?
Hermes-san's in a bath?
Good job there, give us the details.
The details, give us the full scoop.
Ok, I'll explain what happened.
Hello?
5 min. ago
I'm calling on behalf of - oops.  Uh, uh.
This is Yamada calling.
Yamada-san?
I'm so glad.
We finally get to talk.
I'm sorry.
It's ok.
The cups.  Th, th, th, th, th.
Thank you so much for them.
I don't deserve anything so nice.
It's nothing.
I couldn't finish leaving you a message yesterday, and
I'm so sorry.
It's ok.
And I'm so sorry I couldn't return your calls immediately.
And it's taken me so long to finally call you.
Is anything wrong?
No, I'm sorry.
You keep apologizing, and all I can say is that it's ok.
I'm sorry-
You're an interesting person.
I almost forgot.
I didn't properly thank you that time.
Not at all.
It seems the police kept you pretty late.
Actually, we got to leave pretty soon after you did.
We were talking about you on the way to the station.
About me?
How you put yourself at risk for total strangers.
You were really brave for someone young.
Yamada-san?
I'm sorry.
It's kind of embarrassing.
Your bath's done.
I'll go in later.
It'll cool down.
It's going to have to wait.
Uhh.
I'm sorry.
My Mom's pestering me to take a bath.
I really don't mind.
No it's ok.  I'll go in later.
No really, I couldn't keep you.
Really?
Then can I call you back after I get out?
If it's not bother for you.
N, no.  It's no problem at all.
Then I'll talk to you later.
Ok, I'll be waiting then.
So now what should I do from here?
Let her know you want to meet her somehow.
Thank her by taking her out to dinner.
I totally agree.
Isn't a thank you dinner strange for a thank you gift?
I need a serious option here.
I'd say it's normal.
Can't you tell her you'd like to thank her in person?
I'm a girl,
but instead of saying you want to meet her,
you should just casually invite her to dinner.
Is Hermes still taking a bath?
I'm getting excited just thinking about it.
It's a guy isn't it?
So you were listening.
I just overhead you.
Is that so.
Take her to dinner to thank her.
"I feel bad recieving something so nice,
but is there anyway I can make it up to you?"
"I know, how about dinner sometime?"  What do you think?
This is it.
"I feel bad recieving something so nice,
but is there anyway I can make it up to you?"
"I know, how about dinner sometime?"  What do you think?
Hey, why don't you come here for a minute.
What is it?  Is there someone you want me to meet?
This time, he's perfect.
Then I'll look at it later.
Why not now?
Ok, I'll give it a good look.
I have to make a call now.
Again?
We were in the middle of talking.
I'm not saying you should stop dating.
This isn't like that.
Is that so?
I know, how about dinner sometime?  What do you think?
I feel bad recieving something-
She called.
Yes?
I'm sorry,
but did you wait long?
No.  Not at all.
You can do it Densha Otoko.
Please, let everything go well.
Densha, take it easy.
So this is it then.
I'm praying for you.
This is the first time I've prayed for someone.
How are you helping, getting all worked up yourselves?
Those c c cups you sent me.
They were really e e expensive, weren't they?
You really shouldn't have.
It's ok.
I can get them for cheap from where I work.
I'm sorry myself.
I didn't mean to make you feel uncomfortable.
Uh, uh, uh, ummm.
Please.  Let everything go welllll!!
The cups-
Um.  I wanted to thank you, b but
if it's ok, would you got to dinner wish mye?  Uh.
Um?
H, h, h, h, h, h, ho
H h how would you like to go to dinner?
I If it's ok, I'd like to t t treat you to something.
You don't have to worry about it so much.
It really wasn't that expensive.
Keep at it, keep at it, keep at it.
That's good.
It's really not right for you to treat me.
How about if we split the bill?
I think it'd be ok if we split it.
Really?
You'd really don't mind?
No.
So when should it be?
When we meet.
Let's see, what's a good day for you?
I'm... let me see.
How about next Sunday?
I'm free.
Then next Sunday it is.
Where should we eat?
Food.  Where's good?
Food?
Yes!!
Chinese, Japanese, Italian...  What should it be?
That noodle place we went to in Tokyo, what was it called?
Idiot!  You don't go for noodles on a first date!
Is it going well? Is that what it is?
Ask her if she can't eat anything first!
Ok.
These short sentences are great.
My heart's pounding here.
Is there anything you really like?  Anything you can't eat?
I can't eat anything too hot.
You can almost see what's happening on the other end.
Decide where to meet.
Where should we meet?
Do you know a good place to eat?
We'll find a good place, so keep her talking.
Umm, uhh.
How about one of those popular restaurant/bars?
Just don't choose a place too quiet.
Go Italian!
How about somewhere in the Aoyama neighborhood?
A , a, Aoyama.
Ok.
You can finalize where to eat when you meet her.
Tell her you'll contact her when you decide on a good place.
Can I call you back when I find a good place?
Sure, that sounds fine.
Find something good to end the conversation!
Ok, then I'll find somewhere good that isn't too hot.
Ok.
Did it go ok?
You were rejected weren't you?
I wonder if they're still talking?
Hurry up and let us know how it went!
I just got off the phone.
Succeeded in asking her to dinner.
The big day is next Sunday.
Thanks so much.  All of you.
Yes!!
Densha Otoko
Congratulations
Awesome Densha Otoko.
Densha, you're flying now.
Fantastic, have a fun dinner!!
What?  You're meeting that guy on the train?
The Last Samurai huh?  That's great.
He's probably no good.
And I'm totally ignored.
Anyway, why is it that you get so worked up
when it's about Saori?
Thats..
It's just dinner.  You two don't have to worry.
Ok then.
Stylish Restaurants
What are you doing reading something like that?
Jinkama-san.
If you were coming to our company,
you should have come to say hi.  It's customary.
So how did it go with your boss?
Well I already shacked up with him.
You shacked-
Really?
If you were to go to dinner,
hypothetically speaking,
where would you want to go?
With who?
With me.
It wouldn't happen.
I'm asking saying, if.
And I'm saying it could never happen.
There's no way a regular girl would
go to dinner with an Otaku like you.
Don't you know?
You have Otaku written all over you.
Otaku?
From top to bottom, you're pure Otaku.
You're such an Otaku, you can smell it.
You can smell it?
Yeah.  Fix yourself up, and like, try again.
Can you smell it?
I just realized something terrible.
I went ahead and asked Hermes to dinner,
but if she met an Otaku like me,
I'd come to a really messy end.
What should I do?
It's no use saying that now.
Forget dating if that's what you think.
I'm hopeless...
It's a pretty big problem,
but let's solve it step by step.
Don't worry; your main problem is your looks.
If you change how you look,
you should be able to hide your Otaku.
When you change how you look,
you change how you feel.
This thread has suddenly become a thread where we help the Train Man.
I see a complete lecture coming,
from clothes to what to say during a date.
Let's start with coordinating the clothes.
The Densha Otoko Renewal Project
If it's clothes, leave it to me!!
This is getting exciting!
Me first, me first!
Good luck Densha Otoko!
Would you guys go to Shibuya with me?
Shibuya?
Please?
You're crazy!
That isn't a place we can ever venture.
But I really need some help here.
We're not listening, we not listening!
Shibuya
You don't go around wearing a waist pouch,
with your sleeves rolled up do you?
Nah, guess not.
Our budget is 50,000 yen.
Is everyone ready?
First change your hairstyle.
Don't even think about going to some 1000 yen shop.
Not a barber, but a proper hair stylist.
If you want to go for impact, go with a hawk or dreads.
Short hair always gives you a good impression.
Forget blond hair, but some color is good.
I think you should leave it up to the stylists.
Oh yeah.
Can I leave it to you?
Certainly!
Don't get too excited with those soft female hands on you.
Hatoh Contacts
Next are the clothes.
It'll probably take him a while before he
can work up the courage to enter a store.
Think about Hermes.  Then you can do anything.
Welcome to our store.
Don't panic when you're asked what you're interested in.
Just think about Hermes.  You can really do anything.
If you're a man, you gotta style like a punk rocker.
Army wear says you can protect a girl!
The biggest point is the shoes;
go with a U or square tip.
For an artistic look, you want the clothes to fit tight.
Can't you go with what you have?
If your whole outfit's not brand name, it'll look lame.
We'll be over budget then.
As long as you coordinate it properly, it'll be fine.
Ask one of the store people what would look best on you.
That makes sense.
I guess Italian might be best for dinner.
Sushi, eating at a diner, fastfood,
cooking food over a hot plate... Noodles are out though.
A Bar/Restaurant has good atmosphere.
Another vote for a nice bar/restaurant
where you can get comfortable.
Your order's ready.
If you've never been to one before, you should go in advance,
so you won't dither when you order.
Makes sense.
I never thought I'd pay so much attention to what a woman says.
I hope we were able to help Densha Otoko at least a little.
H, hot.
No good for Aoyama-san.
I should check where the washrooms and cashier are located.
I'm home.
You're back.
Your Mom's gone on out to patroll.
Gross, what are you-
Your hair...and your glasses.
Uh, I thought I'd make it lighter.  Is it wierd?
Are you wearing cologne?
You can tell?
So it actually makes a difference.
Hey Tsuyoshi.
What are you trying to do?
Everything went according to plan.
I'm giving her a call right now.
Give it your best.
You can feel this aura from about his posts.
He doesn't sound flustered anymore, does he?
Ok.
Hello?
Sorry for c, calling so late at nyight.
Good evening.
How does Japanese sound, for dinner tomorrow?
That'll be fine.
That's good.
Japanese...that fits your image.
Really...
Also, about tomorrow.
I might go a little dressed up,
but please don't laught when you see me.
Dressed up?
Not that you shouldn't expect too much...
Really?
Then I'll also dress up for dinner.
I'm sorry.
For what?
I feel like I'm forcing you to dress up on my account.
Uhh...umm.
You know, you're right.
You shouldn't try to just please someone else.
It's not good for the either of you.
It was about something else I was thinking about.
I'll see you tomorrow then.
Ok, tomorrow then.
What do you think of this?
I was thinking...
do you think you can call off meeting this person?
Why?
If I'm not interested in him,
I think it would be impolite.
You're still not ready?
Saori,
I'm sorry.
I went out and bought all these Kimonos you know.
I'm not giving up you know?
It went kind of like that.  I think I messed up.
No, no.  I think it was fine.
You're hot stuff, Densha Otoko.
I'm into Hermes too now.
I think all your best qualities showed through.
It's going to be pretty exiting come Sunday.
You know, I haven't actually thought about
going out with Hermes-san, or anything yet.
It's true that I'll never get a chance like this though.
I am definitely feeling attracted to her.
When I talked to her just now,
I felt something more than just nervousness.
If I meet her again, I'll probably end up falling for her.
Of course she probably has a boyfriend,
and then if I do fall for her, I'm really going to suffer.
It hurts right now.
But that a total loser like me could ever feel this way,
is really an amazing thing.
And it's all because I had all of you around.
Reading your posts, I somehow got this
feeling that everything would go well.
It really gave me the confidence to continue.
Receiving all your prayers and encouragement,
I think I was able to grow a little.
Your support was what allowed me to change.
These past several days seemed both so short and so fast...
It's a strange feeling.
So thank you.
For all your precious feelings,
thank you so very much.
I'm going to give this everything I have.
It's me.
I want us to get together again.
I remembered what it was like back when we first met.
How precious you were to me back then.
I can't hear what it is, you're saying.
All right.
Wash face.
If you're using a shaver, use it here.
Trim nose hair.
Clean ears.
Don't use too much wax!  Just blend it in lightly.
4. Get Dressed
Put on cologne here.  Careful not to put on too much!!
Give it here.
The cologne.
Now just rub your wrists together.
This is it?
How much did you put on yesterday?
I don't know who you're going to meet,
but if you put on that much, they'll hate you instead.
I heard I'm such an Otaku, you can smell it.
Are you that dense?
They didn't mean you actually smell.
Just that you wreck the atmosphere wherever you go.
That's what it was.
Hey,
Do I still look like an Otaku?
It's ok, I guess.
I'm leaving my house now.
Thanks for everything.
I'll be sure to post as soon as I get back.
Only an hour left!
She'll come.  She won't.
She'll come.
She won't.
Next Episode
This piece of fiction is based on a true story.