[Good luck at work, and work hard]
Working hard.
Yamada!
Huh?
Did you learn to surf in time?
No,
but when I apologised, she forgave me.
I knew it.
Ah, wai- give it back.
This girl,
she doesn't know does she?
What?
That...
you're an otaku.
Otaku
I wonder what she'd do if she found out.
If it was me, I'd probably never see you again.
Work hard, and good luck at work.
Otaku idiot.
What is it?
Nothing.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
I didn't think Yuki would drink so much.
It was only class reunion afterall.
Did something happen to her recently?
Why do you ask?
Something to do with her Father maybe..
How can you say that?
Doesn't it matter how I feel?
Leave me alone already.
Did she say anything?
No no.
It's probably just my imagination.
Don't worry about it.
Thank you very much.
The Train Man
Original Story
"Densha Otoko"  by Nakano Hitori
Script:
Takefuji Shougo
Openning Theme
"Twilight" by Electric Light Orchestra
Itou Misaki
Itou Atsushi
Shiraishi Miho
Sudou Risa
Satou Eriko
Hayami Mokomichi
Kishibe Shirou
Toyohara Kousuke
Akiyoshi Kumiko
Openning Anime Production       Character Design
GONZO                               OKAMA
Director
Nishiura Masaki
You're taking courses?
Yep, "How to live the life of a lonely hag".
You don't have to get so pessimistic.
You'll find a boyfriend someday.
When's someday?
I don't even get asked to matching parties anymore.
I have to look for places to meet guys using a magnifying glass.
Think about it,
the chance of meeting a hot guy out on the street like this...
could be pretty good.
What?
Hey, it's Yamada Tsuyoshi.
Yamada?
What, that Yamada?
Yeah, THE Yamada.
He's great, it's destiny, how dramatic.
You should haved figured it out from our conversations.
It's the puny one.
Oh.
The friend is seriously good looking.
Huh? A matching party?
Um.. If you don't want to, you don't have to.
Yamada,
take this with you when you go.
Ok, I got it.
Really? It's ok.
Uh..That.. That.. was..
There will be 3 of us then.
Yes, see you there.
I got asked to a matching party by Hermes-san.
I said ok in the spur of the moment, but this is a problem right?
Of course it's a big problem.
I can't help you there though,
that's unknown territory.
I can't think of Hemes going to a matching party.
Then let it to me!
Her friends might have asked her to arrange it.
You're new.
I've been assigned here now.
I hope we can get along.
My name is-
It's ok.
No one else but you comes here anyway.
You're only going to make a fool out of yourself.  Decline.
1st look good, 2 go with the flow
3 make it happen.
They say your friends say a lot about who you are.
Just find some friends who you can show Hermes.
Just don't call any Otaku friends, it's going to hurt otherwise.
Otaku
This is all getting out of hand.
What should I do?
Hey, hey!
Don't close it, touch it, or look at it.
Got it?
Yes.
A matching party?
That's going to be a problem.
It's been a while,
how's work been since then?
Oikawa-san,
I can take you to a matching party if you want.
No, thats' too arrogant.
Oikawa-sama,
could you possibly accompany me to matching party?
and that's too formal.
A matching party?  Sure.
When is it?
It's tonight.
Tonight?
OK I'll leave my schedule open.
Really?
Thank you so much!
Don't cry.
A matching party?
Why?
I don't know.
Good evening ladies.
Good evening.
Why?
Why does this kind of thing happen?
Ow, ow, you're strangling me.
I've gone to the beauty salon for this,
and went to a spa,
and got my nails done at a store that movie stars go to.
For the first time in a year,
no, in 3 years, I bought underwear that's not beige.
Yuka, you're going to kill me!
Why were we drafted for this mission?
The other guys cancelled at the last minute.
But to ask us to hide our Otaku.
Is really pushing the limits of credibility.
And that's what I'm begging you to try.
Is there something the matter?
Gyha!  It went well!
The women seemed to be happy.
I guess you should give anything a chance.
Kawamoto-shi, your jive was magnificent.
Oh, dude.  I'm so in trouble.
Even deader than the MK5!
Stop it, stop it,
Matsunaga-shi, you were great too.
Your sea turtle gag had them rolling in their seats.
I hate to say it myself, but-
that was the worst dirty joke ever!
How do they come up with something so lame?
We're talking about sea turtles laying eggs.
It was so realistic it was gross.
The act with the glasses was so pathetic he had me shivering.
I'll tear them apart with my bare hands!!
Wait, senpai!
I wonder if everything went ok.
Hm?
Uh.. well...
It's just that it seemed your friends
looked angry when we left the store.
I think they had a good time.
I had a good time too.
I'm glad you said that.
Did you hear about the stalker?
Scary isn't it?
[Serial Stalker Murders]
Are you tired?
No.
You can sleep if you want.
I'll wake you before you get to your station.
I'm all right.
Well ok.
It's pretty late isn't it?
You don't have a curfew do you?
I'm not that young anymore.
Um.
Yes?
I can accompany you home if you'd like.
That's ok.
Thank you for the thought.
Well ok then.
Thank you for today.
I enjoyed it as well.
I'll mail you again.
Good night.
Actually,
could you accompany me home?
Yes.
...she gently look my hand
and lead me off the train.
We ended up leaving the station together from there.
Oh Hermes.
I think even I'm falling in love with you.
Right now, I'd do anything you say.
Then for awhile,
do you think I could sleep over here?
Eh?
See, I just broke up with my girlfriend.
Nope.
You just said, you'd do anything I asked.
Idiot.
Who said I was talking to you?
Besides, you have a home you can go back to.
I don't want to go back there.
You know Keisuke,
you can't stay so selfish forever.
You're not a kid anymore.
This is a huge house.
I wonder what kind of people live here.
It's here, this is my house.
Thank you so much for everything.
Not at all.
I was actually a little afraid.
Lately, I get this feeling someone's watching me.
Someone?
I could be just imagining it though.
Oh, so that's why you asked?
I'm sorry.
No, no.
I'm glad I could help.
Well, it was kinda like that.
Like what?  What were you waiting for?
I want to escort Hermes-san too!
You've really matured, being able to take her home.
You've had courage all along.
You can tell her you like her soon.
It's still waay too early.
All right, let's all think of ways that Densha
can tell Hermes how he feels.
He can decide that for himself.
Yeah, that's not our job.
Everyone's getting ahead of themselves.
[It turns out I wasn't just imagining it]
[I found all these pictures of myself in my mailbox just now]
[Aoyama Saori]
An emergency just came up.
It looks like someone's following Hermes-san around.
[Stalker]
What!!
Give us the details.
It seems she's noticed someone watching
her on her way to work lately.
And now someone's dropped off all these pictures of her.
If we can't figure out what's happening, the police can't do a thing.
Even if we went to the police,
there's a good chance they'll ignore us.
Bastard!
I'll take my American M72A2 bazooka,
and smash him to smithereens.
Alert, alert!
We've just found someone more dangerous that the stalker!
Target eliminated.
I'm a girl, but knowing it might be someone you know
it makes it hard to speak out.
Please help her Densha-san.
Then what should I do?
I want to help Hermes-san too.
I'm sure we can come up with something.
Aren't there anti-surveillance goods you can buy at Akihabara?
I'm sure she'd be happy having you to walk her home.
Make sure you shred all her garbage.
Covering your tracks is the most important thing in espionage.
Dark curtains prevent people from knowing
when you're home.  Good.
Thanks for all of your suggestions.
I want to set her at ease as soon as possible.
I'll see what I can do on my end.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I went out and bought some things you might be able to use.
Anti-crime buzzer.
A sniffer to find bugs.
and this, and this...
And a stun gun.
And...
I've compiled a list of things you can do to prevent stalkers.
If you have a chance, please have a look at it.
Anti-Stalker
Manual
So you could read it in the shortest possible time,
I'll highlighted the key parts.
Just reading those should make a difference.
You did this in one day?
I'm sorry.
I thought it might be a bother, but...
I'm pleased you went to the trouble.
Thank you very much.
Not at all.
Also...
I, i, if it's ok, with you...
C, could I w, walk you to and from work?
What?
Uh... See...
It's not that I want to walk with you or anything, but
I can't bear to sit by and not do anything.
I can't ask that of you.
I'm really ok.
It's a bother, isn't it.
It's not that.
I just think it'll be too much trouble for you.
Please.
Then ok.
Hm?
Thank you for letting me do this.
Um.
Yes?
What are we supposed to talk about at a time like this?
Let's see...
I'm sorry.
I really don't know about these things.
How about movies?
Movies?
What kind do you like?
It's been a while,
but the Matrix comes to mind.
With Keanu Reaves.
Do you know it?  I loved it.
It's commonly known that the Matrix was
heavily influenced by Japan Anime.
In a recent discussion between Director Oshii
and the Wachowski Bros.,
Oshii said he would have used Gina Gershon
for the role of Trinity.
S s sorry.
...and so I became her bodyguard because I was worried about her,
but I ended up worrying in a different way.
I was happy to spend such a peaceful time
together with her though.
I can't stand it anymore.
I feel sick.
Could you please bring me a glass of water?
You know,
there's this tea that helps when you have a hang over?
Probably.
Do you want to go together?
No.
Why not?
It's that store Keisuke works at right?
That's why I'm not going.
Mother?  You don't want Keisuke to come back home?
Not a bit.
Keisuke always sides with his Father.
Densha, aren't you forgetting something?
It's good that you're enjoying your peaceful time together,
but that's not solving any of her problems.
Forward, Melos.
That's true.
I really do want to do something.
Without knowing the identity of the stalker
there isn't much we can do.
It's not a job for amateurs like us.
It would he good to have some hints.
How about those photos that were sent to Hermes-san?
Depending on the angle of the shot,
you can figure out where it was taken.
Good point.
That's definitely worth following up on.
What are you planning on doing once you find the stalker?
There's no way you'll find him.
It it was me, I'd start by hitting him.
Will Densha have the muscles to fight the stalker?
I'm worried.
He might have a knife.
Knife
Don't spook me out like that.
But if I do find him-
Sic the police on him.
I'd lecture him for 5 hours.
Find him first, then think about it.
You'll deal with it in your way.
The photos are in here.
Thank you.
Let's go.
But what are you planning to do?
Don't worry about anything.
I'll protect you no matter what.
All right.
17 o'clock.
T minus 5...
_4_
_3_
_2_
_1_
What are you planning, leaving on time?
I'm sorry.
I have things I have to do.
Bah~  Hey, phone.
I'm Yamada's supervisor.
Yamada's currently busy, and cannot come to the phone.
I'll take your message for him.
Ok, all right.  Uh huh.
Here, have it back.
It's from some girl called Aoyama.
She'll be meeting a friend today,
so she doesn't need you to pick her up.
A f, f, friend?
Her f, f, friend, is probably a guy.
So what's Mom learning today?
Otoko (1st 2 syllables reversed)
A guy?
Here.
Koto Lessons
Dispair
I got a call from Hermes-san saying she'll be meeting a friend,
and so she wouldn't need me to walk her back.
I think I messed up.
A friend...could be a significant other.
That's her boyfriend for sure.
Did you ask her if she was seeing anyone?
Not yet.
It doesn't sound like it from what you've told us so far.
It might have all been for nothing.
She has her own life too.
That's true.
From her POV,
it might have all been a bother.
Maybe,
I'm just a stalker too.
Don't worry about it.  Just think about protecting her.
Quit thinking negatively.
It doesn't matter if she has a boyfriend,
or if she thinks you're a bother.
You're working hard to make sure she stays safe, right?
You're right.
I lost sight of what I was doing.
I'll go and find her stalker now.
I'll protect you!
He seemed pretty enthusiastic, but is it going to go that easily?
His movements will be between her station and her house.
It's here.
Next!
This looks like it.
Maybe he'll be mistaken as a stalker himself.
I can imagine him being questioned right now.
It's going to take a while investigating each picture one by one.
We'll be cheering you on even from our graves.
We're not dead yet.
I know what you're trying to say.
But Mother-
Then why hasn't she called me once?
I was just telling her to divorce and try to start moving ahead.
She just-
That's why she can't apologize.
She hasn't been able to  move forward.
Mother's not that strong.
Look, I'm sorry.
But I not going back.
I think Mother wants you close by right now.
Yes, hello?
She's here.
Hold on a moment.
Sis, it's from work.
Let's check here too.
The angle's right.
The position...
is around here.
[Imura Shunpei]
Please, please...
He's not home.
Often in dramas, places like this
are unlocked?
It openned.
You again.
L, L, Lo
Hello?
Yes.
Aoyama would be me.
There's a package here for you.
we need to verify receipt,
but would you mind coming here as soon as possible?
Does it have to be today?
All right.
I'll head over there right now.
See you there.
I have to head back to work.
Sorry for intruding.
I'm coming in.
What's all this?
Incredible.
Cute.
This is Yamada,
but are you ok?
She's not around at the moment.
It's a guy.
She left a while ago after being called to work.
Is there anything I can do?
Oh no!
From someone who loves you very much.
Aoyama-san!
Ow, ow, ow...
Are you ok?
I'm so sorry.
I was in such a rush, and it's all my fault.
[Imura Shunpei]
Uh, uh, i if you don't mind my asking...
you're not by any chance, Aoyama-san's stalker are you?
You shouldn't-
Get away from me!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do this kind of thing.
I've hardly talked with any girls.
And that's why,
I don't know how to go about it.
I just wanted her to notice me.
I know how you feel.
That's a lie.
No one could know-
I've also never dated a girl in my life.
So...
I don't know what they're thinking.
I try to act differently so she'll like me,
but it doesn't work.
When I'm with Aoyama-san,
I'm just as scared as I am happy.
Never knowing when this happiness is going to disappear.
I'm really a pathetic guy.
It work I'm always scolded.
I'm made fun of by my family.
Anything I try,
I can't do right.
It's the same when I'm with Aoyama-san.
When I call her,
my hands are always shaking.
And my voice gets all squeaky.
Because I don't want to be seen wearing the same clothes,
I buy a new set every time.
I can hardly drink,
but I pass it off like I hardly feel it.
I really want to know if she has a boyfriend,
but I'm so afraid of the answer
I can't ask her.
And that's why
I can empathize.
I've felt everything you've felt.
I'm like a stalker too.
That's not so.
All I ever did was hurt her.
But you...
This is my best picture of her.
I also wanted to become like you.
I didn't get here on my own.
There's people out there,
who cheer me on,
and scold me,
and encourage me.
I have all these people,
who watch over me.
Try again tomorrow.
It's the first time I've ever really cheered someone on.
Please,
let everything go well.
Densha, you're our hope.
Take it easy for today.
B.
Densha
You can do it, Densha Otoko.
Ok, I'm ready.
You can take me in now, I'll go wherever you tell me.
Then,
let's go see Aoyama-san.
And apologize to her.
I'll go with you.
[That's true.]
[Still, he taking forever.]
[Maybe the tables got turned.  Is he ok?]
Densha's talking forever.
Maybe he's been pummeled already.
Carried into a hospital in an ambulance.
Even without Densha here, there's an awful lot of us here.
We're a strange group aren't we?
Bound by solidarity?
Friendship! Comrades! Unity!
Sounds like something out of a teenage comic.
I thought we all hated the idea of banding together.
It's the opposite.
I think that's what we're all hoping for.
I just like being here.
It's getting mushy in here. You guy are laying it on a little thick.
Densha, when are getting back?
[Express]
[Densha Otoko]
[We're all with you!]
Kaoru-chan,
It's getting late; you should sleep.
Good night.
This is the second time.
That I've been saved by you.
No, no.
It seems like I'm always causing a commotion.
He was saying he'd go back to the country side.
Really?
Um.
Yes?
When I called your cell phone earlier,
a, a , a man answered.
Hm?
My cell..
It must be at Keisuke's
Keisuke?
He's my little brother.
Your brother.
It's late, who is it?
What happened?
Here, Saori forgot this.
You came here just for that?
Man, I'm hungry.
All we have's beer.
I'm back.
Thank you for today.
No,
Thank you.
I'll mail you again.
Ok.
Good night.
Could I walk you home?
Yes.
Densha,
If you're not back yet, could it mean...?
Did he finally tell her!
We'll be giving out a 100 CDs containing the ending theme
for this drama as performed by Sambo Master.
For your chance to win, please send us a post card
with your commends to the following address.
Next Week
This peice of fiction was based on a true story.