[Kibonnu, Returned.]
I got to go to Akiba with Hermes-san ^-^
What?!
Akiba? You mean the fortress of Otakus,'Akihabara'?
"This type of guy, that type of guy, this, that, this, that guy!?
Guys who are broke!!
Ah~ even guys like this!!!"
You mean that 'Akihabara'?
Moreover, aren't you showing her too much?
Details! In Japan!
Then I will explain the phone call will Hermes-san briefly...
No! No! Tell us fully!
Conversations with women are always new to us
Please, kill us slow~ly and painfully!
All right. I will tell you what happened
Um... Do you remember the promise?
Pro...mise?
You forgot?
Um... Um....
Co...m...pu...ter.....
You did forget
Sorry
Then
As a punishment
Please come with me next time
OK!
What is up with this sudden happy-mode
I am excited! Hermes! Moe~~~
Until now I was cheering him on! But... but... but...
Medic! Medic!
There is no hope for you!
How are you... going to use the computer?
Just to access the Internet... and write mails
Then... it must be easy to use
Where do you usually go to buy computers?
I... usually go to Akiba....
Usually Akihabara
Then we will go there
Um... but... if you really don't care about specifics
Any store would be...
I want to go where you usually go
Huh?
I want get to know you better
Bombs~! It is not late! To the shelter!!!!
It's too late. Bye.
This is the conversation that I was dreaming about!!
And they are actually doing ittttt!!!
So... date in Akihabara...
Akiba, the best!
Hermes-san is wearing a maid costume in my dreams!
Maid costume...
Welcome home~ Master
No! No! Not a cute Hermes-san!
Do you need to go to the hospital?
To go with Densha's otaku fashion
You can't go wrong with a flower patterned one-piece with tantalizing skirt length & pigtails
How about this?
Pigtails moe~
Ahh~
Let's look for a computer for Hermes-san!
Please~
OK~
Densha Otoko
Subbed by: Hijouguchi Team
hijouguchiteam@yahoo.co.jp
[Akihabara]
Um...
Yes?
You want to hold hands?
Huh?
Is it ok with you?
My pleasure~
L...Let's go
I didn't know what you exactly wanted...
Maybe it won't be much of a help...
Did you research all this?
Because that is...
All I could do for Aoyama-san...
I appreciate it so much
Thank you
No... It's okay
In Akihabara
There are a lot of people with backpacks
Do they all sleep overnight somewhere?
No, they all go home right away
I am glad you found something you like
No... it is all because of your help
No... not really...
You want to take sticker photos?
Over there
You... you mean... just the two of us?
Oh, you don't want to?
No, no! My pleasure~
2 (Here!)
Ah, one more shot
Really?
Back here, back here
It is a little bit weird...
But as a keepsake
Thank you
Wow, you are great! Yamada-san
Yamada-shi!
Hello
Matsunaga-shi
Aoyama-san is here, so go for Shibuya-style
Waa it's so tight we met out of nowhere~
!@$@!$ nothing !@$!
It's okay now...
I can't understand him, yo~
So funny!
I mean
You don't have to talk in Shibuya-style anymore
What?
Really, Yamada-shi?
Did you confess that you were otaku?
You grew up!
But
Here
Aoyama-san, are you okay...
Hanging out with people like us?
Regardless of being okay, it's fun~
What a nice person!
Compared to high school girls or OLs (Office Ladies) that get to us
You are about 23 levels higher
Maybe 15000 in terms of experience?
Level?
Experience?
Do you often come to Akihabara?
About four times a week
We look at girl-stuffs or figures
If there is an event, we go there
Girl-stuff?
It is a "bishoujo"(pretty girls) game
Definitely moe~
Moe~
Um...
One more time, please!
Moe~~~
This is...
My own secret place
Really?
Yes
You...
Are the first person that I ever told
Then it is our secret place now, the two of us
Yes
When I come here
I get courage
So
I only come here on special occasions
Then, is today a special occasion?
Eh? N.. No...
That is not what I meant...
Hey~ Perfect chance to confess!
If you can't, when will you ever be able to?!
Hermes-san is definitely waiting for it
Um...
Yes
No...
No...thing...
Nothing...
Oh... I see...
Densha, you sure you want to go out with Hermes-san!?
You are not even qualified to be a human-!!
I did think it was a chance...
But, it hasn't been long since we got back...
And I thought
"If I do get to go out with her, what kind of person am I?" So...
Don't be weak!
And you say you are a Japanese!
You forgot Yamato spirit?
Well, Yamato spirit has nothing to do with this... Or so I thought
If you are sincerely seeing her and the atmosphere is warm
Then I don't think you need to hurry and tell her
Your urge to confess will be uncontrollable until you actually do it
Let's not push him anymore
For now, rather than bunch of singles telling him what to do
Densha's own choice is more valid
Densha, tell her when you think the time is right
Relax
Whatever happens, I will be with you to the end
Haa Haa Haa Haaaa~
WTF?
What Densha? What is going on?
He's gone crazy~~~!
Which reply sent him mad?!
Because you guys were hurrying him to tell her
Densha went mad!
Densha, return normal!
Hermes-san sent me her photo in sleeping clothes with photo mail drftgyhujiko
Hey, it was just Hermes-san's photo?
What was that bombing!
Why are you attacking us! We are unarmed!
Sleeping clothes? Pajamas? Negligee?
Pajamas
Me, worried about you? I feel so stupid
Just confess or something, stupid asshole!
She is rolling around on her bed
So cute~
Shit, I never wanted to see Hermes-san's face this bad
Hey everyone, who are you imagining her as?
Nakatani Mikiro!
Definitely, Baisho Michiko in her prime
No! No! It is Ooba Kumiko
Ogura Yuko, or Yukorin~
I was thinking of Kuninaka Ryoko-san
You guys, you think such pretty girls would have Densha on their radar?
Geez, this is why an otaku's imagination is so disturbing
But even more than anyone on television
I like her
I am... getting... mad...
Densha, I don't know what you are thinking...
... but Hermes-san is not your girl yet
Shhh!
Well said
So hurry and get her
Don't forget you were the one who saved her
That's right
Even if she wants to say no, maybe she can't
Chase after her and subdue her!
Yeah...
Of course. Sorry for being carried away OTL
I should know where I stand
This time, I am going to install the computer in her room
So I thought I could confess to her then
But never mind
I am going to sleep. Good night
Wait!!!
What, her room?!
You should tell us something that important first!
More than that, don't give up on confessing!
Sorry, we were bad to you!
We were joking! Tell us when you are going!
Densha! Don't sleep!
Reply~! Reply please! Reply~! Reply please!
Densha (subway) can't depart!
This way please
Excuse me
Mom
This is Yamada-san
Welcome
Saori
Where is Yamada-san?
What?
This is Yamada-san
Hello
My name is Ya.Ya.Ya...Yamada
(Bark!)
Saori
Did you put on your contacts?
Yes
Then... that is a joke?
To me.... more like... a weird... organism...
You are being rude to Yamada-san
Um... that...
Why did I get my hopes up only to be disappointed
Nice to meet you
Please come to my room
Hello?
This is Aoyama spea...
Please come in
Is this
Aoyama-san's room?
I will bring tea
So please make yourself at home
Sure
Um...
Yamada-san
Looks like a good person
He has his charms
If you look at him right, he does look okay
Your attitude is so different from a while ago
Really?
Anyway
This Sunday
Let's invite Yamada-san as a family
And eat dinner together
Why are you acting this way so suddenly?
Smells good~
Is anything wrong?
No, nothing...
This is a good computer
Here
Thank you
Can I help you with anything?
No, it will be done soon
Please sit down and rest
Really?
These days...
It's been hot, hasn't it?
Yes
I don't like summer that much
Really?
If the clothes are thin, I can't hide my figure
But
Aoyama-san is skinny
So I don't think there is any problem
You said it
Huh?
Friends and mom think
Because I am so thin
I am not that attractive
Ah, I see
Maybe because I am always like this
I can't get a boyfriend?
What?
You don't have a boyfriend?
No
How about a fiance?
What are you talking about?
No boyfriend~
FREE---!!!
Are you okay?
Oh, nothing
But
I think...
Regardless of your figure
Aoyama-san is great
The guys around you
Don't have the sense to see it
Um....
Please don't talk that way
[Confession]
-Um... -Um...
Aoyama-san first
Um... Actually...
This Sunday
Do you want to eat dinner with my family?
Dinner?
Okay
Then
I will tell you the details later
Okay
With... Fa..family...?
What should I do?
Now it is dinner with Hermes-san's family
According to her, her father won't come
Why did I ever say yes~ OTL
It is punishment for making us wait
Another trial before the confession
But, if her father won't be there, all we have to aim for is Hermes's mother
I think you should make Hermes's mother satisfied with you
Rich women will look at your appearance first
My mom is not rich, but she hates untidy men too
That doesn't help!
But still, you should be tidy
How about my usual clean clothes?
If you are eating with her family, you should dress up
Choosing suits rather reveals your sense
Go in tuxedo
Ask me about suits. I can talk about them for three hours!
If there is anything else you should be careful about when dining...
Of course, are your table manners all right?
Table manners?
BbrrrrrRRRRRRRR!!! (shiver)
Of course you don't know... OTL
I will tell you how to eat banana with honor!
Conversation skills that make the dining enjoyable are also important
Go to a self-improving seminars!
Read newspaper to keep up with current events
Task at hand is suits, newspaper, table manners, and conversation
This flow... It's been a while! Want to do it again?
Densha Otoko
Renewal Project
Part 2
Um... Where did you buy those suits?
With suits, giving good impression is more important than being trendy
Rather than magazines, well-dressed people around you will be more helpful
Oikawa-san
Where did you buy those suits?
Paris Milan New York
Ah.. Sumizura from Milano?
Oh, of course I can't win against Oikawa-kun
Mine is also Italian
Of course, I can't win against Oikawa-kun, hahaha
You can find a lot of well-dressed people among company superiors
That's true
Awesome!
Of course
Japanese suits are a little hard to wear
That's right
Of course...
Eh?
Um... this is...
Japanese
Oh... Um... Yeah...
Huh?
Communication with Hermes's mother is important
But Densha's improving his conversation skills might be impossible
How about starting with complements?
Nobody hates complements
Be very humble
What are you doing? You make me sick
Oh Jinnkama-san, you have the best dirty mouth in Japan!
You want to fight me?
Always smile!
Nice sense!
You put such heavy make up on! You look younger!
Shut up!
Nice sense!
The thoughtless facial expression is great!
DEATH
For sure, the recipient will be smiling too!
Haa~ How refreshing!
Lastly, table manners
Don't hold the knife backwards
Or make sounds when drinking soup
Only manners, but still manners!
Um... Are you really okay?
If I don't do this much, I won't be able to remember in such short time
All right
Start with the knife and fork on the outside
Okay
Ohh~ What are you doing?
Can you switch with me?
If he is even a little weird, then push this
Okay okay! Leave it to me!
I will be a good judge!
After eating...
Wipe mouth with a napkin...
Drink
Too long~ Too long~
Was something weird?
Nono, just your face
Yamada and Saori's family are eating dinner together?
But I can't find a good restaurant
Saori, you bought a computer recently
Then
Look it up on the internet
Senpai, you use the internet?
Heyhey, you know about Aladdin channel? (2ch)
Aladdin channel?
It is a forum becoming very popular these days
People can talk about any personal problems
What?
Oh I heard
That it was a vulgar site
Where otakus swear and write about creepy things
Really?
I was thinking of talking about my guy-issues
Saori
Someone my father knows runs a restaurant
Really?
Really
[Aoyama Kengo]
[Divorce Papers]
T...TTT...Today...
Thank you for treating me to dinner
You don't need to be so nervous
So, can I go back?
No
You have to stay
I have no reason to be here
Thank you for coming today
Tonight under the name 'Sakurai Kazuya-sama'
By the wish of 'Sakurai Kazuya-sama'
The whole restaurant was reserved
That's great
Reserving the whole restaurant
Nope
To 'Sakurai Kazuya-sama'
We are always indebted
Please, enjoy your time
Hey you...
Did you say my name three times?
Yes
Full name
Three times
All right. Everyone listen up!
I bought out this restaurant for the day!
I demand complete obedience to my commands!
Understood?
Yes, sir!
Densha~
As of today, it is "The End"
It's spicy
It's delicious
Yes quite good
It is delicious, isn't it?
Yes, indeed
[For Yamada]
Thank you
Drink drink drink
It's hot
Drink drink
Drink drink drink drink drink drink
Drink! If you don't go to the toilet
Main dish can't start!
I can't hold it anymore
I am going to leak in my pants
Sorry but...
Please excuse me for a moment
Drink drink drink drink drink drink drink drink
Good
Mizeshi, come out!
Fake Tsuyoshi!
You will be his replacement!
Is this really okay?
Huh?
Yeah
You look alike. Look alike
Don't worry
Let's go, fake Tsuyoshi!
Father
Father?
Wait, don't go
What are you going to do?
Mother
Explain what is going on
Even if I am getting a divorce with this man, I have nothing to say to him
That is why I told you guys to come
What?
Why didn't you tell me?
If I told you, you wouldn't have come
Of course not
Yuki
Did you bring it?
Let's not talk about it here
You are going to run away like that again?
Then sign it now
Stop it... not here
Um....
Who are you?
Ah... Um... Um...
I... I am...
Yamada Tsuyoshi-san
My friend
Oh? I am Saori's father
Yes?
Sorry but
We have important family business to talk about
Can you leave now?
Then
I will go back
Sorry
It's okay
Thank you
For today
Um...
I... have to go my next appointment
Thank you
It's been eight years now
You said
Until Keisuke graduates from college
You wouldn't divorce
So I waited
Now it's fine, right?
I have an appointment after this
Can you hurry up?
Is that person waiting for you?
It's none of your business!
Mother, hurry up and do it
Be quiet, Keisuke
If you don't make a decision here
It will only harm the family
Because of mother and father
My sister can't trust men anymore
Keisuke
Don't get us involved
Is that so, Saori?
What are you saying now!
Shut up!
Stop it, Keisuke
Um...
I forgot something...
I am going back
Hurry up and get it
Sorry
What now?
N.. No...
Marriage is...
Something so amazing
Just dating someone
Is such a huge thing for me
But
Proposing
Meeting each other's parents
Buying a ring
Having a wedding
For sure,
It is continual display of an unimagniable amount of courage
What are you trying to say?
Be quiet
Actually
Even I
Do not know what I am saying
Just
I don't want to see
Aoyama-san's sad face
Also I
Have a father and a mother
They are different from Aoyama-san's
That it is hard to lean on father
And mother is frequently not home
Even then
They...
Always smile
Because of useless things
As if they were stupid
So...
Even I...
Relax and smile with them
Children want
Their parents
To smile
Definitely
Even more than anyone
They wish for their parents to be happy
So
Always
They want their parents to be smiling
For some reason...
Sorry
Here
Divorce papers
I even signed it already
Yuki
All right.
Mother
I think now I can understand a little bit
Why you chose him
Let's go
Saori
Sorry
Father
See you again
I lost
Densha Otoko
Um...
Hands....
You want to hold hands?
Sure
It went something like this
Good job! I feel like crying! Densha!
Is Densha's mobilesuit a monster!?
Renewal Project was all useless
If the ending is good, all is good!
Looks like you left a good impression with Hermes-san's mother
Mission cleared!
So your blind spot is gone now
Now it is the confession! For real!
This is getting big!
Talking about getting big,
This forum also became quite famous
Yeah, there are more people involved now
It is only natural for people to be attracted to interesting things
Oh, I overheard some high school girls talking about this forum in the subway
I was also surprised that my friend knew about it
Now we are famous!
But if it gets bigger and bigger
Hermes-san might find out about this forum
There is a possibility that Hermes-san's friend might find out about it
BbrrrrrrRRRRR
What do you think, Densha?
I don't think it is a problem...
"No don't say anything!" trying to upset him
How are you so optimistic?
This is where all your inner thoughts are
"It smelled good" "Age = years without a girlfriend"
All your bizarre statements are here too
"Where should I go for food?"
Things we talked through together are also here!
My Hermes-san moe will be known too
Us 'Anonymous' are fine~
Densha, Your "Haa~ Haa~" will also be known!
Don't scare me like that OTL
Hey Densha
This is quite a serious problem
If you get caught, you will for sure be hated
Even Hermes-san won't appreciate
Her story being widely known
As a woman, if I am talked about where I don't know
I might dislike it
That is an honest opinion
Holding hands or going on a first date...
To a woman, they would want them to be kept as a secret between the two
To have what I said casually all recorded somewhere...
... ruins everything
How about when she confided in only you? Like the stalker story?
She will cry if she see that on the internet
Misunderstandings like "surfing" and mistakes being known will also be tough on her
If you look at it from a different approach, it will be like opening up her privacy
Scrutinized completely
I thought about it after all of your replies
This might be a betrayal toward Hermes-san
[Betrayal]
Betrayal...
I never even thought about it
Did I betray Hermes-san?
Well, these are all "if"s, so don't worry too much
Can we decide that these are only "if"s? Nope! Can't do that!
It will be better if you tell her before she finds out
Densha, if you feel guilty, better to tell her
If you tell her, she will hate you
There is less than one percent chance that she will find out
If she never finds out, it won't be a betrayal
I think if you tell her carefully, she will understand
If I were Hermes-san... Sex, I mean end of friendship!
Hermes-san will be internet-shocked to death
When this forum is revealed
Densha's hope of going to the World Cup is gone~ Benoist~!
This is singles' headquarters
Densha, save the Earth!
Hey Densha, are you listening?
I tried everything...
But I think I can't go back there
Bye bye
Densha
Ouch ouchouchouch ouch!
Wait a second...
Is this small tank-like piece the heart of the probelm?
Wait for me, Densha!
All right. It's this! This one!
Where does this go?
Wait... what are you doing?
This...
No...
What is going on?
What are you talking about?
Why are they talking about my sister?
Did you do it?
No, I couldn't have done it!
Then...
Yamada did this
You came to me
To spy on my sister?
No, it's not that
Yes, you deliberately did it
Damn it
Wait
We are not trying to scare you
If you tell Hermes-san about this forum, it will be like committing suicide
Densha, we are giving you advice for your sake
We don't want to see you getting hurt
No, if you tell her, that is the end of the world
Can you give up all your hard work you put in?
We are fine with being singles all our lives
We don't mind being treated as stupid people
But for you
All we want is your happiness
We are putting all our hopes on you
So don't tell her
Whether you were betraying her or not
Depends on how you look at all this
Depends
Only on you
Ask yourself
"What did this forum mean to me?"
And find an answer
All your concerns
Are greatly appreciated
Thank you
For worrying for me
But
I can't stay like this
On this forum...
I have written
All the conversations between her and me
To her...
That might be
Too cruel
But
If I didn't write on this forum
I couldn't have
Met
Hermes-san
If I didn't write on this forum
I couldn't have
Liked myself as I do now
And moreover
I couldn't have
Met such precious friends
Because always
You guys were beside me
I could
Try my best
This forum
Is my pride
So
Now
I will tell her
About this forum
My precious heart for her
Your precious concerns
I would like her to know them
Lastly,
With sincerity that can't be expressed in words
Guys,
Sorry
And
Thank you
What is going on?
You look so serious
You were played by that man, Yamada
Huh?
That bastard
He wrote everything about you on the internet
The meetings with you, your trauma
Funnily and bizarrely he wrote about them and made a fool out of you
It's a lie...
That is...
[Haa~ Haa~]
He is the worst...
[Stalker]
[Surfing]
That bastard betrayed you