Didn't you have work?
I'm sorry.
To be honest, I was surprised.
Yes.
So you were..
lying to me.
I thought I could finally...
I'm sorry.
I...
At such an important time...
I believed you...
_         Love
Sunday   PC   Aoyama-san / Yamada Tsuyoshi
This guy...
Woa, what an Otaku.
I don't think we should see each other any more.
Bye.
Um...
So that,
was Densha and Hermes.
Were you able to meet him?
Do you want a ride?
Ankle Princess              _
I wonder why Men have to always lie.
Aren't you drinking too much?
It's ok.
Is it?
I wonder why I can't forgive those lies.
I too scared now...
You know,
Saori?
Did her cup size change?
Tsuyoshi.
Say something when you get back.
Enter Message
[So tomorrow Densha tells her how he feels.]
[So this is it then.  It really makes you think.]
[Let's all send him off in a big way.]
So Saori's Hermes.
Right now,
the Angel and the Devil are fighting inside of me.
Hey, hey, what are you thinking of?
This is the girl you've looked after like a sister!
Idiot!
The girl in front of you is Hermes.
"I'm holding on"?  THAT Hermes.
Saori's looked up to you like an older brother.
She'll lose faith!
Get real.
"I was leading you that way from the beginning"?  That's Hermes.
Don't listen to what this guy is saying.
Take her home.
Shut up already.
Get lost.
Sorry, good me.
Wow, look at the time!
What a dream.
I'm sorry I fell asleep.
No, it's ok.
I changed back into an angel again.
Do you want a ride back?
I got dumped by Hermes-san today.
What happened?  Weren't you supposed to meet her tomorrow?
Why? Why? Why?
G, g, give us the details.
Hermes came to Comike to bring me something I lost.
And that's when she saw me in full Otaku mode.
Then she suddenly started crying.
It's The End.
That's why I told you not to go to Comike!
It's just what we feared!! Shiver, shiver.
Why do women hate Otakus!
That even Hermes can't accept Otakus;
Les Miserables
Would she cry just because of that?
I thought so too.
A prejudice wouldn't cause her to cry.
It could be there's another reason.
They say a women's heart is as fickle as the sea.
It's because you lied about work.
It's because you were drooling over those cosplay girls.
She was definitely shocked that you were an Otaku.
I'm clueless.
The mystery just deepens.
It's ok.
Knowing the reason won't fix anything now.
Densha!  If you give up now, you'll revert to your old self.
You've always been able to get back on your feet.
Were your feeling for Hermes so light?!!
Yeah!  Don't give up so easily!
Why don't you keep trying to become a better man?
Get on the offensive again!
This isn't the Densha I remember!
You can still evolve!
Get up!!
Densha!!
I'm sorry.  It's no good.
I didn't know it hurt so much to be rejected.
I'm scared to try again.
You idiot.
I can understand that.
It must hurt.
Short/Long Term Overseas Studies
The Train Man
Original Story
"Densha Otoko"  by Nakano Hitori
Script:
Takefuji Shougo
Openning Theme
"Twilight" by Electric Light Orchestra
Itou Misaki
Itou Atsushi
Shiraishi Miho
Sudou Risa
Satou Eriko
Hayami Mokomichi
Kishibe Shirou
Toyohara Kousuke
Akiyoshi Kumiko
Openning Anime Production       Character Design
GONZO                               OKAMA
Director
Kobayashi Kazuhiro
Look,
We can't have you constantly changing workplaces like that.
But see,
I don't want to work there anymore.
We still have a responsibility to our clients.
What's that face?
Sir, could you get her a new placement somewhere?
Eh? Eh? Eh? She's a friend of yours?
No, we just met.
Oh, so that's, that's, how-
I got it.
Oikawa-kun, your wish is my wish.
Hey, someone!
Someone!
Yamada!
Find someplace for Jinnkama-san to work.
Yamada,
if you don't come here in 5 seconds,
I'm going to drop you.
Can't you forgive a lie like that?
He was just playing while he was supposed to be at work.
He rejected Saori's company and went to a Otaku festival.
No wonder I felt something was wrong.
It's only right that it ends here.
Stop it.
Yamada-san isn't at fault.
It was just a small lie...
He-
There's nothing you can do.  It's not your fault.
Hey,
Don't go easy on Yamada.
Eh?
You don't think it'll work out either right?
If that's what you really think,
you should make it a clean break.
If you don't, you'll both suffer more than you have to.
So give him the cold shoulder.
Got it?
Can't you do something about that negative energy?
Misuzu-san!
Hey, what're you doing?
What a coincidence.
Isn't it?
We're going to go eat, but do you guys want to come too?
Keisuke, wait.
Can he come too?
Sure.
I gotta go back and write up some reports.
You're coming too.
Yamada-kun,
prepare the Shabu-shabu for us won't you?
Don't keep staring at your boyfriend like that.
I'm not.
And he's not my boyfriend.
It's almost my sister's birthday.
You didn't have to say that.
When is it?
August 21st.
Make sure you celebrate it with her.
I'm sure my sister wants you to.
Keisuke.
Oh, I forgot.
I've been called by Sakurai-san.
Later.
I'm sorry.
I remembered I have to be someplace too.
Later.
Wait-
Jinnkama-san!
I told you, I have to be somewhere!
Um..
I'm so sorry about what happened last time.
It doesn't concern me anymore.
Eh?
I don't plan on seeing you again.
Um.
Which one is the dream?
The time we were together,
or the now that I can't be with you anymore?
Which is it?
The days we spent together...
weren't any dream.
They were irreplacablely precious and real.
But now...
They've ended.
[Aoyama-san's birthday]
The days we spent together...
weren't any dream.
They were irreplacablely precious and real.
I met Hermes-san by accident today,
and it's all clear now.
She's was irreplaceable to me,
and this is true even now.
I can't let it end this way.
All right, Densha!
I was waiting for you to say that!
Just when things started happening!!
Then to start, we have to find out why she was so upset.
That was because you put Comike before her.
No, it was because he turned out to be an Otaku.
I'm sure a regular woman like Hermes will have some
kind of bias against Otaku.
Do you think?
It it really because I'm an Otaku?
Then it's easy.  Give up being an Otaku!
Don't say that lightly.  It isn't that easy.
It's not just about changing your appearance like before.
Are you going to turn your back on your animes and figures?
Densha's been posessed!
Losing your Otaku means changing
your personality and the way you think!
You can't just wash away your Otaku personality with soap!
Why can't you take pride in your Otakuness?
Densha, forget this madness!!!
He's possessed!
I liked you when you acted like an Otaku!
Give it up.
I only sympathized with you because you were an Otaku.
Everyone, let's all respect Densha's choice here.
I'm sorry,
but I want to make up with Hermes.
This is going to upset some of you,
but I think I'm going to try losing my Otaku.
Just because you stop being an Otaku,
it doesn't mean Hermes will like you.
Densha, don't worry about it.
We'll still support you.
I'm disappointed in you Densha.
It's sad, but escape from our bonds and go your own way.
I'm proud of your decision.
Do what you have to until you're satisfied.
I think it's great that you chose Hermes.
It's too bad,
but we all want you and Hermes to get back together.
Don't look back!  Now go young master!
Thanks everyone!
I'll do my best to lose my Otakuness.
What is it?  You said it's important?
It's about going to study in America.
That again.
I'm serious.
I want to study acting.
That's a lie.
I'm serious!
If you were serious, you wouldn't be standing here.
Enough about that.  This is your schedule for tomorrow.
First thing we have...
Karin, Karin-chan?
Too bad Densha.
While you're busy trying to lose your Otaku,
Saori's going to fall in love with me.
And that'll grow into true love.
How about something light?
Herme-  Saori!
What is it, Kazuya-san?
I just happened to be passing thru,
so I thought you might want to get something to eat.
The two of us.
But-
You don't have to worry about us.
Right.
You two have fun.
Sorry.
Don't be.
Let's go.
They seem to be getting along.
I hope it goes well between those two.
Deal with the room first.
Get rid of all your figures.
I can't.
It looks like you're going to have to put your personal feelings aside.
Sell all your games for the money.
\2300
\1500
\320
The more they mean, the less they're worth.
We're having a promotional deal.
Cheer up, take one.
Top Prize.
Top Prize?
The latest game console and 10 games.
That's more than I started with.
You have to be careful where you throw them out.
Goodbye, Zaku.
To everyone who gave up their lives in Operation Odessa,
we give our profound thanks.
All hands,
Atten-hut.
Matilda-san.
Matilda-san!
Are you also a fan?
Maybe not?
Ok, then.
In a hurry, gotta go.
I'm sorry.  Sorry to the 100th power.
Am, Amuro?
Why?
The guy who found the boxes
saw these labels and brought them here.
How about these?
He brought them too.
My collection increased again...
Matilda-san.
For Matsunaga-san           For Kawamoto-san
You're really going to quit being an Otaku?
Yes.
You have no regrets?
No.
Yamada-shi, I think it best if you re-consider.
I got it.
Let's begin.
Yamada Tsuyoshi.
You have overcome countless hurdles
and now are graduating from being a true Otaku.
I hereby declare you non-Otaku.
I'm to give these to you.
I might have been infected!
Yamada Tsuyoshi-kun
Banzai!
Thank you.
What is it?
It seems we're always together nowadays.
Do you mind?
No.
It's your birthday next Sunday right?
Uh huh.
Do you have plans?
I'm going to celebrate with Kaho and Yuuko.
Then do it at my place.
We'll make it grand.
I'll ask them then.
Noritake
Yoshino (5 pc Dessert Plate Set)
incl. taxes    \26,250
That's steep!
Take care guys.
All right.
I've successfully graduated from being an Otaku.
I've also managed to get hold of a suitable
present for Hermes' birthday tomorrow.
Can anyone give me some serious
suggestions for what I should say?
You're going to have to call her of course.
Even if she doesn't answer, you can leave her voice mail.
Since it's her birthday tomorrow, why not call her at midnight?
Isn't it rude calling her so late?
It's different if it's her birthday.
She won't mind if it's a congratulatory call.
I just remembered an old boyfriend
who used to call me on my birthday.
"I want to meet you on your birthday",
it makes it easier to ask her doesn't it?
That's true.
She still might not say yes.
She's probably got plans, so tell her you only need a bit of her time.
Show her a part of you you've never shown.
Your masculine side.
Be firm.
Be aggressive.
Just don't back down.
I don't have confidence.
It can be an act.
It's enough that she thinks you might have changed.
You have to do this to break free from your Otaku image.
You just have tell her how you feel without anything holding back.
I think I can do that.
I'll think about how I'll tell her on my own.
"I'll think about it on my own", huh.
You've grown.
Wait for me Densha,
That guy needs me.
Yamada Tsuyoshi
Yes?
Uh,
This is Yamada calling.
Congratulations on your birthday.
What is this?
You see,
I wanted to hand something to you today.
I think I told you already.
I won't see-
I don't want to think-
Yes?
I don't want to think you were just a dream.
At 7 o'clock today,
I'll be waiting where we first met.
I won't go.
I'll be waiting anyway.
Goodbye.
Was that too aggressive?
This is for Saori.
No, I'm offering this to Hermes.
I have a present for you.
What is it?
Here,
this will be our first ritual together.
This way.
That's so pretty!
Hermes.
I want you to forgive me
for not realizing we were destined for each other.
Hermes.
Densha,
Hermes is mine now.
Application for Divorce
Aoyama Kengo
What is that?
Hm?
I'm practicing some magic.
It's your birthday today isn't it?
I thought I would show you something.
Really?
I was joking.
So where are you off to?
A date maybe?
No.
Kayo and some friends are throwing me a party.
Really?
You didn't break up did you?
It's none of your business.
So that's why.
You don't glitter the way you used to.
I haven't changed a bit.
See you later.
Glitter huh?
Hermes-san's birthday's finally here.
She probably won't come.
But I think I'll wait.
Not just so I can say I did.
Up until now I thought time passed at the same rate.
But it doesn't.
When I'm waiting for her, time seems to stretch on for eternity.
When I'm with her, it passes in an instant.
I don't want to have any regrets about
this relationship that taught me so much.
And you were ones who reminded me of this.
I'm always the one relying on you,
but I have nothing to give you in return.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to make up for that by waiting here.
Probably,
as time passes...
I'll become so sad
it'll hurt.
And get scared,
and want to leave.
But I'll stay and wait for her.
Because you guys are here for me.
I know.
You can do it.
We're there for you.
We'll be waiting here too.
The ticket's only one way.
Fight!  Densha.
Densha-kun, you can do it.
Persevere!
Give it everything!
We'll keep cheering you on.
Have confidence.
We'll be watching over you.
We're all there for you.
Densha, keep at it.
It's all heart.
Densha-san, you can do it.
Hermes, go to him.
As long as you wait, she'll come.
Who does she think she is?
Going off to study?
Bring her back.
Sir,
Please let her go.
You knew about this?
Please.
She's serious.
[Hirayama Manager
I'm serious about this!!
-Karin]
You can do it, Karin.
[Hirayama Manager
I'm serious about this!!
-Karin]
_
Please let her go!
[Happy Birthday]
[Hermes   Densha Otoko]
Saori,
where's Sakurai-san?
It doesn't look like he's here yet.
Sakurai-san...
Shoot!
Everyone sure is late.
Maybe I got the time wrong.
Yes, Healthy Drink-
Hey, Keisuke!
What are you doing?
Today's party-
Oh, they changed the venue.
They changed the venue?
Uh huh.
Got it.
Tell me earlier!
I can't prepare this somewhere else!
I'll be right there Hermes.
Wait for me.
Are you waiting for someone?
You look like you're worried about the time.
No, not really.
Ok, then I won't worry.
There aren't any good men today.
Do you want to go somewhere to drink after this?
Actually, I can't.
You have something else?
Misuzu-san!
Who is she?
Just someone I know.
It suddenly started raining.
Really?
Are you ok?
Good evening.
Misuzu-san.
Happy Birthday.
Thank you.
Do you mind?
No.
He isn't here?
Yamada Tsuyoshi.
So I guess he's waiting somewhere else.
You know,
he's so awkward, and such a dunce.
I get noxious just being near him.
Even then,
I somehow can't leave him alone.
Don't get me wrong,
it's not like there's anything going on with us.
Hey,
Do you think time passes constantly?
Hm?
That guy told me,
When you're waiting for someone you like,
time seems to stretch on for eternity.
And when you're with them,
it passes in an instant.
Right now,
he's probably waiting for what feels like eternity.
Was waiting anyway.
In this rain I guess even he would have left by now...
Saori!
Sakurai-san.
Keisuke.
Herme-
Where's Saori?
There.
Saori.
Kazuya-san.
I want you to come with me.
I've got something I want to show you.
I was so close.
Who is that guy?
Sorry for dragging you out so suddenly.
I had to show you something.
We're almost there.
You'll definitely be surprised.
And I think you'll be happy.
Stop the car.
Hm?
Stop the car!
What is it?
You wanted to bring me here?
No, no.
To my store.
You brought me here to meet Yamada-san?
Uh huh.
Well...
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Huh? Wait-
What just happened?
Aoyama-san.
What are you doing?
I was going to go buy an umbrella,
but then...
I was afraid we'd miss each other.
What were you thinking of?
Your face when you smile.
That's what I was imagining.
I, I've...
stopped being an Otaku.
I wanted to be...
worthy of you.
You're wrong.
That's not why.
That's not why I was angry.
It's my fault.
Because I couldn't forgive...
such a small lie.
I'm sorry.
If we're together for any longer,
I'll just hurt you more.
So...
Yamada-san?
Happy...
Birth...
day.
Yamada-san!
I'll...
become...
a better man.
much...
Yamada-san!
Are you ok?
Next Week
This peice of fiction was based on a true story.